<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 31.  A great Union meeting occurred to-day in this city.  There has been a sharp battle near Somerset, Kentucky.  The rebels were defeated.  Jacksonville, Florida, has been evacuated by Union troops.  The town has been burned by Union soldiers.  The Union gunboat St. Clair was attacked by the rebels on the Cumberland.  The woods near Washington, North Carolina, has been shelled by Union gunboats.  The rebels opened fire on the fort back of Washington, North Carolina, the place being closely invested by the rebels.  The rebel batteries at Grand Gulf on the Mississippi has been attacked.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 30.  Point Pleasant, Virginia, has been catpured by rebels, but subsequently recaptured by Union troops.  The investment of Washington, North Carolina, has commenced.  Richmond, near Vicksburgh, has been taken possession of by Union forces.  WASHINGTON, Friday, March 27. The Administration is in receipt of reliable information to the effect that the rebels are preparing to abandon Richmond as the capital of the Confederate Government. The fortifications in and around the city, which have been unoccupied for some time, are being put in order for occupation for that part of LEE's army which has been falling back.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 29.  Our pickets have reportedly been driven in at Washington, North Carolina.  Our fleet has reached the Coldwater River, near Vicksburgh, by the Yazoo Pass.  Williamsburg, Virginia, was attacked to-day by the rebels.  Rebel news from FORT PEMBERTON, Friday, March 20. Gen. LORING has whipped the enemy back from this point. They are now in full retreat to Yazoo Pass. A dispatch dated March 10 says the old troops of the enemy have been replaced by new ones.  The fleet continues out of sight. The two vessels above have been slowly steaming up the river. They landed, and cut down a few poles and telegraph wires. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 28.  Danville, Kentucky, has been recaptured by Union troops.  A Union train was captured between Memphis, Tennessee, and Grand Junction.  Cole's Island, nine miles from Charleston, South Carolina, has reportedly been taken possession of by Union troops.  The Steamer Aries was captured running the blockade at Charleston.  The Union gunboat Diana was captured by rebels in Louisiana.  The Treasury Department is evidently highly gratified with the daily accounts received of the increased improvement in our National finances.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 27.  This has reportedly been declared Fast day in the Confederate States.  A deserter was shot at Indianpolis, Indiana, to-day.  Rebel Col. Talcott has been arrested in New York City.  Palatka, Florida, has been occupied by a Union regiment of colored troops.  Admiral Farragut's troops have engaged the rebel batteries at Warrenton, three miles below Vicksburgh.  The bark Lapwing and M. J. Colcord have been taken by the Florida.  U.S. troops have landed at Cole's Island, near Charleston, South Carolina.  A bombardment of Fort Pemberton, at Vicksburgh, has commenced.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 26.  A skirmish occurred to-day near Camp Dick Robinson, Kentucky.  Orange Grove, Floriday, has reportedly been occupied by a Union regiment of colored soldiers.  Dispatches to the Navy Department announce that Admiral FARRAGUT's flag-ship, the Hartford, was below Warrenton on the 20th. This confirms the report received by way of New-Orleans, that she had succeeded in passing the rebel batteries at Port Hudson. It is announced further, however, that she is the only one of the fleet which did succeed in passing them. Admiral FARRAGUT's Secretary was on his way to communicate with Admiral PORTER.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 25.  Union troops were captured to-day at Brentwood, Tennessee.  The Union rams Lancaster and Switzerland attempted to run past the batteries at Vicksburg.  The Lancaster was sunk and the Switzerland was captured.  Confederate President Jeff. Davis has signed a bill for the impressment of property.  From France, there is a good deal of talk about a loan of 60,000,000 francs, to be contracted by the seceding States, and the emission of which in Europe, and especially in France, would place the Imperial Government in a very embarrassing position. The South is in high favor with many eminent financiers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 24.  A guerrilla party has been captured near Stafford Courthouse, Virginia.  Our fleet has commenced to enter the Yazoo Pass near Vicksburgh.  Considerable excitement was created in Wall-street, yesterday afternoon, by the appearance of a well-executed counterfeit  SX 500 bill, purporting to have been issued by the Central Bank of Worcester, Mass. It was so well done, and so nearly did it resemble the genuine, that Messrs. GWYNNE  ES  DAY, money brokers, of No. 21 Wall-street, received it as genuine. The paper, engraving, and in fact everything about it, is so much an imitation, that good judges pronounce the spurious note to be a photograph.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 23.  Our pickets at Chantilly, Virginia, were attacked to-day.   A protion of Pensacola, Florida, has been destroyed by Union troops.   The following telegram was yesterday received at the New-England Rooms: S.W. PASS, Louisiana, Sunday, March 15. Commodore FARRAGUT passed the Port Hudson batteries, last night, with his fleet. The steamer Mississippi was aground, abandoned and burned. Col. CLARKE was wounded, yesterday, but not seriously. No big fight yet. General is well and in good spirits, and within five miles of Port Hudson with the army. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 22.  Gen. Wool, commanding the Department of the East, issued an order to-day relative to deserters.  Rebel forces captured Mount Sterling, Kentucky, and burned the town.  The steamer Granite City has been captured off the Bahamas.   The telegraphic wire from Fortress Monroe sends a series of shocking magnetic shocks. There are but four brief and jerky paragraphs in the dispatch, yet each one of them thrills the nerves. A battle on the Blackwater in Virginia -- an attack on Newbern, in North Carolina -- a naval fight at Port Hudson, in Mississippi -and the capture by the French of the capital of our neighboring republic of Mexico.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 21.  The steamer Nicholas I. has been captured off Wilmington, North Carolina.  The steamer Aries has been captured off Charleston.   NEW YORK, March 21.  Gen. E. V. Sumner died at his daughter's house in Syracuse to-day.  NEW YORK, March 20.  The subject of the Atlantic Telegraph was presented to the Board of Brokers, yesterday, by Mr. CYRUS W. FIELD, and was very favorably received. Resolutions pledging the aid and influence of the Board in favor of the enterprise were adopted, and a Committee to solicit subscriptions is to be appointed to-day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 20.  To-day there was an engagement at Milton, Tennessee.  Two of Commodore Farragut's vessels arrived at the mouth of the canal opposite Vicksburgh.  A fight reportedly occurred to-day at Auburn, Tennessee.  From the Richmond Dispatch, March 13. The prisoners captured by Capt. MOSBY arrived in Richmond by the Central cars on Wednesday night.  The prisoners were taken in custody on the night of March 9, near Fairfax Court-house, by Capt. MOSBY and his command, whose daring and intrepidity in making a successful raid within a few hundred yards of the camp ground of two Abolition brigades deserves the highest praise.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 19.  The Anglo rebel steamer Georgiana has ran ashore near Charleston.  The rebel cavalry crossed Duck River, advancing toward Franklin, Tennessee, but were driven back by Union cavalry.  Rebel guerrillas to-day attacked a railroad train near Richland, Kentucky.  PORT HOOD, Nova Scotia, Monday, March 16. We have been unable to work through the Newfoundland Telegraph cable since Thursday last, and fears are entertained that it is broken, or that something serious has happened to the operator at Port au Basque, the first station on the Newfoundland side. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 18.   A brilliant cavalry fight reportedly occurred yesterday at Kelly's Ford on the Rappahannock.  The steamer Calypso arrived at Charleston, South Carolina, having run the blockade.  Gen. ROSECRANS has telegraphed to the War Department a report which has reached him, to the effect that the rebels have evacuated Vicksburgh. Information had previously reached Washington that they were removing their stores and war material into the interior, and the report of the evacuation is quite likely to be true. A positive confirmation of the destruction of the Indianola by the rebels has been sent to the Navy Department by Admiral PORTER.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 17.  There has reportedly been spirited fighting on the Blackwater with an unsuccessful attempt to carry the rebel breastworks.  PHILADELPHIA -- The Chief of the Detectives of the city recieved information that parties were engaged in shipping goods for the South by means of the Delaware Railroad.  A lot of goods at Adams' Express office was found to be ready to be forwarded. A visit was paid to the express office, and there he discovered several boxes, which, on examination, proved to contain 150 pounds of surgical needles, 265 pounds of quinine and morphine, 150 pounds of chloroform, and a large number of surgical instruments.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, March 16.  To-day there was a great Union meeting in Brooklyn.  WASHINGTON, March 16.  Water has reportedly been admitted into the canal at Lake Providence, near Vicksburgh.  PHILIADELPHIA, March 7. A prominent and leading Democrat of this city was discussing public affairs recently, denouncing the Government and advocating peace most vehemently. Among his auditors was a colored man, a contraband, who knew the inside of the rebellion, and could see the beating of the gentleman's argument. After listening patiently awhile he remarked, addressing the speaker,  QN I don't know who you is, but you talk just as they do down in Richmond. QN  -- Providence Journal. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 15.  The schooner Chapman has been taken possession of at San Francisco as a privateeer.   A telegram from Salt Lake City made the announcement, unexpected by most people, that a collision between the military and the Mormon citizens of Utah was imminent -- that the Governor of the Territory had ordered the arrest of the Prophet, and that the Saints were in arms to prevent it.  Gov. HARDING, during his brief term of office, has become very offensive, officially and personally, to the Mormons. His inaugural speech was directly in antagonism with their religions prejudices, social customs and political proclivities.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 14.  Port Hudson has been attacked by Admiral Farragut's fleet.  The steamer Mississippi ran aground and was burned.  Rebel Gen. Fitzhugh Lee made an advance on our lines at Gloucester, Virginia, but reportedly retired upon learning that we had been reinforced.  The engagement at Deep Gully, North Carolina, continued to-day.  The ship Punjaub was captured by the Alabama.  The reports telegraphed from the West are still conflicting. The rumor which reached us from Memphis a day or two ago, that Yazoo City had been captured by the forces which went up the Yazoo Pass, has not been confirmed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 13.  The rebels attacked Newbern, North Carolina, to-day.  There has reportedly been a fight between the Union gunboat Chillicothe and the rebel Fort Pemberton, near Vicksburgh, at the mouth of the Tallahatchie River.  There has also been a fight at Deep Gully, North Carolina, between Union and rebel infantry forces.  Rebel Gen. Van Dorn's forces have reportedly escaped from before Gen. Rosecran's at Duck River, Tennessee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 12.  The rebels successfully raided Hilton Head, South Carolina, during the night.  The gunboat Chillicothe was attacked to-day at the town of Greenwood, near Vicksburgh.  From the Army of the Potomac, corroborated by reports from the rebels themselves, a large numbers of the rebel troops are being withdrawn from the vicinity of Fredericksburgh. It is known positively that LONGSTREET has gone, taking his entire division with him. We have another bad report from Tennessee. It is stated in a dispatch from Jackson that two hundred men and two pieces of artillery belonging to Gen. SULLIVAN's division have been surrounded by rebel cavalry.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 11.  The rebel steamer Parallel has been burned on the Tallahatchie River.  MEMPHIS, March 11.  An engagement has taken place at Port Hudson. If there has been a battle there, it is pretty certain to have been a victory for our forces -- else we should before now have heard of it from the rebels. Important changes in the rebel army are noted in our telegrams this morning. PEMBERTON, until recently commanding in the Department of the Mississippi, has been removed, and BRAGG has been put in his place. while LONGSTREET has taken command of BRAGG's old division in Middle Tennessee. It is said also that PRICE is again to operate in Missouri.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 10.  To-day, President Lincoln issued a proclamation ordering soldiers absent from their regiments to return immediately.  Skirmishing commenced at Rutherford's Creek, near Columbia, Tennessee.  Gen. VanDorn's force retreated toward Shelbyville, Tennessee.  ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, Wednesday, March 4. Gen. WYNDHAM's command has visited all the principal points east of the Shenandoah and north of the Rappahannock Rivers, without encountering any force whatever of the rebel regular troops. Small detachments of the command had skirmishes at different points with WHITE's guerrillas.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 9.  The rebels have reportedly entered Fairfax Court House, Virginia, and captured Brig. Gen. E. H. Stoughton and his guard.  The Anglo-rebel steamer Douro has been captured by the Quaker City.  The Washington Star states positively that Maj.-Gen. DIX telegraphed the President on Tuesday evening, stating that rebel papers had been received at Fortress Monroe, containing the important intelligence that Fort McAllister had fallen into the hands of the Union forces. The Washington Republican is equally positive in its assertion that such a telegram was received by the President.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 8.  To-day, the schooner Enterprise was captured off the coast of Florida.  NEW YORK, March 8.  The Inman screw-steamer City of New-York, Capt. PETRIE, which sailed from Liverpool at 11 o'clock on the morning of the 18th, and from Queenstown on the afternoon of Feb. 19, arrived here yesterday morning. She brings the United States mails and 449 bales of cotton. Her advices have been mostly anticipated.  A very limited business was transacted at the Produce Exchange. Flour was quoted down 15c. TO 25c. per bbl.. Wheat, nominally, 5c. TO 8c., and Corn 2c. TO 3c per bushel. Provisions and Whisky were also generally cheaper.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 7.  An expedtion reportedly continued to-day into Northumberland County, Virginia.  There is a large capture of provisions etc.  A cavalry engagement occurred at Unionville, Tennessee, near Murfreesboro.  The Yazoo Pass expedition arrived in the Tallahatchie.  Meetings and lectures in favor of President LINCOLN'S emancipation policy are of daily occurrence in various parts of England.  The resolutions and addresses to President LINCOLN, which are to be proposed, emphatically approve of his Anti-Slavery policy. A crowded meeting on the subject was held at St. James Hall, London, on the 18th of February.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 6.  It is reported that yesterday, Gen. Halleck addressed a letter to Gen. Rosecrans relative to the treatment of disloyal persons.  NEW YORK, March 6.  At a meeting for the Atlantic Telegraph enterprise, Mssrs. Cooper and Field said an ocean telegraph would offer incalculable advantages to our great agricultural interests, from the prompt knowledge of the prices ranging in European markets, and the facility afforded European dealers for forwarding orders. Another great advantage would result from the avoidance of any misunderstanding between Great Britain and the United States -- one such prevention would more than pay for the cable.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 5.  To-day there was a severe engagement near Springville, Tennessee.  Brig. Gen. H. M. Naglee was relieved of his command by Gen. Hunter.  Gen. Colburn's force has reportedly been captured by rebels at Thompson's Station, Tennessee.  BOSTON, March 5 -- Arrived bark Amy, Messina, Lawrence, New-Orleans. The brig Herald, Capt. Wing, arrived to-day from St. Domingo City, brings home Capt. James Warren, late of the brig Chastelain, lately burned by the Confederate steamer Alabama. There are also eight seamen from that vessel and the bark Golden Rule, also burned.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 4.  Congress adjourned to-day.  A skirmish has occurred near Franklin, Tennessee, and at Skeet, North Carolina.  The Senate bill to organize a Signal Corps, after amendment, was passed. The House concurred in the Senate's amendment to the bill granting permission to the Independent Telegraph Company -- the line extending from Portland to Washington to extend their wires into the District of Columbia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 3.  The gunboat Indianola was destroyed by the rebels to-day.  An expedition has reportedly left Belle Plain, Virginia, for Northumberland County, Virginia.  An act amendatory to the tax law passed both houses of Congress to-day, as amended by a conference committee.  NEW YORK, March 3.  The City Inspector reports that 426 persons died in New-York during the past week, 87 men, 92 women, 132 boys, and 115 girls -- a decrease of 29 from the mortality of the previous week, and of 2 as compared with the mortality of the corresponding week of 1862. Of the deceased, 221 were children under five years of age.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 2.  The Ship John A. Park was captured and burned by the Alabama.  ROCHESTER, N.Y., Saturday, Feb. 28. ISAAC B. ELWOOD, an old and esteemed citizen and Secretary and Treasurer of the Western Union Telegraph Company from the date of its organization, died last night. He was run over by a runaway team while in his own sleigh some days since, and the injuries then received have proved fatal. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 1.  To-day, the rebels were defeated at Bradyville, Tennessee.  NEW YORK, Feb. 28.  About 1 1E2 o'clock yesterday morning, a collision occurred at the Princeton Station, between the 11:15 P.M. owl train, from Philadelphia, and the 11:30 passenger train, from Jersey City, by which three cars filled with passengers were more or less broken up, and about twenty persons are reported injured. It appears that the train from Philadelphia, upon which was about 400 passengers, was behind time. The telegraph operator had neglected to display the red signal lamp of danger until he heard the whistle of the locomotive close by.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 28.  President Lincoln called and extra session of the Senate.  Col. Wyndham's cavalry arrived at Falmouth, Virginia.  The rebel steamer Nashville was destroyed by the Montauk in Ogeechee River, Georgia.  The Yazoo Pass expedition reached the Coldwater River, twelve miles from Moon Lake, through Yazoo Pass.  Although the Signal Corps connected with the army has not as yet been recognized by the War Department as a separate and distinct organization, still there are various urgent reasons favoring the adoption of the system which it is proposed to inaugurate. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 27.  Col. Wyndham's cavalry left Centreville, Virginia, on a reconnaissance, afterward reaching Falmouth, Virginia.  Brig.-Gen. John Cochrane, having resigned his commission, took leave of his corps of the Army of the Potomac.  Confederate President Jefferson Davis issued a proclamation appointing March 27 as Fast Day in the Confederate States.  Gen. Stevenson was released from arrest by Gen. Hunter.  Three Anglo-rebel steamers, the Georgiana, the Britannia and the Gertrude, arrived at Nassau.  A sham monitor sent by Admiral Porter passed the rebel batteries at Vicksburgh.  The schooner Palmetto has been captured by the Alabama.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 26.  An expedition through Yazoo Pass, near Vicksburgh, left Moon Lake.  Col. D.D. Thompkins died to-day.  LOUISVILLE, Ky., Tuesday, Feb. 24. The Journal, of this city, gives various reports concerning the rebel invasion of the State on the borders of the Blue Grass region. It thinks that the rebels are threatening Lexington, Frankfort, Danville and Louisville. The same paper learns by telegraph that seven hundred rebel cavalry were at Nicholasville yesterday morning, supposed to be about cutting the Louisville and Lexington Railroad, near Medway. It expresses the belief that this last rebel invasion is a formidable one. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 25.  A cavalry skirmish has occurred at Piedants Farm, Virginia.  A cavalry fight occurred near Strasburgh, Virginia.  Our forces were defeated.  The Privateer Retribution arrived at Nassau.  The Anglo-rebel steamer Peterhoff was captured by the Vanderbilt near St. Thomas.   WASHINGTON, Monday, Feb. 23. Gen. HOOKER has been in the city, and was to-day in consultation with the President and Secretary of War. Late accounts from the Army of the Potomac indicate greatly improved discipline, and give promise of a state of efficiency never before known there. Expeditions are making successful forays against the enemy, capturing supplies.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 24.  The iron-clad gunboat Indianola was captured by the rebels near Vicksburgh.  Some shells have been thrown into Galveston, Texas, by the Brooklyn.  WASHINGTON, Monday, Feb. 23. The Chair presented a communication from the Secretary of the Navy in response to a resolution of the Senate, transmitting reports of the relative condition of the steamers Ossipee and Pensacola. The Chair also presented resolutions from the Legislature of Kansas against any division of the country and in regard to public lands. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 23.  A bill authorizing the suspension of the writ of habeas corpus passed the United States Senate.  PORTLAND, Me., Sunday, Feb. 22. A special dispatch to the Press, from Augusta, states that both branches of the Legislature concurred in referring J.J. SPEED's petition for the incorporation of a new telegraph line to the next Legislature. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 22.  Richmond, Kentucky, is now occupied by rebel cavalry.  Tuscumbia, Alabama, has been reached by a Union cavalry force.  The ship Golden Eagle was destroyed by the Alabama.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, Feb. 21. Mr. HARRIS, of New-York, (Rep.,) presented a petition from a large number of the citizens of New-York City, asking for the establishment of a submarine telegraph from Fortress Monroe to Galveston.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 21.  The newsboys in the army are in a state of insubordination. They are evidently  QN demoralized. QN  The telegraph advises us that they have refused to do duty, unless Gen. HOOKER rescinds the order restricting their numbers to one to each division. This is quite in keeping with the general course of things in the army, so far as a portion of its officers and men are concerned. We are not at all surprised that the newsboys should have come to the conclusion that they had as good a right to command the army as Gen. HOOKER. He ought to get in the habit of submitting his orders for their approval, before issuing them. The sutlers may strike next.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 20.  The National Currency bill passed in the House of Representatives.  The United States steamer Alabama left St. Thomas in search of the Florida.  The Vanderbilt left St. Thomas on a cruise for privateers.  WASHINGTON, Feb. 18. The uncertainty which has prevailed concerning the future financial policy of Government is somewhat relieved by the summary action of the House on the Loan bill. The hostility thus manifested to Secretary CHASE's policy has demonstrated the power of the bank interest to dictate some of the terms in a destined compromise, and it seems very clear that neither party can achieve a complete triumph. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 19.  Brig Emily Fisher was captured and bonded by the privateer Retribution.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Feb. 17. The vote in the Senate to-day on the bill authorizing the President to grant letters-of-marque and reprisal was not strictly marked by party lines, and included in the opposing minority the names of Messrs. DAVIS, HENDERSON, SUMNER and TRUMBULL. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 18.  Gen. Beauregard issued a proclamation announcing that an attack on Charleston and Savannah would probably soon be made.  Vicksburgh, Mississippi has been bombarded.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Feb. 17. Messrs. FOOT, DAVIS, COLLAMER and HOWE presented petitions for camp hospital and ambulance corps. Mr. KING, of New-York, (Rep.,) presented the resolutions adopted at Turner Hall, in Brooklyn, N.Y., and a petition asking for equal privileges to all telegraph companies. Mr. COLLAMER, of Vermont, from the Post-office Committee, reported a joint resolution authorizing the collection of foreign postage in coin.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 17. Brig.-Gen. Thos. G. Stevenson has been placed in arrest by Gen. Hunter, at Port Royal, for objecting to fight in company with negroes.  NEW YORK, February 17.  The Independent Line of Telegraph, which has for some time been in operation between Portland and this City, has been completed to Philadelphia, having opened their office for business in that city yesterday. This line is being rapidly pushed forward to its completion at Washington. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 16.  The Conscription bill has been passed by the United States Senate.  NASHVILLE, Monday, Feb. 16. Yesterday a foraging party of the Second Minnesota Regiment, Gen. STEDMAN's brigade, camped near Nolinsville, had a severe skirmish with two companies of FORREST's command. Our men killed five and wounded five. The latter were taken prisoners. The balance of the rebels escaped. Twenty-six buildings are used in this city as hospitals for sick and wounded soldiers. An immense quantity of coal has arrived, including five barges loaded for the Government, consigned to one house, BARNARD, CHANDLER  ES  CO. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sunday, Feb. 15. Lieut.-Col. DOOR, of Gen. FOSTER's Staff, arrived here to-day, direct from Port Royal, with dispatches for the Government. He utterly denies the recent sensation reports in regard to a quarrel between Gens. HUNTER and FOSTER. The same denial is made by the President, and no reason exists to believe that anything has occurred likely to impair the efficiency of our army in the Department of the South. Two refugees, who arrived here to-day from Richmond, state that five brigades of troops from the Confederate army at Fredericksburgh passed through Richmond last Sunday, apparently on their way to Charleston. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 14.  A dispatch from Vicksburgh, dated the 5th inst., states that on the Thursday previous, a force from MCARTHUR's division, was sent Richmond, La., and captured the telegraph office at Tallula, La., with a large number of dispatches, and destroyed several miles of wire. This line extended from Lake Providence to Tallula, and was used to telegraph the names of steamers passing down the river. Just in front of Richmond they had a skirmish with rebel cavalry over a deep bayou, and had one man severely wounded. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 13.  A Court of Inquiry, relative to cotton and other traffic on the Mississippi River, has been instituted.  A skirmish has occurred near Bolivar, Tennessee.  The gunboat Indianola ran the blockade at Vicksburgh.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Feb. 11. As anticipated in our last evening's dispatch, the Bank bill to-day overrode all other questions in the Senate, and was debated nearly the whole day without a vote being reached. The speech of Mr. COLLAMER against it, and Mr. SHERMAN in favor, were both strong efforts. The prospect for the passage of the bill looks more favorable than it did yesterday. The vote is expected to be taken to-day. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 12.  The National Currency bill has been passed by the Senate.  A slight skirmish occurred near Smithfield, Virginia.  There has been a great fire at Norfolk, Virginia.  The ship Jacob Bell, from China, was captured and burned by the Florida.  The rebel fort on Pelican Island, near Galveston, Texas, has been shelled by the Brooklyn.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 11.  Secretary Seward transmitted to the Senate a communication relative to the visit of the French Minister to Richmond.  Following is the act to provide for the construction of a coastwise submarine cable, as it passed the House Feb. 4: Be it enacted by the Senate and House of Representatives of the United States of America in Congress assembled. That the Secretary of War is hereby, authorized to cause to be constructed and laid down a submarine cable from Fort McHenry, in Baltimore, or Fort Monroe, to Galveston, Texas, touching at Fort Macon, N.C.. Port Royal S.C.. Fernandina, Fla.. Key West, Fla.. Fort Pickens, Fla., and Galveston, Texas.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 10.  Gen. Rosecrans issued an order declaring that all rebel soldiers found in National uniforms should not be treated as prisoners of war or receive quarter in battle.  FORTRESS MONROE, Saturday, Feb. 7. The flag of truce boat New-York left this afternoon for City Point with thirty rebel prisoners, in charge of Capt. ALEXANDER MANN. Col. LUDLOW sent up on the boat a large supply of clothing and medical stores for the comfort of the Union prisoners in and about Richmond.  The storm has entirely cleared away, and the telegraph cable will soon be repaired. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 9.  A collision occurred to-day between the transport North Star and the steamer Ella Warley near Sandy Hook, New Jersey.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, Feb. 7. A communication was received from the Secretary of the Interior, asking for an increased appropriation of  SX 25,000 for land offices in Kansas. Mr. LANE, of Kansas, (Rep.,) presented a memorial from the Legislature of that State for an appropriation for land surveys. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 8.  Our forces entered Lebanon, Tennessee, capturing a number of rebels.  A telegraphic dispatch from San Francisco last night stated that among the arrivals of ships at that port, was one from Shanghai, bringing as cargo seven hundred bales of cotton goods (drills and sheetings) from China. Hereafter the California market will be liberally supplied with cotton goods from that quarter. Considering the present enormous prices of cotton goods in this country, this is not at all wonderful. Cotton can be raised in China cheaper than in any other part of the world, except the Southern States, owing to the great abundance and low price of labor.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 7.  Reconnaissance from the right wing of the Army of the Potomac occurred to-day.   There has been an engagement near Williamsburgh, Virginia.  WASHINGTON, Thursday, Feb. 5. As the speculation in gold is largely based on the idea that the Government will have to make large purchases of gold to pay its current interest, it may not be improper to state that the Government has bought no gold for the past six months, and has a sufficient supply now on hand for all its necessities for the next payments. In the Senate to-day, most of the time was spent in discussing Senator WILSON's bill authorizing the establishment of a National Guard.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 6.  A raid has occurred of Union cavalry to Middleburgh and Aldie, Virginia.  The House, by a vote of 71 against 63, passed the bill reported yesterday, authorizing the Secretary of War to contract for the construction of a telegraph cable from Fort McHenry or Monroe to Galveston or New-Orleans, and the intermediate points.  In the Senate, yesterday, the credentials of ALEX. S. RAMSEY, elected Senator from Minnesota, were presented. A bill to aid in the construction of railroads and telegraphs in Kansas was introduced. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 5.  Union forces repulsed a rebel attack on Fort Donelson, Tennessee.  The Union ram Queen of the West returned from her expedition past the batteries of Vicksburgh, having destroyed three rebel transports and an immense quantity of rebel stores.  YORKTOWN, Monday, Feb. 2. Nothing has transpired here of importance. On Tuesday some excitement prevailed, from the intelligence that our pickets had been driven in at Williamsburgh, and that the enemy was approaching in force. But it proved only to be a raid of guerrillas. They turned, at the approach of our forces, and were soon off toward Richmond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 4.  To-day there was an engagement at Fort McAllister, Georgia.  BALTIMORE, Monday, Feb. 2. A telegraphic dispatch was received announcing the capture of the British steam propeller Princess Royal while attempting to run the blockade into Charleston. At the time of the departure of the Princess Royal from Halifax for Bermuda, Northern papers announced the fact and gave a description of the vessel and cargo. The Federal cruisers were therefore on the lookout for her, and as she was making her way in before daylight on Thursday morning, she was suddenly surrounded, and her officers were compelled to run her on Long Island beach. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 3.  The rebels were repulsed in an attack on Union forces at Dover, Tennessee, by Union gunboats.  Fort Donelson, Tennessee, has been invested by the rebels.  LOUISVILLE, Sunday, Feb. 1. MORGAN, with a considerable force, is reported crossing the Cumberland River, above and below Rowena, either to cut the railroad or obtain possession of certain points in Northern and Central Kentucky. PHILADELPHIA, Sunday, Feb. 1. Mr. BOILEAU telegraphed his family this afternoon that he had been released from Fort McHenry, and will arrive home to-night. He will be received by a large number of friends. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 2.  A bill providing for the employment of negro soldiers passed the United States House of Representatives.  The rebel camp at Middletown, Tennessee, came under surprise attack.  The Department of Washington has been constituted under command of Gen. Heintzelman.  The Union ram Queen of the West ran past the rebel batteries at Vicksburgh, and attacked the rebel steamer City of Vicksburgh.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 1.  Franklin, Tennessee, is now occupied by Federal forces.  A.J. Boileau, editor of the Philadelphia Evening Journal, has been released from Fort McHenry.  Fort McAllister has been attacked again.  The gunboat New Era attacked Island No. 10 near New Madrid, Missouri.  NASHVILLE, Saturday, Jan. 31. One thousand cavalry, FORREST commanding, with a battery of four pieces of artillery, are still at the Shoals, awaiting the passage of the fleet to this point, which left from the vicinity of Franklin, Tenn., for that place last night. A stupendous effort for the capture of the boats on the Cumberland River is determined on by the rebels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 31.  The fleet blockading Charleston, South Carolina, has been attacked by the rebel iron-clads Chicora and Palmetto State.  Rebel Gen. Beauregard and Flag-Officer D.N. Ingraham formally declared by proclamation that the blockade of Charleston, South Carolina, was raised.  The Union gunboat Mercedita has surrendered.  Confederate Secretary of State, J.P. Benjamin, gave official notice that the blockade was broken.  The schooner Hanover was destroyed by the Retribution.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 30.  Victory of Gen. Corcoran over the rebel Gen. Roger A. Pryor's force near the Blackwater, the engagement being called the Battle of the Deserted House.   Union gunboat Isaac Smith has been captured by the rebels in the Stono River, South Carolina.  WASHINGTON, 11 O'CLOCK, Monday Evening, Jan. 26, 1863. It became known early this morning in the encampment, comprising  QN Headquarters, QN  that Gens. BURNSIDE, SUMNER and FRANKLIN had all three been relieved of their commands. The news occasioned the most profound sensation, and rapidly spread to the surrounding commands. By 11 o'clock it was generally known.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 29.  There is excitement in Philadelphia over the arrest of the editor of the Evening Journal.  The English steamer Princess Royal has been captured off Charleston, South Carolina.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Jan. 27. Mr. OLIN was instructed by the House Military Committee to report a bill, authorizing the Secretary of War immediately to contract for the construction of a submarine telegraph from Fort McHenry or Fortress Monroe to Galveston, touching at various points on the coast of North and South Carolina and Florida, and at Fort Dickens, and with a branch to New-Orleans.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 28.  Bombardment of Fort McAllister, on the Ogeechee River in Georgia, has been carried out by the Montauk.  Brig Chastelaine has been burned by the Alabama.  WASHINGTON, Sunday, Jan. 25. Major-Gen. CURTIS has telegraphed to Major Gen. HALLECK, General-in-Chief, under date of St. Louis, 24th, as follows: Gen. GORMAN telegraphs from Duval's Bluff, 18th inst., that aided by three gunboats, he ascended White River to Duval's Bluff and Des Arc, taxing one hundred and fifty prisoners two columbiads and about two hundred small arms. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 27.  Gen. Hooker visited Washington.  Gen. Burnside has arrived in New-York.  A cavalry skirmish has occurred at Middleburgh, Virginia.   New York Republican party leader Thurlow Week has taken leave of the Albany Evening Journal.    A.D. Boileau, proprietor of the Philadelphia Evening Journal, has been arrested by order of the Government.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 26.  Gen. Burnside has turned over command of the Army of the Potomac to Gen. Hooker.  Gen. Hooker, in General Orders, assumed command.  Gen. W.B. Franklin, having been relieved of his command in the Army of the Potomac, took leave of his division.  Gen Sumner is relieved of his command.  The bark Golden Rule was burned by the Alabama.  The ship Washington was captured by the Alabama.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 25.  Cars on the railroad, between Nashville and Franklin, Tennessee, have been destroyed by rebels.  SAN FRANCISCO, Saturday, Jan. 24.  The opposition steamer Moses Taylor is advertised to sail for Panama on the 11th of March.  The Legislature of Washington Territory has passed an act punishing persons refusing to receive  QN legal tender notes QN  at par, by imposing a fine of from five to ten hundred dollars, and imprisonment for six months. The telegraph poles are all set from the northern border of California to Vancouver, Washington Territory, and the wires will be placed on the poles in less than three months. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 24.  Gen Burnside is relieved of command of the Army of the Potomac and the command is assigned to Gen. Hooker.  PHILADELPHIA, Friday, Jan. 23. It is reported here that the sole offence of Mr. DEMING was endeavoring to communicate by telegraph to the Northern Press the address of Maj.-Gen. BURNSIDE to the soldiers, a copy of which he had received from Gen. BURNSIDE himself, for transmission in season for Thursday afternoon's papers. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 23.  Arrangements are being made for the speedy emission of the one hundred million new Treasury Notes authorized by the late joint resolution of Congress. The agents of the Companies now engaged in printing green backs for the Government are here, as are also the representatives of two other Companies, each desirous of securing a share of the new work. It is believed that Secretary CHASE, profiting by experience, and in order to provide against damaging delays, will so divide up the printing of these new notes as to guarantee the payment of the army in the very shortest possible time that the resources of American art can compass.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 22.  The House Committee on Military Affairs, at their meeting to-day, authorized their Chairman, Mr. OLIN, to report a bill in accordance with the proposition of CYRUS W. FIELD, for laying a telegraph line from Washington to New-Orleans, coastwise, touching at such points as the Government might designate. Mr. MCPHERSON was also authorized to report a bill, in accordance with the recommendation of the Secretary of War, to give authority to select a Paymaster-General, with the rank and pay of a Brigadier-General, from the regular or volunteer service. and also to report upon the bill before them to increase the pay of Paymasters' Clerks.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 21.  The expedition under Gen. Grant, from Napoleon, arrived at Young's Point, nine miles from Vicksburgh.  An engagement has occurred near Sabine Pass, Texas.  The gunboat Morning Light and the bark Velocity were captured by rebels off Sabine Pass, Texas.  HELENA, Ark., STEAMER BRAZIL, Friday, Jan. 9, 1863.  QN Going down the river QN  is not a very pleasant thing these warlike days, and nothing but the thought of our brave soldiers, wounded and dying, before the entrenchments at Vicksburgh, would have called out the little party who steamed down the river on Monday last, and are now lying off the levee at this dreary little town.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 20.  Gen. Burnside announced to the Army of the Potomac that it is about to meet the enemy again.  Gen. Hunter assumed command of the Department of the South.  The rebel privateer Alabama has arrived at Jamaica.  WASHINGTON, D.C., Saturday, Jan. 17, 1863. After the reading of the journal of the previous day, Gen. McDowell stated that he himself had procured from the War Department the minutes of the Council of Corps Commanders held in this City last Spring, referred to by him in the proceedings of yesterday, which minutes he produced to the Court. By request of Gen. McDowell, Gen. Heintzelman was sent for to verify these.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 19.  A large fleet has reportedly sailed from Napoleon and Memphis for Young's Point and Milliken's Bend, near Vicksburgh.  NEW-YORK, Monday, Jan. 19, 1863 -- 6 P.M. The receipts of the principal kinds of Produce, since our last, have been: 49 bbls. Ashes. 10, 438 bbls. Flour, 150 bbls, and 325 bags Corn Meal, 1,061 bushels Wheat, 2,495 bushels Barley, 15,562 bushels Oats, 2,313 bushels Malt, 8,152 pkgs. Provisions, and 452 bbls. Whisky. ASHES -- Sales 30 bbls., at  SX 8 37 1E2 TO  SX 8 50 for Pots, and  SX 7 87 1E2 TO  SX 8 for Pearls, 100 lbs. COTTON -- Continues in good demand at buoyant prices. sales 1,300 bales.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 18.  Gen. Hunter arrived at Hilton Head to take command of the Department of the South.   WASHINGTON, Friday, Jan. 16. In the McDowell Court of Inquiry to-day, Gen. RICKETTS was examined, testifying that the road by which he was ordered to march by Gen. McDOWELL on the morning of the 28th of August, was so obstructed by wagons in his front as greatly to impede the progress of his command.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 17.  The steamer Vanderbilt arrived at Fortress Monroe after an unsuccessful cruise after the Alabama.  The rebel privateer Oreto destroyed the brig Estelle.  WASHINGTON, Thursday, Jan. 15. GENERAL ORDERS No. 5. -- By direction of the President, the troops in the Department of the Gulf will constitute the Nineteenth Army Corps, to date from Dec. 14, 1862, and Maj.-Gen. N. P. BANKS is assigned to the command. By order of the Secretary of War, E.D. TOWNSEND, Assistant Adjutant-General. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 16.  The rebel privateer Oreto ran the blockade out of Mobile, Alabama.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 14. The Judiciary Committee of the Senate have reported back the Missouri Emancipation Aid bill, recommending amendments to make the remuneration twenty instead of ten millions, the bonds to bear but five per cent. interest. the maximum allowance, for each slave,  SX 300, and the limit for the entire extinction of Slavery, July 4, 1876, with a proviso that the act of emancipation shall be passed by the Legislature, and the exclusion of Slavery forever thereafter from said State. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 15.  The Union gunboat Columbia has been destroyed by rebels near Wilmington, North Carolina.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 14. Mr. STEVENS, of Pennsylvania, (Rep.,) reported a point resolution to provide for the immediate payment of the army and navy. The joint resolution authorities the Secretary of the Treasury, if required by the exigencies of the public service, to issue, on the credit of the United States, fifty millions of United States notes, in such form as he may deem expedient, not bearing interest, payable on demand, in denominations of not less than one dollar, which notes shall be a lawful and legal tender.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 14.  Col. James W. Wall has been elected United States Senator from New-Jersey.  An engagement occurred at Bayou Teche, Louisiana.  Union Lieutenant Commander Thomas McKeon was killed.  ST. LOUIS, Monday, Jan. 12. Last night Gen. CURTIS received dispatches from Col. CRABB, commanding at Springfield, Mo., that the rebels were repulsed at every advance on that place, and that our forces held the town. Our loss is seventeen killed. The number of wounded is not yet known. We buried thirty-five rebels, and many more were taken off the field. They left a large number of wounded in our hands. Little of the town was destroyed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 13.  Peace resolutions were introduced to-day in the New Jersey Legislature.  MURFRESSBORO, Saturday, Jan. 9. From official returns it has been ascertained that the total loss in Gen. NEGLEY's Division, comprising killed, wounded, and missing, is one thousand three hundred and fifty-six (1,356.) The total loss in Col. HAMBRIGHT's Seventy-seventh Regiment of Pennsylvania Volunteers is three hundred killed, wounded, and missing. over half of the regiment are lost. Gen. ROSECRANS has taken occasion to compliment the Colonel and his men personally for their conspicuous and unflagging courage under fire.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 12.  Gen. John E. Wool has assumed command of the Department of the East. ST. LOUIS, Friday, Jan. 9. Telegraphic communication with Springfield ceased at 3 o'clock this morning. The enemy entered our stockade yesterday afternoon. Our force was reported to be 2,000 strong, with two pieces of artillery. Springfield contains a very large amount of army stores, arms and ammunition. Fifteen four-horse teams, and thirty men belonging to the Telegraphic Corps, were supposed to be captured a few miles south of Springfield. Gen. BROWN's left shoulder is badly shattered. He would have to submit to amputation to save his life. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 11.  Forts Hindman and Arkansas, both on the Arkansas River, have been surrendered by the rebels.  A fight occurred to-day at Huntsville, Missouri.  The Union gunboat Hatteras has been sunk by the Alabama on the coast of Texas.  Gen. Weitzel crossed Berwick Bay and attacked the rebel gunboat Cotton in the Bayou Teche.  ST. LOUIS, MO., Thursday, Jan. 8. Gen. CURTIS has received the following dispatch from Gen. BROWN: SPRINGFIELD, MO., Jan. 8 -- 3 P.M. The enemy are crowding the fighting, but my men are behaving well. I am holding all the strong positions. The enemy must fight as I want him to, whether he likes it or not.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 10.  A cavalry skirmish has occurred at Catlett's Station, Virginia.  A battle at Arkansas Post has commenced.  The English steamer Rising Dawn has been captured.  American brigantine J. P. Ellicott has been captured by the privateer Retribution.  LONDON, Saturday, Jan. 3. The markets continue very quiet during the holidays, and there is no feature worthy of notice. Fair business in good blackest leaf Congou TEA. TALLOW market steady at 44s. 6d.. January to March, 45s.. March, 45s.. sellers, April, June, 40s. 2d. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 9.  An order has been issued by Gen. Halleck, thanking Gen. Rosecrans and his army for the victory of Murfreesboro.  A reconnoitering expedition has returned from West Point, Virginia, to Fort Monroe.  The rebels have been repulsed at Providence Church, on the Blackwater, Virginia.  LITTLETON, N.H., Thursday, Jan. 8. The Boston and White Mountain section of the American Telegraph Company is completed to this town, and the office here is opened for public business. Offices will soon be opened in nearly all the villages on the line of the railroad, between Littleton and Plymouth, on the new portion of the telegraph. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 8.  Springfield, Missouri, has been attacked by rebels.  Capt. Moore, with about 100 men, attacked a camp of 300 rebels at Huntoon's Mills, 35 miles east of Fort Pillow, Tennessee, on the morning of the 8th. The rebels were completely surprised. Sixteen rebels were killed, and forty-six taken prisoners. Fifty horses and a lot of small arms were captured. Two Nationals were wounded. The expedition was absent from Fort Ely about twenty-seven hours.  The steamer Mussulman was burned by guerrillas near Memphis, Tennessee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>HEADQUARTERS, ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, Sunday, Jan. 4. Everything is quiet and unchanged. Richmond papers of the 3d inst., contain dispatches from Murfreesboro of the 1st. BRAGG says the expedition under Gen. FORREST fully accomplished its object. The railroads are broken in several places. A large amount of stores have been destroyed, many arms captured and 1,200 prisoners paroled. Gen. MORGAN has done his work, but the full effect is not known. The enemy in Tennessee and Mississippi are without railroad or telegraph communication with the rear. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 6.  Gen. Carter's Union force has reached Manchester, Kentucky, on its return from a raid into East Tennessee, where they destroyed bridges and took a number of prisoners.  LOUISVILLE, Ky., Saturday, Jan. 3. Telegraphic communication is restored between here and Nashville. It is reported that Gen. BRAGG was killed to-day. There has been fighting all day, but no particulars are given. Our forces are advancing, and the rebels are falling back across Stone's River. The following officers are wounded slightly: Col. MILLER. Col. BLACK, of the Fortieth Indiana. Lieut.-Col. NEFF. Col. HILL. Capt. PATE. It has been raining heavily all day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 5.  Murfreesboro, Tennessee, is occupied by a National force.  J. P. Usher, of Indiana, has been nominated as Secretary of the Interior.  Gen. Milroy, in Western Virginia, issued a proclamation notifying the people of Winchester and neighborhood of the provisions of the President's Emancipation Proclamation.  BUFFALO, Sunday Evening. The telegraph lines West are all down, hut it is expected they will be repaired by to-morrow morning. PHILADELPHIA, Sunday Evening. The wires of the telegraph lines to the West are disarranged, probably by storm, consequently we have nothing further from Murfreesboro.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 4.  The Department of the East, including the New-England states and the State of New-York, has been created and Gen. John E. Wool is assigned to its command.  BALTIMORE, Friday, Jan. 2. This route will be opened for through travel and freight by Tuesday next, the 6th inst. Gens. SCHENCK and KELLY are confident that their forces will be able, without difficulty, to protect the road permanently. The telegraph line is already reestablished its entire length from Baltimore to Wheeling and Parkersburgh, and the maintaining of this great thoroughfare undisturbed will be of incalculable advantage to Government and commercial interests.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 3.  The rebels have retreated from the battle-field at Murfreesboro. Army paymaster Isaac N. Cook has been arrested in Cincinnati for default. Union forces at Moorefield, West Virginia, have been attacked.  The boat containing a missing portion of the Monitor's crew has been picked up on Hatteras Shoals.  ST. LOUIS, Saturday, Jan. 3. Gen. BLUNT telegraphs from Van Buren, Ark., on the 30th ult., that the rebels retreated during the night towards Arkadelphia, abandoning about sixty wounded rebels at Fort Smith, whom they left with Instructions to take care of themselves. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 2.  Galveston, Texas, has been recaptured by the rebels who also took the steamer Harriett Lane.  The steamer Westfield was blown up by its commander to prevent it from falling into the hands of the rebels.  Charges have been made against the New-York Police Commissioners for illegal action in making arrests for treason etc.  The Battle of Murfreesboro is continuing.  The rebels have been repulsed in an attack on our left wing.  Gen. Sherman's force, operating against Vicksburgh, was withdrawn from the Yazoo River.  Dumfries, Virginia, has been entered by rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry who captured some public stores etc.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 1, 1863.  The President has issued his Emancipation Proclamation in which it is declared that slaves in the insurrection states and districts are forever and henceforward free.  An Emancipation Jubilee of the negroes occurred at Hilton Head, South Carolina.  The battle at Murfreesboro is continuing.  The engagement opened at dawn by Gen. Rosecrans.  The battle was hotly contested and the losses great on both sides.  The rebel Gen. Morgan has been defeated in Kentucky.  The rebel Gen. Forrest has been defeated at Hunt's Cross Roads, Tennessee, by Gen. Sullivan.  Gen. Butler and his staff arrived in New-York City from New-Orleans.  </description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
