<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 30.  York, Pennsylvania, was evacuated overnight by the rebels.  Martial law was proclaimed to-day in Baltimore.  A skirmish has occurred at Sporting Hill, Pennsylvania, near Oyster Point.  A cavalry battle occurred to-day at Hanover Junction, Pennsylvania.  A skirmish has occurred at Mechanicsburgh, Pennsylvania.  Gen. Buford has reportedly passed through Gettysburgh on a reconnaissance in force.  HARRISBURGH, Penn., Thursday, June 25, 1863. At no period during the present invasion of that of last year has there been so much excitement in Harrisburgh as now.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 29.  Wrightsville, Pennsylvania, has been evacuated by the rebels.  To-day there was a fight at McConnelsburgh, Pennsylvania.  Gen. Meade's army is moving in the vicinity of Emmettsburgh and New-Windsor.  HARRISBURGH, Penn., Saturday, June 27, 1863. The rebels are slowly advancing toward this place, having entered Carlisle at 1 P.M. Telegraphic communication with Carlisle was suspended at about 12 M. Our forces have retired to Mechanicsburgh, which is nine miles from Harrisburgh. All the ammunition, knapsacks and surplus clothing of the advance force have been sent here by rail.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 28.   Gen. Hooker has been relieved of the command of the Army of the Potomac and Gen. Meade has been appointed in his place.  The rebels are now within four miles of Harrisburgh, Pennsylvania.  The bridge over the Susquehanna at Columbia, Pennsylvania, has been burned.  Mechanicsburgh, Pennsylvania, has surrendered to the rebels.  Brookville, Maryland, is now occupied by the rebels.  At Donaldsonville, Louisiana, the rebels attempted to take the Federal fort to-day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 27.  The advance of Gen. Rosecrans' army has arrived at Manchester, Tennessee.  Kingston, Pennsylvania, is now occupied by the rebels.  York, Pennsylvania, is also occupied.  Chambersburgh, Pennsylvania, is occupied by the divisions of the rebel army under Gens. Longstreet and Hill.  PITTSBURGH, June 25. Last night, about 10 o'clock, a message was received in the telegraph office here from McConnellsburgh, which left no doubt that the line at that point was in possession of the rebels. The rebel operator does not appear to have been gifted with any great degree of sharpness, as he made himself known the moment he attached his instrument.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 26.  Gettysburg, Pennsylvania, is now occupied by the rebels.  Gov. Curtin issued another proclamation to the people of Pennsylvania.  The rebel privateer Archer, with the crew of the Tacony has reportedly entered Portland Harbor and captured the revenue cutter Caleb Cushing.  This enterprise has resulted in the capture of the Archer by the Union navy.  White House, Virginia, is now occupied by our troops.  BALTIMORE, Monday, June 22. A body of cavalry belonging to Gen. COUCH'S command entered Frederick yesterday afternoon, and drove the rebels out of the place. It is now believed there are no rebels in Frederick County.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 25.  Fairfax Court-House, Virginia, is now occupied by the rebels.  A skirmish occurred to-day at Marysville, Pennsylvania, near Harrisburgh.  Another engagement has occurred at Liberty Gap, Tennessee.  An expedition reportedly left West Point, Virginia, for the interior.  One rebel fort at Vicksburg was destroyed to-day by the explosion of one of our mines.  The cargo ship Constitution has been captured by the privateer Georgia.  The Union army has crossed the Potomac at Edwards' Ferry.  Gen. Rosecrans has reportedly resumed his march.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 24.  Shippensburg, Pennsylvania, has been reached by a portion of the rebel army.  Sever skirmish of Gen. Rosecrans' army has occurred at Hoover's Gap, Tennessee, and has been successful to our arms as a result.  The rebels have been driven from Liberty Gap, near Murfreesboro.  Heavy skirmishing has commenced near Murfreesboro.  The main body of Lee's army has reportedly entered Maryland, crossing the Potomac at Shepperdstown and Williamsport.  HARRISBURGH, Penn., Tuesday, June 23, 1863. At 11 O'clock last night dispatches were received by Gen. COUCH, informing him that rebel scouts had reentered Greencastle.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 23.  Chambersburgh, Pennsylvania, is now reoccupied by the rebels.  ALBANY, Tuesday, June 16. The Governor is receiving urgent messages from the authorities of Pennsylvania asking for troops, and is doing everything possible to hurry them forward. Gov. CURTIN advises that they be shipped via Easton. Secretary STANTON telegraphs that the men will not be needed for more than 30 days, and probably not for that period. that arms will be supplied to them at Harrisburgh, and that they report to Gen. COUGH.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 22.  Rebels now occupy Millerstown, Pennsylvania. The portion of rebel Gen. Ewell's corps which had not yet arrived in Pennsylvania has now crossed the Potomac and moved up the valley.  Rebels are driven from Cumberland, Maryland.  HARRISBURGH, Saturday, June 20. A heavy force of rebels continue to linger in the vicinity of Hagerstown and Williamsport. Scouts sent out from Chambersburgh, report that their movements this morning indicate a retreat to the other side of the Potomac, but this afternoon they moved up in the direction of McConnellsville and Bedford. Gen. MILROY is on the alert for them. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 21.  A great cavalry engagement is underway near Middleburgh and Upperville, Virginia.  The rebels are driven from Frederick, Maryland.  HARRISBURGH, Sunday, June 14. Dispatches received from the operators at Chambersburgh and Hagerstown give the information of negroes who have arrived there, to the effect that the rebel cavalry arrived at Perrysville and Martinsburgh about noon, and at the latter place there had been considerable hard fighting. Gen. MILROY was contesting the advance of the rebels. Telegraph communication is destroyed between Winchester and Martinsburgh, the lines having been broken by the rebels about 11 A.M.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 20.  The ship Isaac Webb has been captured and bonded by the Tacony.  Rebels have been driven out of Frederick, Maryland.  PHILADELPHIA, Monday, June 15. The movements of the rebels on the borders of the State caused much excitement at the Corn Exchange this morning, and trade was partially suspended. PHILADELPHIA, Monday, June 15. The principal citizens of this city have telegraphed to Gen. GEORGE CADWALLADER, now at Washington, asking him to obtain authority to repair immediately to Philadelphia, and organize the troops, his petitioners regarding him as a man fit for the crisis. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>SHIPPENSBURGH, PENN. Friday, June 19, 9 A.M.  Last night considerable excitement was created in this place by the arrival of farmers from the neighborhood of Chambersburgh, who brought with them all their stock or horses, in anticipation of the advance of the rebels. The town is one vast stable. The rebels hold Greencastle with a force of two hundred men. They are scouting the country in all directions in search of horses. Last night a traitor led the rebels to a gap in the mountain near Greencastle, where they took sixty horses which had been secreted by citizens. The apparent object of the rebels is to obtain horses and run off negroes.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 18.  From MEMPHIS, Friday, June 12. The steamer Fort Wayne, from Young's Point, arrived here to-day. She brings no later dates from Vicksburgh than the 8th inst. No guerrillas were seen on the way up. The fight at Milliken's Bend on, Sunday last, was much larger than at first reported. The rebels under MCCULLOUGH, 2,500 strong, advanced upon the Federal forces, composed of three negro regiments and the Twenty-third Iowa Volunteers. The rebels made a desperate charge at daylight. The negroes broke in confusion, but finding that their captured companions were being slaughtered by the rebels. rallied with great desperation.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>HARRISBURGH, Wednesday, June 17. No doubt whatever exists as to the presence of the enemy at Chambersburgh up to about 3 o'clock this afternoon, when they retreated, it is supposed, toward Hagerstown. The operator is at Chambersburgh, and telegraphic communication has been reestablished. BALTIMORE, Wednesday, June 17. Hagerstown dispatches are very unreliable. Trains arrived this evening from Westminster, bringing also passengers from Emmittsburgh, who report no rebels in that section of the country. The excitement along the line toward Harrisburgh was abating.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 16.  Harper's Ferry has been reached by Gen. Milroy's army.  Gov. Parker of New Jersey has to-day called for volunteers to repel the invasion of Philadelphia.  Harper's Ferry has been invested and attacked.  Our forces have retired to Maryland Heights and have shelled the rebels out.   HARRISBURGH, Tuesday, June 16, 1863. The telegraph offices at Carsisle and Shippensburgh are still open, and business is transacted with them as usual. As Shippensburgh is twenty miles beyond Carlisle, it is evident that the rebels are not advancing with much rapidity, and there is to-night a fair prospect of securing the Capital against attack, if the rebels advance.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>HARRISBURGH, June 15. The telegraph operator left Chambersburgh at 9 o'clock to-night, some time after the rebels had entered the town. His instrument is now in operation five miles east of Chambersburgh, at Scotland Bridge. A.G. CURTIN.  The operator from Chambersburgh says that a great fire is now raging at Greencastle. The column that entered Greencastle consisted of 5,000 cavalry, supported by infantry and artillery. The fire at Greencastle is believed to indicate a determination on the part of the rebels to burn, plunder and destroy our cities.  Gov. CURTIN and Gen. COUCH are working night and day.  The bells are rung and people are assembling en masse.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 14.  A skirmish occurred to-day at State Creek, Kentucky.  Berryville and Martinsburgh have been occupied by the rebels.  The Army of the Potomac has reportedly left Falmouth for Pennsylvania in pursuit of Gen. Lee's forces.  Port Hudson has been assaulted.  Our forces were repulsed with heavy losses.  HEADQUARTERS, NINETEENTH ARMY CORPS. IN THE FIELD NEAR PORT HUDSON, June 1, 1863. No person, military officer or other, will take from any plantation worked by the U.S. Quartermaster's Department, any article of property whatever, or in any way interfere with the working of the same.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 13.  The town of Eunice, near Vicksburgh, has been destroyed by our gunboats.  Winchester, Virginia, has been attacked and its armament and part of its garrison has been captured.  MURFREESBORO, Tennessee, Tuesday, June 9. Col. LAWRENCE WILLIAMS ORTON, formerly LAWRENCE WILLIAMS, of the Second United States cavalry, one time on Gen. SCOTT'S Staff, and late Gen. BEAGG'S Chief of Artillery, and Lieut. DUNLAP, of the rebel army, were arrested and hung as spies last night, at Franklin.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 12.  Governor Curtin of Pennsylvania has issued a proclamation calling for volunteers to repel the anticipated invasion of that State by rebels.  Gen. Couch assumed command of the Department of the Susquehanna.  President Lincoln has reportedly addressed a letter to Erastus Corning and others, in relation to the arrest of Vallandigham etc.  Gen. Hunter has left the Department of the South.  Gen. Q. A. Gillmore has assumed command.  A brisk engagement between Union batteries on Folly Island and rebel batteries on Morris Island has occurred in Charleston Harbor. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 11.  C. L. Vallandigham was nominated for Governor of Ohio to-day.  Darien, Georgia, has reportedly been destroyed by our forces.  The Herald has been destroyed by Union gunboats in Charleston Harbor.  The steamer Calypso has been captured.  Gen. Halleck has directed the garrisons at Martinsburgh and Winchester, Virginia, to retire to Harper's Ferry.  Tribune, Tennessee, has been attacked by rebels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 10.  The draft in Indiana has been resisted.  An engagement occurred to-day near Monticello, Kentucky.  Lake Providence was attacked by rebels and successfully defended by negro troops.  The Havelock sunk off Charleston bar.  CINCINNATI, Monday, June 8. Two thousand rebel prisoners left Indianapolis on Saturday for Fort Delaware. One hundred and sixty-five officers of PEMBERTON's were sent to Johnston's Island. CINCINNATI, Monday, June 8. Maj.-Gen. AMBROSE E. BURNSIDE returned to this city on Saturday, the 6th inst. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 9.  a severe cavalry engagement at brandy Station or Beverly's Ford, Virginia, occurred to-day on the Rappahannock.  Rebels have been driven from Monticello, Kentucky.  The Departments of Monongahela and Susquehanna were created to-day.  Gen. Rosecrans executed two spies to-day.  HEADQUARTERS ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, Saturday, June 6, 1863. The boldest reconnaissance of the war was begun yesterday afternoon by a portion of this army. For the third time in six months, the Rappahannock has been successfully crossed by our brave men, with slight loss.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, June 8.   The telegraph has not taken the trouble either to contradict or confirm the story it brought us, a few days since, that the rebels had captured a regiment of negro soldiers at Helena, Arkansas, and had hung every man of them, with all their white officers. We should think that when it was thought worth while to startle the whole country with a rumor of this kind, it would also be considered worth while to contradict it when it was proven to be false. The absurd stories which are often telegraphed to the Press may, perhaps, not be thought worthy of contradiction, but the fact is they deceive many people, and leave many others in doubt.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 7.  The Battle of Milliken's Bend has concluded to-day.  THE VICKSBURGH WOUNDED. Assistant Surgeon-Gen. WOOD telegraphs to the Department here that the wounded from Vicksburgh are being removed as rapidly as possible to hospitals at Memphis and elsewhere. Large quantities of ice and other comforts have been forwarded from St. Louis for the use of the wounded.  The Medical Department is now prepared to furnish, free of charge, artificial arms to such soldiers as have lost their natural ones in battle.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 6.  The bark Whistling Wind was destroyed by a privateer to-day.  Rebels have attacked Milliken's Bend and Young's Point, near Vicksburgh, but were repulsed.  Shawneetown, Kansas, has reportedly been destroyed by guerrillas.  WASHINGTON, Thursday, June 4. A party of contrabands direct from Culpepper, who arrived at Union Mills yesterday, report that a few days since three rebel brigades of infantry arrived at Culpepper from the Rappahannock, and the soldiers said they were going to Richmond. The bridge over the Rapidan has been rebuilt, so that trains pass over the road from Culpepper to Richmond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 5.  From MURFREESBORO, Tennessee, Wednesday, June 3. Scouts who have thoroughly scoured the country on our left and in our rear, report having neither seen nor heard of any rebels. A gentleman who is known here, and whose statements are regarded as reliable, has just reached our lines from Tullahoma. This gentleman says there are not more than two regiments at that place, and that the enemy have thrown all their forces forward to Shelbyville Beech Grove and other points on our immediate front.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 4.  Our forces at Franklin, Tennessee, have been attacked.  Gen. Burnside has revoked his order suppressing the New-York World and Chicago Times, by order of the President.  An expedition has departed King William County, Virginia, from Yorktown, with good results.  To-day there was a brisk fight at Sataria, on the Yazoo River.   NEW YORK, June 4.  The total subscriptions in America to the Atlantic Telegraph stock to date are  PX 66.615. Every person in the United States, and the British North American Provinces owning any of the stock of the Atlantic Telegraph Company has shown his confidence in the enterprise by subscribing for new stock. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 3.  To-day there is a great peace meeting in New York.  Gen. Lee has reportedly broken up camp at Fredericksburgh, Virginia.  CHICAGO, Tuesday, June 2. The proprietors of the Times were notified to-night by Capt. PUTNAM, commanding Camp Douglas, that if they attempted to issue their paper for to-morrow morning, he would, in accordance with a telegraphic order from Gen. AMMEN, take military possession of the office. Judge DRUMMOND, of the United States Court, was Immediately applied to for a writ enjoining Capt. PUTNAM from any interference whatever with the Times office. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 2.  Gen. Burnside has suppressed the circulation of the New-York World and Chicago Times in his department.   CINCINNATI Saturday, May 30. There are no later advices from Murfreesboro. It is believed that the Army of the Cumberland is in motion. Gen. BURNSIDE will soon take the field. Gen. HARTSUFF has issued Order No. 1, assuming command of the troops in Kentucky, except the Ninth army corps and Gen. CARTER's division, with headquarters at Lexington. Brig.-Gen. BAYLE has charge of the railroad and depot guards throughout the State.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 1.  To-day there was a meeting of Vallandigham sympathizers at Philadelphia.  James Island has been evacuated by the Union troops.  Col. Grierson's men, in their famous raid through Louisiana, had a very clever way of cutting the telegraph wires so as to avoid discovery. Instead of cutting the wires and letting the ends hang loosely, they tied up the ends with strips of leather, so that it could not be easily seen and yet the connection was severed. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 31 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 31.  Skirmishing reportedly occurred to-day near Monticello, Kentucky.  The schooner Echo has been captured.  The Commissioner of Internal Revenue has just made the following highly important decision, covering the whole ground of the income tax: The income tax must be assessed and paid in the district in which the assessed person resides. The place where a person votes, or is entitled to vote, is deemed his residence. When not a voter, the place where the tax on personal property is paid is held to be the place of residence.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 30 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 30.  An attack on a train of cars near Catlett's Station, Virginia, by Moseby's rebel cavlry occurred to-day.  Moseby's force has been defeated near Greenwich, Virginia.  A train of cars was destroyed near Kettle Run, Virginia.  CINCINNATI, Friday, May 29. It is reported that Gen. BRAGG telegraphed to JEFF. DAVIS as to what he should do with Mr. VALLANDIGHAM. JEFF. DAVIS replied, if Mr. VALLANDIGHAM would take the oath of allegiance to the Southern Confederacy, to receive him, and if not to send him back. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 29 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 29.  A skirmish occurred to-day at Thoroughfare Gap, Virginia.  Gen. Kilpartirck left Yorktown on a raid up the Peninsula with good success so far.  PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, May 27. MARION DAY, for many years an operator of the American Telegraph Company, died this morning, after a severe and painful illness.  MOBILE, Monday, May 25. A special dispatch to the Evening News, dated Jackson, May 24, (Sunday,) says firing was heard till 9 o'clock this morning. No report of artillery has been heard since that hour. This morning the Twentieth Mississippi regiment (mounted) dashed into Raymond, capturing 400 prisoners.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 28 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 28.  An attack on Port Hudson is continuing to-day.  Our forces have been repulsed. From a special reporter in Jackson Mississippi, May 17.  The Catholic church of this place was destroyed, and the Mississippian Office gutted, the presses broken, and the type thrown into the street. The furniture in the Capitol was badly abused, and the Governor's mansion demolished. Ladies were robbed of jewelry and money. All the stores were sacked, and their contents destroyed, iron safes broken open. The railroad was badly torn up for several miles, and the telegraph wires torn down. About three hundred negroes from Hinds County joined the Yankees.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 27 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 27.  Kearney medals were presented to-day to the Third Army Corps.  Rebels have been defeated at Florence, Alabama.  An attack on Port Hudson has commenced.  The Union gunboat Cincinnati was sunk by rebel batteries at Vicksburgh.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, May 26. Arrangements are nearly finished to make a draft as soon as the enrollment under the Conscription law has been completed.  An order from the War Department furnishes the long-promised rules and regulations for negro enlistments.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 26 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 26.  Messrs. GLASS, ELLIOT  ES  CO., of London, the large and wealthy manufacturers of submarine telegraph cables, offer to manufacture and lay down a good and durable sub-marine cable between Ireland and Newfoundland, on condition that they are paid each week their actual disbursements for labor and materials, and that when the cable is laid and in good working order, they shall receive interest on capital and profit, twenty per cent,  provided the cable at the end of each successive month shall be found in perfect working order. This great international work will now be pushed forward without delay, and completed during the summer of 1864.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 25 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 25.  Gen. GRANT'S army is in Vicksburgh, and that his victory is complete. We had previously learned that the outer works had been taken -- that Haines' Bluff batteries, immediately on the north, the Warrenton batteries immediately on the south, and the line of the Big Black River, including the great railroad bridge, in the rear, were all in our hands.  Gen. GRANT fought five pitched battles with the rebels, in all of which he had been successful. We had seen how skillfully he divided their forces.  We knew that he had committed terrible havoc in the enemy's ranks, had captured in the vicinity of 10,000 prisoners and an immense quantity of artillery.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 24 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 24.  An official dispatch from Memphis, which the President has furnished to the Press, announcing a great battle in the vicinity of Vicksburgh, and the capture by Gen. GRANT of the outer works of the place, with a large number of prisoners and fifty-seven pieces of artillery. The battle, it is said, was still raging on Wednesday. We are not told when it opened, nor its precise locality. but if we really hold the points mentioned in the dispatch, it must have been close in the rear of the great stronghold. Haines' Bluff, as our readers know, is directly north of Vicksburgh, and has always been considered the key of the position.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 23 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 23.  The battle at Gum Swamp, North Carolina, is continuing to-day.  Gen. Bank's forces met in junction with Gen. Augur's forces at Bayou Sara, Louisiana, to-day.  A DISPATCH FROM GEN. JOE JOHNSTON. CAMP BETWEEN LIVINGSTON AND BROWNSVILLE, Miss., May 18, 1863. To Gen. S. Cooper: Lieut.-Gen. PEMBERTON was attacked by the enemy on the morning of the 16th inst., near Edwards' depot, and after nine hours' fighting was compelled to fall back behind the Big Black. J.D. JOHNSTON, General Com'd'g.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 22 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 22.  The sentence for Vallandigham has been changed to banishment.  The blockade runner Eagle has been captured.  An assault on rebel works at Vicksburgh, Mississippi, is in progress.  Yesterday, our forces were repulsed with severe losses.  A battle began to-day at Gum Swamp, North Carolina.  There has been an engagement at Port Hudson Plains.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 21 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 21.    There is no later news from Gen. GRANT this morning. This need cause no apprehension. he had notified the War Department that a cessation of intelligence from him for a short period, might be expected. A report was current in Cincinnati yesterday -- how it reached there is not explained -- that Gen. GRANT, after destroying the State House and rebel stores in Jackson, evacuated the place. This is quite likely to have been the case, if the report of the evacuation of Vicksburgh, and the movement of the rebels to the northward is true. The Government, our Washington correspondent says, expects to hear from Gen. GRANT to-day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 20 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 20.  U.S. gunboat Isaac Smith, earlier captured by rebels and renamed steamer Stono, has been destroyed off Charleston, South Carolina.  The bark Goodspeed has been destroyed by the Tacony.  Vicksburg is being invested by Gen. Grant's forces.   NEW YORK, May 20.  CYRUS W. FIELD, Esq., has placed specimens of every kind of submarine cable now in use in the world on exhibition at the Merchants' Exchange Reading Room, Nos. 50 and 52 Pine-street. They embrace all the English, European and American cables, and are indeed a curiosity well worthy the inspection of the public, who are invited to view them. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 19 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 19.  Gen. Meagher took leave of his troops to-day.  Richmond, Missouri, was sacked by guerrillas.  Vicksburgh's fortifications have been assaulted.  The blockade runner steamer Union has been captured.  CINCINNATI, Tuesday, May 19. The defeat of the rebels at Raymond, Miss., is said to have been very disastrous to them. We are yet without particulars. Gen. GRANT took Jackson on the 14th inst., and burned the State Capitol. Heavy reinforcements were hurrying forward to the rebels, and stopping twelve miles east of Jackson. A great battle is imminent. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 18 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 18.  A meeting to express sympathy with Vallandigham was held to-day in New York.  Vallandigham has been sentenced to confinement in Fort Warren.  A Union victory has occurred on the Black River, Mississippi.  Admiral Porter has captured Haines' Bluff, near Vicksburgh.  The schooner Isabel has been destroyed, and the schooner Ripple has been captured, both off Mobile Bay.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 17 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 17.  The steamer Cuba has been pursued and destroyed and the schooner Hunter has been captured.  A battle occurred to-day at Big Black River Bridge, Mississippi.  From the Richmond Inquirer, May 13. HOW JACKSON WAS WOUNDED, HIS SUFFERINGS AND DEATH.  Gen. JACKSON, having gone some distance in front of the line of skirmishers on Saturday evening, was returning about 8 o'clock, attended by his Staff and part of his couriers. The cavalcade was in the darkness of the night mistaken for a body of the enemy's cavalry, and fired upon by a regiment of his own corps. He was struck by three balls and bled to death.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 16 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 16.  The cavalry captured by the rebels at Charlestown, Maryland, have been freed by Union forces.  Rebels under Gen. Pemberton have been defeated at Edward's Station, Mississippi.  A great battle occurred to-day at Baker's Creek, near Vicksburgh, and is now being called the Battle of Champion's Hill.   There was an engagement at Berry's Ferry, Virginia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 15 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 15.  A company of U.S. cavalry has been captured at Charlestown, Maryland.  Rebel stores were destroyed at York River, Virginia.  A fight occurred to-day at Carrsville, Virginia.  The evacuation of Jackson, Mississippi, by Union troops has commenced.  The British brigantine Cornet has been captured.  The ship Byzantium was burned by the Tacony.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 14 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 14.  Jackson, Mississippi, has fallen to Gen. Grant.  The resignation of Gen. Thos. F. Meagher was accepted to-day by the President.  Clinton, Mississippi, is now occupied by Union troops.  Senators WADE and CHANDLER, after a lengthy interview to-day with the President and Secretary of War, left, this evening, in a special boat for the army. The President, to-night, received from the headquarters of the army of the Potomac an original letter of JEFFERSON DAVIS, addressed to one of his Colonels, in which he speaks despondingly of affairs in the Southwest and on the Rappahannock. The letter was found in a rebel camp.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 13 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 13.  Rebel forces have been defeated at Mississippi Spring, Mississippi.  Gen. Joe Johnston has arrived at Jackson, Mississippi.  Ar large amount of rebel property was destroyed to-day at Yazoo City.  The schooner A. J. Hodge has been captured.  The ship Crown Point has been burned by the Florida.  BOSTON, May 13. -- Arrived ship Courier, Havre. brig Nahant, Remedios. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 12 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 12.  A Union victory has occurred to-day at Raymond, Mississippi.  SAN FRANCISCO. May 11. -- Arrived steamer Orizaba, Panama: ship Panther, Lathrop, New-York. BOSTON. May 12. -- Arrived ship Hignland Chief, Newport: barks E.F. Herriman, Buenos Ayres. Smyrnite, Smyrna. brig Coquette, Cienfuegos. schr. Emma, do. At Barbados April 22, schooner Island Belle, Johnson, from Philadelphia, just arrived -- she had lost deck load, split sails, etc. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 11 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 11.  The news on Monday from the Philadelphia papers concerning the advance upon Richmond as having been sent by telegraph from Philadelphia to this City, and as having thus passed under the notice of the Government Censor. We have since learned that this was not so. It came from Philadelphia here by special messenger, and was only committed to the telegraph from this City to Boston, over the Independent line. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 10 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 10.  To-day, rebel Gen. Stonewall Jackson has reportedly died.  PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, May 9. The Bulletin, of this City, publishes the following  intelligence this evening:  QN We learn from the editors of the Philadelphia Inquirer that one of their correspondents, who has just returned from Washington, informed them that Gen. Hooker recrossed the Rappahannock in force yesterday, the men carrying eight days' rations with them. We also learn from another source, that is vouched for as reliable, that Gen. Keyes has taken Richmond, having advanced upon it by way of Yorktown. and that the Federal flag now floats over the rebel Capital.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 09 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 9.  Rebel guerrillas have attacked at Horseshoe Bend, on the Cumberland River, Tennessee.  The schooner Sea Lion has been captured off Mobile Bay.  WASHINGTON, May 8, 1863. To the Governor of Pennsylvania: The President and the General-in-Chief have just returned from the Army of the Potomac. The principal operations of Gen. HOOKER failed, but there has been no serious disaster to the organization and efficiency of the army. It is now occupying its former position on the Rappahannock, having recrossed the river without any loss in the movement. Not more than one-third of Gen. HOOKER's force was engaged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 08 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 8.  President Lincoln made a proclamation to-day in relation to the draft, defining the duties of persons of foreign birth.  Gen. T. F. Meagher resigned his commission to-day.  Gen. Banks has reached Alexandria, Louisiana, having captured on his expedition 2,000 prisoners, 20 artillery pieces, 2 transports, and a large amount of property.  FORT MONROE, Wednesday, May 6. Col. LUDLOW, Commissioner for exchange of prisioners, has just returned from City Point, and has effected the release and exchange of all United States officers held by the rebels. These officers, 250 in number, and 325 men, include Gens. STOUGHTON and WILLICH.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 07 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 7.   President Lincoln and Gen. Halleck visited the Army of the Potomac at Falmouth, Virginia, this morning.  Col Kilpatrick and a force of cavalry have arrived at Gloucester Point, Virginia.  Gen. Whipple died to-day.  The trial of C. L. Vallandigham concluded to-day.  West Point, Virginia, is now occupied by Union forces.  The bridges etc. near White House, Virginia, have been destroyed by Union forces.  Gen. Lee issued a congratulatory address to his army.  The steamer Cherokee has been captured off Charleston, South Carolina.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 06 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 6.  The trial of C. L. Vallandigham has commenced in Cincinatti.  The Army of the Potomac continues to return across the Rappahannock.  Gen. Hooker has issued an address to his army in respect to the battles at Chancellorsville.  A severe battle has occurred at Clinton, Mississippi.  The Steamer Eugenie has been captured off Mobilie Bay, by a Union gunboat.  A battle at Fourteen-Mile Creek, near Vicksburgh, has commenced. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 05 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 5.  Meadow Bridge, on the Chickahominy, has been destroyed by Col. Kilpatrick's forces.  The schooner Jupiter, a blockade runner, has been captured.  The Honorable C. L. Vallandigham has been arrested at Dayton, Ohio, for treason.  A riot broke out in an attempt to rescue him at Dayton.  The Army of the Potomac has commenced to return from Chancellorsville, across the Rappahannock.  Col. Kilpatrick has surprised some rebel cavalry at Aylett's Virginia.  The governor of Mississippi has called on the people of the state to arouse for its defence.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 04 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 4.  Grand Gulf, Mississippi, has been captured by Admiral Porter's fleet.  A battle occurred to-day at Salem Heights, near Fredericksburgh, Virginia.  Gen. Stoneman's cavalry have now reportedly reached Beaver Dam, Ashland, and Hanover Court-house, Virginia.  Newspaper correspondents have been captured when running past rebel batteries at Vicksburgh.  Col. Kilpatrick's cavalry left Louisa Court-House, Virginia.  Col. Streight's Union cavalry have been captured near Rome, Georgia.  Gen. Stoneman's cavalry are now within two miles of Richmond, Virginia.  He has reached the Chickahominy Bridge.  Hungary, Virginia, has been reached by Col. Kilpatrick. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 03 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 3.  To-day there is terrific fighting at Chancellorsville.  The Chancellor mansion has reportedly been shelled and burned by the rebels.  Gen. Berry has been killed.  Rebel Gen. Jackson has likely been mortally wounded.  Gen. Sedgwick has attacked Fredericksburg.  Mary's Hill has been stormed.  There is great panic in Richmond due to the approach of Gen. Stoneman's cavalry.  Columbia, Virginia, on the James River, has been reached by our cavalry who destroyed the canal there.  Goochland, Virginia, has been visited by our cavalry.  A fight has occurred at Suffolk, Virginia.  Fighting continues near Warrenton, Virginia. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 02 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 2.  To-day the battle at Chancellorsville is continuing.  Culpepper Court-house, Virginia, has fallen into Union hands.  Big Black River, Mississippi, has been reached by Federal forces.  Col. Grierson's cavalry force has reportedly reached Baton Rouge, Louisiana, from Tennessee.  BALTIMORE, Saturday, May 2. The crisis with the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad is past. The Confederates have all left it, moving southward, and our military forces are following and endeavoring to intercept them. The extent of the injury done to the road is now known. The line is intact, from the Monongahela River, three hundred miles distant, to Baltimore.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 01 May 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 1.  A battle has commenced at Chancellorsville, Virginia.  Thompson's Hills, Mississippi, also known as Port Gibson, is occupied by Union forces.  PORT ROYAL, Saturday, March 28. The Keokuk arrived yesterday.  Four Monitors are in North Ecisto Inlet, with three mortar schooners, distant about 16 miles by land from Charleston. The troops landed at Stono are said to have accompanied a gunboat expedition. Firing has been heard there, but there is nothing definite from that quarter. The rebel pickets are visible all along the shores at North Edisto, and at night signals by colored lights are telegraphed along the coast from thence to Charleston.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 30.  To-day is Fast Day in the United States.  Chancellorsville, Virginia, is now occupied by Gen. Hooker's army.  Rebel Gen. Longstreet's army has commenced to withdraw from the south side of the James River.  Gen. Grant's army has landed at Bruinsburg, Mississippi.  FALMOUTH, APRIL 26.  A few days ago a telegraph wire was discovered on the river bank. the finder touched it and received a slight shock. the fact was reported, and upon examination the important discovery was made that one end end of the line was within the enemy's lines, and the other in a house at Falmouth. The operator -- a rebel -- was arrested and is now in custody.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 29.  Gen. Hooker's forces to-day crossed the Rappahannock at Kelly's Ford in the advance upon Fredericksburgh.  There has been an attack on the rebel batteries at Grand Gulf, Mississippi.  Haines' Bluff near Vicksburgh has been bombarded.  Orange Springs has been reached by Gen. Stoneman's cavalry.  The ship Oneida has been destoryed by the Florida.  The bark Henrietta has also been destroyed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 28.  The U.S. sloop-of-war Preble has been destroyed by fire.  A skirmish near Kinston, North Carolina, is continuing.  Gen. Stoneman's cavalry have reportedly crossed the Rappahannock at Kelley's Ford.  ST. LOUIS, Friday, April 24. The correspondent of the Democrat, of this city, writing from Rolla, says:  QN Gen. MARMADUKE has a force of twenty thousand rebels in Southeast Missouri, and Gen. PRICE has a force of twelve thousand conscripts at Pocahontas. QN  This is, doubtless, an exaggeration.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 27.   Gen. Stoneman's cavalry expedition has reportedly left Warrenton Junction, Virginia.  WASHINGTON, April 24, 1863. One of the guards in the town of Falmouth, stationed outside a dwelling adjoining the brick church on the river bank, heard a choking like that of a telegraph instrument. He advised his superior officers, and was defected to enter the house and investigate. This was done, and on opening a door he discovcovered a party of four or five persons, one of whom was seated by a telegraph instrument, sending messages by a submarine wire across the Rappahannock. They were all arrested, and as their offense is of extraordinary atrocity.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 26.   Rebels at Cape Girardeau, Missouri, have been routed.  The schooner Clarina, a blockade runner, has been captured.  STONEMAN's STATION, Va., Saturday, April 25. Thursday morning's expedition, consisting of two regiments -- the Fourteenth Brooklyn and Nineteenth Indiana, under command of Col. MORROW, of the Twenty-fourth Michigan -- reached Port Conway, and at daylight launched several pontoons, crossed the river, and seized the town of Port Royal, which was occupied by a body of the enemy's cavalry, numbering not over two hundred. The cavalry were speedily dispersed, and twenty or more of them captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 25.   Tuscumbia, Alabama, is now reportedly occupied by our cavalry.  The ship Dictator has been destroyed by the Georgia.  MURFREESBORO, Tenn., Thursday, April 23. Refugees relieved from oppression at McMinnville, by a highly successful expedition by Gen. REYNOLDS, have arrived at Readyville. Gen. HAZEN telegraphs that they state that REYNOLDS took the town, capturing two railroad trains and a train of wagons. Among a number of prisoners taken was Mrs. JOHN MORGAN.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 24.  FORTRESS MONROE, Thursday, April 23. The flag-of-truce boat State of Maine, Capt. J. E. MULFORD, of the Third New-York regiment, has arrived from City Point. The Richmond papers of to-day contain telegraphic information from Port Hudson, confirming the loss of the steamers Queen of the West and Diana. The former got aground in Grand Lake, and was blown up by a shell from the Federal gunboat Calhoun. The Diana was burned by the rebels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 23.  A Union raid has reportedly occurred on Middleton, Tennessee.  Gen. Hunter addressed a letter to Jefferson Davis, threatening retaliation for the execution of negro soldiers and their officers.  BOSTON, April 23. -- Arr. ship Lisbon, from New-York. bark John Bunyan, from Messina. Armenia, Constantinople. brigs Sea Lark, New-Orleans. Sparkling Sea, Buenos Ayres. Jesse, Matanzas. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 22.  McMinnville, Tennessee, has been taken by our troops and the rebel stores there have been destroyed.  Tompkinsville, Kentucky, has been destroyed by our troops.  A large force with gunboats has ran past the rebel batteries at Vicksburgh.   A dispatch from Berwick Bay, dated the 15th inst., reports that there is a Federal force beyond Franklin, La., and marching on. There are no reports from Charleston later than the 17th, and they contain nothing new. Much interest is felt in Richmond in regard to matters at Suffolk. The papers admit that a battery has been captured. The tone of the editorials is desponding. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 21.  Gen. Halleck visited Suffolk, Virginia, to-day.  NEW-YORK, TUESDAY, April 21. Steamship Hammonia, Hamburg 5th inst., via Southampton 8th, with mdse, and 172 passengers to Kunhardt Co. Had moderate winds but heavy sea during the passage. 8th inst., passed steamship Teutonia, going in the River Elbe.  Gen. WRIGHT, in command at Louisville, telegraphs to Gen. BURNSIDE that the town of Celina was destroyed, together with 100,000 pounds of bacon, 10,000 bushels of wheat, 10,000 bushels of corn, 100 barrels of whisky, a quantity of flour, sugar, coffee, tea, etc., and forty boats, which had been used for transportation on the Cumberland.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 20.  A great mass meeting occurred to-day in New-York in commemoration of the grand uprising of the people in 1861.  Gen. Banks' forces now occupy Opelousas and Washington, Louisiana.  A rebel fort at Butte a la Rose, Louisiana, has been captured.  Telegraphic communication with Norfolk was cut off for a short time day before yesterday, by a rebel guerrilla, who escaped with a patrol as a prize. The roads toward Norfolk and Portsmouth are now securely guarded. It is presumed that the rebels will attempt to destroy the railway tracks at Deep Creek, but the attempt, if made, will be foiled.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 19.  A rebel battery at the West Branch, Nansemond River, near Suffolk, Virginia, has been captured.  Our forces have landed at Eastport, Virginia.  The sloop Neptune has been captured off Charleston, South Carolina.  The steamer Norseman has been destroyed off Charleston.  SUFFOLK, Va., Saturday, April 18, 1863. Rumors threatening the recapture of Suffolk and Norfolk have been more or less rife since the occupation of this place, now nearly a year ago. The inhabitants here (utterly Secesh) have repeatedly prophecied their deliverence from Yankee rule, and the annihilation of all fortifications in this vicinity.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 18.  To-day, Fayetteville, Arkansas, was attacked by the rebels but they were repulsed.  There has been fighting near Memphis, Tennessee.  The steamer St. John's has been captured off Charleston, South Carolina.  HEADQUARTERS, ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, April 14.  The corps was encamped in the vicinity of  QN Spotted Tavern, QN  3 1E2 miles west of Hartwood. The river was swollen by recent rains. the corps pushed forward to Rappahannock Station.  A brigade of cavalry was sent across by the ford -- the most serious obstacle to their passage being a telegraph wire stretched across poles under water near the opposite bank that entangled horses.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 17.  An engagement has occurred at Vermillion Bayou, Louisiana, that was successful for our troops.  Col. Grierson has embarked on a cavalry expedition from Baton Rouge, Louisiana.  Despatch from Vicksburgh this morning is highly important. On the night of Thursday, the 16th instant, five gunboats and three transports ran past the rebel batteries, carrying down a large number of Gen. GRANT'S troops, who are thus placed in a position either to cooperate with Gen. BANKS in the reduction of Port Hudson, or to attack Vicksburgh from below.  All got safely by with the exception of one transport, which caught fire opposite the batteries.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 16.  Last night, it is reported that the Federal gunboats Benton, Tuscumbia, LaFayette, Pittsburgh, Carondelet, Gen. Price and three transports ran past rebel batteries at Vicksburgh.  Acting Rear-Admiral LEE telegraphs to the Secretary, off from Newport's News, at 6 A.M., April 16, as follows: Reports from Lieut. CUSHING just received. The enemy have not crossed the river, and there is every indication that they are retreating, though they still have some artillery and sharpshooters on the Nansemond. Our boats shot down a number of their men to-day with canister. We have had three wounded, making in all five killed and eighteen wounded.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 15.  A fight occurred yesterday at Kelly's Ford, near Fredericksburgh, Virginia.  A rebel battery near Suffolk, Virginia, has been silenced.  Gen. Foster arrived at Newbern, North Carolina, from Washington, North Carolina, where his army was besieged.  New-Orleans Era, April 14. By way of Matamoras, we have received news from the City of Mexico to the 27th March, conveying intelligence of a grand battle between the French forces, advancing on Puebla, and the Mexicans, defending that place.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 14.  A fight has occurred near Suffolk, Virginia.  Aid has reached Gen. Foster at Washington, North Carolina.  The rebels have been repulsed in the Nansemond River, Virginia.  The ram Queen of the West has been recaptured from the rebels in Grand Lake, Louisiana.  Action is continuing between Gen. Banks' army and the bebels in the Teche country of Louisiana.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, April 13.  A riot occurred to-day between black and white laborers in South Street, New York.  WASHINGTON, April 13.  The rebels have reportedly evacuated their works at Centreville, Louisiana, in the night.  The fighting in the Tech country, Louisiana, is continuing.  CHICAGO, Sunday, April 12. A special to the Times, from Helena, Ark., 9th says: The entire Tallahatchie fleet, consisting of the divisions under Gens. ROSS and QUIMBY, and numerous gun and mortar-boats, arrived last night. The expedition, which has been absent forty-three days, left Fort Greenwood Sunday. As soon as the bustle was observed by the enemy, they opened a brisk fire.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 12.   Col. E. A. Kimball has been killed by Gen. Corcoran.   A battle between Gen. Banks' army and the rebels in the Tech Country, Louisiana, occurred to-day.  The steamer Stonewall Jackson has been destroyed off Charleston.  Our iron-clads have left Charleston Harbor.  NEW-YORK, SUNDAY, April 12. U.S. steam transport George Peabody, Atwell, New-Orleans March 31, via Key West April 6, with mdse. and passengers to U.S. Quartermaster. April 11, 11 A.M., 60 miles E. of Cape Henry, passed a schooner's foremast, carried away above the deck. also passed several floating bales of hay and flour barrels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK,  April 11.  A great meeting occurred to-day in New York to commemorate the attack on Fort Sumter in 1861.  Skrimishing has reportedly been occurring around Williamsburgh, Virginia.  A rebel telegram from Vicksburg, under date of Tuesday last, announces that GRANT's troops have struck their tents, abandoned the peninsula, cut the levee and turned the water into their camping ground. and that a number of transports, laden with his soldiers, have gone up the river. There have been rumors that Gen. GRANT was again about to change his base to Memphis, with the purpose of renewing his once baffled march into Central Mississippi.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 10.  Gen. Granger has been attacked by the rebel Van Dorn's army at Franklin, Tennessee.  A passanger train near Lavergne, Tennessee, was attacked by a rebel force.  An address from Jeff. Davis to the rebel states has been issued.  The Richmond (Va.) Whig, of April 9, revives ancient memories in politics by bringing forward two Old Whig names for public office in Virginia. A public meeting in Albemarle County presents the name of the Hon. W.C. RIVES for election to the Confederate Congress, which action the Whig warmly commends and hopes to see followed with unanimity by all other counties in the District.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 9.   The ship Morning Star has been captured by the Alabama.  A fight occurred to-day at Blount's Bridge and Kuff's Mills, North Carolina.  NEW YORK, April 9.  The subscriptions to the capital stock of the Atlantic Telegraph Company now exceed fifty thousand pounds sterling, among the bankers and leading merchants of this City, and additional subscriptions are being received daily. The amount already subscribed in this City and in London insures the success of the great enterprise next year beyond all reasonable doubt. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 8.  The Army of the Potomac was reviewed to-day by the President.  The monitor Keokuk has sank in Charleston Harbor.  The Yazoo Pass expedition that has been operating against Vicksburg has reportedly arrived at Helena, Arkansas.  A  QN venerable, white-haired QN  refugee in Washington asserts that Fort Sumter is clad in Palmetto logs and sheathed with 4 1E2-inch iron. that the channel is barricaded, and the harbor paved with monstrous torpedoes -- that 2,000 cannon are in positon, and that 116,000 troops hold the city. The patriarchal graybeard is despondent when he thinks of our bad prospects.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 7.  To-day our monitors attacked Fort Sumter in Charleston Harbor.  Our forces were repulsed.  An additional force from Newbern, North Carolina, has been sent to aid Gen. Foster at Washington, North Carolina.  The report of the Medical Board appointed to determine the physical disability of conscripts, is said to be made, and said to present many holes of escape. The plates for the fractional currency are complete, and will be put upon the presses in a few days. The notes will be of a much higher character than the postal, and will defy counterfeiting.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 6.  A report on the conduct of the war was published to-day.  Gen. Mitchell reportedly dashed into a rebel camp at Green Hill, Tennessee.  The President and his family visited the Army of the Potomac to-day.  The expedition against Charleston, South Carolina, has reportedly started for that city.  By order of Maj.-Gen. HOOKER, the prohibition as to granting leaves of absence and furloughs to members of the Tenth New-York (BRUEN's) and the Eleventh New-York (PUTTKAMER's) batteries has been rescinded, as both have recently improved much in discipline.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 5.  The Yazoo Pass expedition operating against Vicksburgh has left Fort Greenwood.  A force has left Newbern, North Carolina, to rescue Gen. Foster's army besieged at Washington, North Carolina.  The iron-clad fleet at Charleston Bar is reportedly armed.  NEWPORT. Rhode Island, April 5. -- Arrived schooners Sparkler, Greenlow, Belfast, for Washington, D.C.. Cape Ann. Cole, do., for Philadelphia: Francisco, Kilby, Portland, for New-York. M.S. Partride, Hix, Rockland, for do.. Montezuma. Dennis, for do.. Sarah Louisa, New-York, for Boston. Daniel G. Bridge, Portland, for New-York.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 4.  Gen. McClellan's report of his campaign, dated October 15, 1862, was to-day made public.  The town of Palmyra, on the Cumberland River, has been destroyed by our forces, in retaliation for the attack on the gunboat St. Clair.  The rebels have been repulsed at Woodbury, Tennessee.  LEWES, Delaware, April 4. -- There is a large fleet of vessels in the Breakwater taking refuge from the storm, including the ship Zanguebar, from New-Orleans, for Boston, 4 brigs, 2 steamers, and about 40 schooners. The steamer Patroon, from New-York, with 120 deserters for Washington, is on the beach. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 3.  The rebel Gen. Morgan has reportedly been defeated at Liberty, Tennessee.  GALLIPOLIS, Ohio, Sunday, March 29. Gov. Peirpoint: Yesterday two steamboats -- the Victor No. 2 and the Gen. Meigs -- were attacked about thirty-five miles below Charleston, West Virginia, by about 400 rebels. The boats escaped, losing two men and two horses. All praise is due Capts. FORD and SUMMERS for their coolness and bravery. Communication is cut off between here and Charleston.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, April 2.  A grand reception for Gen. Butler occurred to-day at the New York academy of music.  WASHINGTON, April 2.  There has been a rebel attack on our iron-clads at Tuscumbia, Alabama.  A serious bread riot occurred to-day in Richmond, Virginia.  A large number of women attacked the store houses.  GREAT SALT LAKE CITY, Thursday, March 19, 1863.  The past week has been one of remarkable tranquility, considering the circumstances. Col. CONNOR having telegraphically denied any intention of pouncing with a posse of military upon the  QN prophet, QN  the community have been relieved of extraordinary fears of any sudden sweep.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 1.  The schooner Antelope was captured off Charleston, South Carolina.  A sharp cavalry fight has occurred at Broad Run, Virginia, near Drainsville.  The intelligence that France had proposed to Great Britain and Russia to join her in advising the belligerents in this country to agree to an armistice, reached New-York by telegraph from Cape Race on the 25th inst. The substance of your Lordship's answer was received at the same time. Yesterday the text of the French proposal, of your Lordship's answer, and or the principal part of the Russian answer, was forwarded to New-York by telegraph from Halifax.</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
