<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 31.  A battle has commenced at Murfreesboro, Tennessee.  ST. LOUIS, Wednesday, Dec. 31. Gen. BLUNT telegraphs to Gen. CURTIS, under date of Van Buren, Ark., Dec. 28, as follows:  QN My long range guns are now shelling the rebel camp across the river, five miles below here. If the enemy does not retreat during the night, I shall endeavor to cross my troops in the morning, and offer them battle. Among the property captured, are four steamers, three of them partly loaded with supplies, a ferryboat and a large amount of ammunition. Quite a number of the enemy were killed. QN  
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Dec. 30, 1862. The examination of Brig.-Gen. Charles Griffin was resumed.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Dec. 23. Secretary CHASE has completed his financial bill, prepared on the invitation of the Committee of Ways and Means, and will send it to the committee at once. All the statements lately emanating from Washington in regard to its provisions are materially defective and erroneous. It seems to be certain that the President had made up his mind to the appointment of Judge USHER as Secretary of the Interior.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday, Dec. 29. The rebel Gen. STUART, with a force of from 2,000 to 4,000 cavalry and two pieces of artillery, made an attempt last night to capture the depot of stores at Fairfax Station, but without success. He took the precaution to visit Burke's Station first, where there were no troops, seized the telegraph operator, and by dispatches passing over the wires ascertained that his approach had been announced, and provision made to receive him. He then crossed to Alexandria Pike, and drove the pickets into Fairfax Court-house, when Gen. STOUGHTON opened fire upon him with two companies of the 15th Vermont, concealed in a piece of woods.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 28.  A bridge on the Louisville and Nashville Railroad has been destroyed by rebel Gen. Morgan.  New-Madrid, Missouri, has been evacuated.  There was an unsuccessful attempt of the rebel Gen. Stuart to capture the depot of stores at Fairfax Station, Virginia.  Van Buren, Arkansas, has been captured and the rebels put to flight.  HEADQUARTERS SIGEL's CORPS, Sunday, Dec. 28. A party of rebel cavalry, 2,500 strong, with six pieces of artillery, under command of FITZHUGH LEE, attacked our forces, under command of Col. CANBY, at Dumfries yesterday P.M. After a brisk fight of some three hours, the enemy was repulsed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 27.  A party of rebel cavalry have been repulsed at Dumfries, Virginia.  Rebel Gen. John Morgan and his guerrillas have attacked a Union force at Elizabethtown, Kentucky.  LOUISVILLE, Ky., Friday, Dec. 26. JOHN MORGAN, with a force of about 3,000 cavalry, entered Glasgow on Wednesday. Three companies of the Second Michigan Cavalry opposed his entrance, but fell back on Munfordsville, having lost one captain and two privates. The rebels lost two captains, five privates and seven prisoners. The rebels were then reinforced and remained in possession of Glasgow.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 26.  In Minnesota, 38 Indians were executed to-day by hanging.  HEADQUARTERS ARMY OF POTOMAC, Friday, Dec. 26. All is quiet here to-night, and nothing has occurred within the last twenty-four hours worth telegraphing.  The Richmond Dispatch, of the 17th inst., contains in its telegraphic columns the following dispatches: FROM NORTH CAROLINA. RALEIGH, Tuesday, Dec. 16. The bill to raise ten thousand troops for State defence passed the second reading in the House to-day. The troops are to be taken from those liable to conscription. The vote was close. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 25.  Rebels under Gens. Floyd and Marshall have reportedly reentered Eastern Kentucky through Pound Gap.  Glasgow, Kentucky, has been captured by rebel Gen. Morgan.  NASHVILLE, Tuesday, Dec. 16, 1862. Upon my return from Louisville I am enabled to present your readers with a statement of the disgraceful surrender at Hartsville, the news of which reached you some days since. The brigade which was stationed at this post was commanded by Col. MOORE, of the One Hundred and Fourth Illinois -- who said some weeks since, in a speech made at the Galt House in Louisville, that  QN he only wanted to catch MORGAN. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 24.  A severe skirmish has occurred on the Blackwater river in Virginia.  PARIS, Friday, Dec. 5, 1862.  The following words of the Moniteur in regard to the arrival of the French fleet at New Orleans may or may not possess importance:  QN The arrival of these three vessels was received with lively satisfaction by the people of New-Orleans, and the French residents show themselves happy at this new proof of the solicitude of the Government of the Emperor. QN   Tuesday, Dec. 23, 1862. A report circulated two days ago, to the effect that the rebels had crossed 30,000 infantry over the Upper Rappahannock, proves to have been greatly exaggerated.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 23.  A Congressional Committee has completed a report on the battle of Fredericksburgh.  Gen. Burnside has returned from Washington to his army.  Winchester, Virginia, is reoccupied by Union forces under Col. Keyes.  Confederate President Jefferson Davis has issued a Retaliatory Proclamation, especially directed against Gen. Butler and his officers.  FORTRESS MONROE, Tuesday, Dec. 23. Gen. FOSTER arrived at Fortress Monroe this morning. After leaving Kinston his forces took Goldsboro without much loss, tearing up the railroad, burning the ties, and destroying the rails so they cannot be used again, and also destroyed the telegraph.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 22.  The President addressed the Army of the Potomac in regard to the occurrences at Fredericksburgh.  ST. LOUIS, Mo., Wednesday, Dec. 17. Gen. HERRON telegraphs that Gen. CURTIS' victory at Prairie Grove was much more complete and the enemy's loss far greater than first reported. Over 1,500 rebels were killed and buried by us. Their wounded were found scattered through the woods for miles in the rear of their position, which had been carried during the action, and left where they retreated. Many consequently died for want of attention. Our cavalry pursued the retreating rebels closely, driving them beyond Van Buren.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, December 21.   The transport Niagara, as the telegraph has already informed us, which left here a few days ago with five hundred soldiers, had to put into Philadelphia to escape destruction. and on examination, her cross-timbers were found to be a mass of black-rot. Our South Carolina correspondent yesterday described the condition of the ship Thames, also of the Banks Expedition, which put into Port Royal on the 10th in a disabled condition, and was there surveyed and condemned. The report of the Examining Board was, that she was altogether unseaworthy.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 20.  GEN. SEGEL's HEADQUARTERS, STAFFORD COURT-HOUSE, Monday, Dec. 15, 1862. After a somewhat tedious march of three days --over numerous streams and muddy roads--we have arrived at the point indicated above. No incident of importance has transpired since we left Fairfax Court-house and Centreville, except that at Dumfries, HAMPTON'S Legion made a dash into the town, early Friday morning, and captured the telegraph operator, Mr. LAME, of Boston.   This is the second time Mr. LAMB has had the misfortune of falling into the hands of the rebels -- the first time he was taken in the Shenandoah Valley.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, WOMAN's CENTRAL RELIEF ASSOCIATION, BRANCH OF THE U.S. SANITARY COMMISSION, Dec. 19, 1862. Pressing telegraphic dispatches have been received at this office, making demands on us to which we are utterly unable to respond. The emergency caused by the recent battle at Fredericksburgh calls for very large supplies of shirts, drawers and woolen socks. The stock both here and in Washington is exhausted, and we earnestly ask the prompt assistance of all interested in our cause. Contributions of flannel will be most acceptable from those who cannot send us ready-made clothing, as many persons are now offering their labor.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday, Dec. 18. The Court-martial in Gen. Porter's case met at 11 o'clock. Theo. E. Mooreland and J.L. Cherry, telegraphic operators, were examined with regard to the messages referred to in the testimony of Gen. Pope, as being transmitted by Gen. Porter to Gen. Burnside, severely criticising the military operations of Gen. Pope.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 17.  Baton Rouge has reportedly been recaptured.  HEADQUARTERS DEPARTMENT OF THE GULF, NEW-ORLEANS, Dec. 17, 1862. GENERAL ORDERS, No. 110. -- 1. All the telegraph lines in this Department are placed under the protection of the Government. By orders from the War Department, CHARLES S. BULKLEY will have the control of all telegraph lines, and will take charge of all telegraph offices and materials in this Department. Commanding officers will afford the necessary aid for the protection and repair of the lines.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 16.  A letter has reportedly been written by Gen. Burnside in which he assumes responsibility for the defeat at Fredericksburgh.  A rebel raid has occurred on Occoquan, Virginia.  Gen. Butler transferred command of the Department of the Gulf to Gen. Banks.  Gen. Banks has issued a general order that states he has assumed command of the Department of the Gulf, including Texas.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 15.  Fredericksburgh was evacuated by our army during the night.  Gen. Butler issued his farewell address to his army.   BOSTON, Dec. 15 --Capt. Robinson, of schr. Franklin Bell, which arrived last night, reports. When lying in Rio Grande, the brig Winthrop, formerly of New-York, but now under British colors, came into port in charge of the second mate of a Brazilian brig, who reported having fallen in with her a few days previous, with signal of distress flying. On boarding her, found the second mate, an Austrian, in irons. The crew stated that the second mate of the W. had murdered the captain and the chief mate. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 14.  Another raid into Poolesville, Maryland, has been made by rebel cavalry.  At James Island, North Carolina, there has been firing on rebel pickets.  Kinston, North Carolina is occupied by Gen. Foster's army.  The rebel salt works at Yellville, Arkansas, was destroyed by Capt. Birch.  Gen. N.P. Banks arrived at New-Orleans with his expedition.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 13.  The Battle of Fredericksburgh is continuing to-day.  It is largely being fought in the back of the town.  GREAT SALT LAKE CITY, Thursday, Nov. 13, 1862.  Success to the Pacific Railroad, or it rather should be called the Atlantic and Pacific Railroad, for it certainly will be of those two oceans the connection most useful and vital to the Union. All right-minded men here desire the speedy consummation of so magnificent and beneficent an enterprise. With its accomplishment the isolation of this Territory will be destroyed. Utah, can then share equally in the benefits arising from the traffic of the two slopes. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 12.  The Union army continued to cross at Fredericksburgh to-day.  Artillery dueling continues between the opposing forces.  There has been a skirmish near Suffolk, Virginia.  The gunboat Cairo has been destroyed on the Yazoo River by a rebel torpedo.  The Senate Post-office Committee, at their meeting to-day, authorized their Chairman to report in favor of the proposition for sounding for a telegraph line from San Francisco to the mouth of the Amoor River. The bids for furnishing Indian goods to the Government were, to-day, opened by Commissioner DOLE, in the presence of the bidders, many of whom were from New-York and Boston.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 11.  Fredericksburgh has been thoroughly shelled.  The place is now occupied by our troops who crossed the river in the face of a terrible fire.  The city has been partially destroyed.  There has been a successful reconnaissance from Nashville.  Two of Gen. Banks' vessels have arrived at Port Royal in a disabled state.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 10.  The rebels have reportedly appeared in force at Nashville and have driven in our pickets.  There was a gunboat fight at Port Royal, Virginia.  Plymouth, North Carolina, has been destroyed by the rebels.  WILLIAMSPORT, Penn., Saturday, Dec. 6. The whole business portion of Lockhaven is reported to be on fire this morning. Our Fire Department has gone thither on a special train. The telegraph operator at Lockhaven reported his office on fire before removing his instruments. We have heard nothing since. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 9.  A sharp fight occurred to-day at Laverne, Tennessee.  BURR's STATION, FIVE MILES FROM THE POTOMAC, Friday, Nov. 28, 1862. As yet there is no movement from this point. Last night a heavy train of supplies arrived from Aquia Creek. The sight of the train caused a shout among the boys, who think at least they have been rather short of rations during the last few days. A train passed here for the first time, to-day, for Falmouth. Now that supplies can be obtained with ease further to the front, our forces here will doubtless move forward. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 8.  The President ordered the execution of thirty-nine Indians in Minnesota.  Execution is to take place December 19.  The Steamer Lake City was destroyed by the rebels at Concordia, Arkansas.  SPRINGFIELD, Mo., Saturday, Nov. 29. Gen. BLUNT, with 5,000 National soldiers, attacked and routed 8,000 rebels, under Gen. MARMADUEK, at Cane Hill, Ark., on the 20th instant. Sixty rebels were killed in the engagement, and the balance driven some twenty miles. Gen. BLUNT telegraphs that the rebels are badly whipped, and will not probably venture north of the Boston Mountains again this Winter.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 7.  A battle at Fayetteville or Prairie Grove, Arkansas, occurred to-day.  It was a Union victory.  A battle against rebel Gen. Morgan's force occurred to-day at Hartsville, Tennessee.  A Union brigade was captured by the rebels who were afterward put to flight.  The California steamer Ariel has been captured by the Alabama.  The Ariel was released upon giving bonds for  SX 228,000, payable 30 days after the recognition of the Southern Confederacy.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 6.  An attack on our forces occurred to-day at Cane Hill, Arkansas.  The rebels were repulsed.  POTOMAC CREEK, SEVEN MILES THE POTOMAC RIVER, AND TEN FROM FREDERICKSBURGH. VA., Friday, Nov. 28. 1862.  The bridge over this stream has been the only connecting link needed in the railroad from Aquia Creek to Fredericksburgh. The structure now completed is about ninety feet high, consisting of one bent erected above another, and firmly stayed on each side.  Mr. HARVEY ROSELLE, with some fifty men, has had charge of the building of the work, which has been completed in less than a week's time.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 5.  There has been a cavalry engagement near Coffeeville, Mississippi.   WASHINGTON, Friday, Dec. 5. The report of Secretary CHASE is receiving commendation from unexpected quarters, and is universally conceded to display an uncommon aptness in dealing with the difficult problems of finance which now perplex the country. Strong opposition to some of his recommendations is being developed on the part of the friends of the banks, who seem to regard them as adverse to the interests of those institutions, but the general expression of opinion indicates that his policy will be sustained by Congress.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 4.  Gen. Banks and a part of his expedition has sailed from New York.  Dec. 3 -- Arr. brigantine Clyde, from New-York. Sailed -- Steamer Dictator, for Buffalo, N.Y.. schr. Brooks, for New-York. CANALBOAT SUNK. -- The canalboat Phillips, from Buffalo, with 8,000 bushels of barley, this morning, while towing up the East River, struck the bulkhead of Pier No. 27, and stove in her how. She was immediately towed to Governor's Island, where she now lies sunk.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 3.  Winchester, Virginia, has been surrendered to Gen. Geary and the place is occupied.  BOSTON, Dec. 3. -- The steamships Ruby and Giraffe sailed from Greenock Nov. 14, for the purpose of running the blockade.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Nov. 25 -- 11 P.M. Advices from the TIMES' special correspondent at Falmouth, dated this morning, show clearly that the rebels, instead of evacuating Fredericksburgh, are preparing vigorously to dispute the passage of our troops across the river.  Their garrison has been reinforced by the Divisions under LONGSTREET and D.H. HILL, variously estimated at from 25,000 to 75,000 men.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 2.  A party of Union cavalry has been surprised and captured at King George Court-house, Virginia.  A fight occurred to-day at Suffolk, Virginia.  The rebels deserted their fortifications at Abbeville, Mississippi, and the place was occupied by the cavalry of Gen. Grant's army. OFFUT's CROSS ROADS, MONTGOMERY, Tuesday, Nov. 25. This morning at daylight a body of rebel cavalry, said to be sixty strong, entered Poolesville, seized Messrs. CHERRY AND SARGEANT, the Government telegraph operators stationed there, in bed, paroled them, and permitted them to telegraph their mishaps to Washington. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 1.  Tallahatchie, Mississippi, has been evacuated by the rebels.  SAN FRANSISCO, Thursday, Nov. 20. The Money market is quiet, with an ample supply of capital at 11E2 TO 2. Exchange remains the same as at last steamer day.  Coal Oil inflated. sales 60c. TO 70c. Hard Coal declined. sales,  SX 18.75. The ships Highlander and Madalan been chartered to take Wheat to Liverpool, the former at  PX 2 10 UT . Desirable tonnage is still scarce and wanted. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 30.  The steamer Vanderbilt returned from a cruise in which it pursued the Alabama.  SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Nov. 19.  Telegraphic news from Oregon mention the hanging of four highway robbers by vigilance committees at Florence City and Lewiston, in Washington Territory, on the 9th. It is believed an organized band of highwaymen infest the mining region.   The President has issued an order directing that the Attorney-General be charged with the superintendence and direction of all proceedings under the Confiscation Act, and authorizing him to call upon the military authorities to aid him in carrying out its provisions. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 29.  Gen. Stahl's force has reached Perryville, Virginia, via Snicker's Gap, where they had a skirmish with the rebels.  The rebels were completely routed.  President LINCOLN's Message will probably be transmitted to Congress on the first day of the session. No copies of this important document will be sent out in advance, therefore it will be telegraphed to the Press as soon as its reading shall be commenced. The object of this course is understood to be the prevention of a premature disclosure of its contents, and to enable the President to avail himself of the latest official intelligence that may come to hand.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 28.  A battle occurred to-day at Cane Hill, Arkansas.  Gen. Stahl's force drove in the rebel pickets at Ashby's Gap, Virginia.  Gen. Burnside arrived in Washington from the Army of the Potomac.  Gen. Grant's army struck their tents and marched in the direction of Holly Springs, Mississippi.  NASHVILLE, Wednesday, Nov. 12, 1862. Since Friday last the arrival of troops has been continuous, and the woods upon the opposite bank of the river, at night, are ruddy with the light of camp fires. The city is now under command of Maj.-Gen. A. McDOWELL McCOOK, who occupies Gen. NEGLEY'S former quarters, on High-street.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 27.  A skirmish occurred to-day near Nashville.  The railroad from Aquia Creek to Falmouth, Virginia, has been completed.  Gen. Stahl's cavalry has completed a reconnaissance in force.  SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Nov. 19. Arrived, an Italian schooner of fifty tons, from Mazatlan, bringing  SX 128,000 in treasure. Sailed, ship Windward, for New-York. Trade is moderately active. sales 1,000 firkins butter at 25c., market firmer. 60,000 lbs. San Francisco Cordage at 91E2c. TO 10c.. 25,000 lbs. Taried, 121E2c.. Cheese, 15c.. Drills, 50c.. Bales, 20c.. Eastern Hops, 20c.. 5,000 kegs Nails at  SX 4. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 26.  The President visited Gen. Burnside at Belleplaine, Virginia, to-day.  Successful reconnaissance has occurred from Bolivar Heights.  Gen. Sherman's force has reportedly left Memphis.  The rebel camp at Cold Knob, Virginia, has come under surprise attack.  HEADQUARTERS ELEVENTH ARMY CORPS, FAIRFAX COURT-HOUSE, Tuesday, Nov. 18, 1862. The headquarters of the Eleventh army Corps were transferred from Gainesville to this place, today. The main portion of the Army of the Potomac having swept down Bull Run Valley, and halted a week at Warrenton, has again taken up its line of march southward.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 25.  A rebel raid has been made into Poolesville, Maryland.  Rebels attacked to-day at Newbern, North Carolina.  LIVERPOOL, Saturday, Nov. 8. The Asia has arrived. COTTON -- Sales, to-day, 1,250 bales. Market very dull and easier. All qualities slightly lower. Speculators and exporters took 600. Breadstuffs quiet but steady. Provisions heavy. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 24.  Scouting parties left camp near Charlestown, Virginia, and marked 210 miles in 70 hours.  The London Morning Post traces the inaction of Gen. MCCLELLAN's army to the success of the Democrats in the State elections. It says that Gen. MCCLELLAN is a consistent Democrat, that he is a universal favorite with the people and the soldiers, and that it is well known that he is not unwilling to see the war terminated. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 23. ST. JOHNS, N.F., Wednesday, Nov. 19. The steamship Anglo-Saxon, from Liverpool at 10 1E2 o'clock on the morning of the 6th, via Londonderry on the 7th instant, passed Cape Race en route to Quebec at 8 o'clock this morning. She was boarded by the news-yacht of the Associated Press, and a summary of her news obtained. The Anglo-Saxon is the last steamer this season for Quebec. The steamship Hansa, from New-York, arrived at Southampton on the 6th inst. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 22.  The War Department has issued an order releasing persons who have been imprisoned for resisting the draft, discouraging enlistments, etc., and also paroling persons who had been sent from the rebel States by the Military Commanders or Governors.  Brig. Gen. Francis E Patterson died to-day, reportedly of a self-inflicted gunshot wound.  He has been criticized for withdrawing troops from Catlett's Station based on unconfirmed reports of Confederate forces in the area.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 21.  It is reported that Gen. Sumner has demanded the surrender of Fredericksburgh.   LONDON, Friday, Nov. 7. The Spanish Government has demanded the punishment of the Americans who violated the Spanish flag on the coast of Cuba. The American Minister at Madrid had an audience with the Queen of Spain, and assured Her Majesty that the American Government did not authorize the acts of the Captain of the Federal gunboat Montgomery.  PARIS, Friday, Nov. 7. The Bank of France has advanced its rate of discount to four per cent. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 20.  A skirmish occurred to-day at Charlestown, Virginia.  GAINESVILLE, Saturday, Nov. 15, 1862. At the date of this letter it will be seen that Gen. SIGEL's headquarters are still at this place, and not further South, as many loyal people north of this hope and believe.  WARRENTON JUNCTION, Va., Sunday, Nov. 16, 1862. The only notable event of the day at this place. has been a flying visit from Major-Gen. BURNSIDE. His advent was entirely unexpected. Soon, however, as the fact became known, the troops stationed at the junction were called out to do him honor. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 19.  Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry are reportedly near Warrenton Junction.  Our pickets have been driven in at Suffolk, Virginia.  GRAND JUNCTION, Miss., Wednesday, Nov. 12, 1862. The route from Cairo at present, is by boat, to that once famous  QN American Gibraltar, QN  Columbus, thence by a series of spasmodic forward movements by rail, until this place is reached.  The ugly-looking torpedoes along the levee have been removed. the charred ruins of the railroad and other buildings replaced by roomy and substantial wooden storehouses.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 18.  The Army of the Potomac reached Falmouth, opposite Fredericksburgh, Virginia.  A skirmish has occurred at Rural Hill, Virginia.  The Alabama escaped from Martinique.  Gen. POPE, as before announced, recently sent form St. Paul, Minn., by telegraph, the names of 324 Sioux Indians, whom a Military Commission had sentenced to death. The dispatch cost the snug little sum of  SX 400. That amount ought to be deducted from Gen. POPE's salary. Of these 324 Indians, 304 have been sentenced to be hung, and 20 to be imprisoned. The few remaining friendly Indians, with all the squaws and papooses, are to come down to Fort Snelling.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 17.  There has been an artillery engagement near Fredericksburg, Virginia.  Confederate President Jefferson Davis has ordered retaliation for the execution of ten rebels in Missouri.  The Alabama has arrived at Martinique, in the Caribbean.  The United States Frigate San Jacinto arrived at the same place and went outside the harbor to await the appearance of the Alabama.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 16.  Gen. Burnside's headquarters has been moved to Catlett's Station, Virginia.  The Postmaster-General has given orders for the redemption of the postage-stamps that have been used for currency. Arrangements for carrying out this order will be perfected in a few days, and the return of Mr. WAKEMAN, who has been urging this matter upon the Department during his present visit to Washington.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 15.  A. J. Hamilton has been appointed Military Governor of Texas.  To-day an artillery fight occurred near Fayetteville, Virginia.  Warrenton, Virginia, has been evacuated by our troops.  HOLMES' HOLE, Nov. 8. -- The following is the condition of the vessels ashore here, viz. Brig Abner, of Bangor, tight. brig Alvira Clark, leaky. schr. M.E. Pierce, tight. schr. Eliza Ellen, tight. schr. Bendovi. tight. schr. Sarah Louise, tight. schr. Benjamin, tight. schr. Fred. Hall, tight. The schr. Arctic, of St. John. N.B., from New-York for St. Johns, also two other schooners and two sloops, went ashore here yesterday, in a severe gale from N.E. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 14.  The following are exempt from conscription under the laws of the United States: All persons now in the military service of the United States, all telegraph operators and constructors, actually engaged on the 5th day of August, 1862, all engineers of locomotives on railroads, all artificers and workmen employed in any public arsenal or armory, the Vice-President of the United States, the officers of the Government of the United States, the members of both Houses of Congress and their respective officers. All Custom-house officers and their clerks, all past officers and stage drivers who are employed in the conveyance of the mail.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 13.  A skirmish has reportedly occurred near White Sulphur Springs, Virginia.  Holly Springs, Mississippi, is now occupied by Union troops after a slight skirmish.  HEADQUARTERS OF THE ARMY, WASHINGTON, Oct. 28, 1862. HON. E.M. STANTON, Secretary of War -- Sir: In reply to the general interrogatories contained in your letter of yesterday, on several occasions Gen. MCCLELLAN has telegraphed to me that his army was deficient in certain supplies. All these telegrams were immediately referred to the heads of Bureaus with orders to report. It was ascertained that in every instance the requisitions had been filled. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 12.  Gen. Halleck has reportedly visited the Army of the Potomac to-day.  Gen. Grant's advance has reached Holly Springs, Mississippi.  LOUISVILLE, Wednesday, Nov. 12, 1862. Guerrillas apparently are at work again on the line of the Louisville and Nashville Railroad, below Munfordsville or Bowling Green, for telegraphic intercourse with Nashville was cut off last evening. ROSECRANS' forces appear somewhat scattered, in order to guard his communications and flanks, and are probably sufficiently strong and alert at every important post to prevent any surprise or surrender.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 11.  Gen. Grant has reported a victory at Garretsburgh, Kentucky.  Gen. Rosecrans' command has arrived at Fort Donelson.  Messrs. GLASS, ELLIOTT  ES  Co., the Submarine Telegraph Contractors, had written a letter to Mr. CYRUS W. FIELD, of which the following is an extract:  QN In reply to your inquiries, we beg to state that we are perfectly confident that a good and durable submarine cable can be laid direct from Ireland to Newfoundland, and are willing to undertake the contract, upon the specified conditions. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 10.  To-day, Gen. Rosecrans arrived at Nashville.  Gen. Halleck has ordered all absent officers to return to their regiments.  Gen. Pleasanton's pickets have been attacked near Amosville, Virginia.  There has been a great Union demonstration in Memphis.  WASHINGTON, Monday, Nov. 10. An official report was received to-day at the headquarters of the army regarding an expedition from the Department of the South, Hilton Head, S.C., dated November 1, 1862, to destroy the Charleston and Savannah Railroad and bridges therewith connected.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 9.  Gen. Butler has sequestered the property in the district of La Fourche, Louisiana, and declared all sales made by disloyal persons since September 18 to be void.  A brilliant cavalry dash of Bayard's men has occurred at Fredericksburg.  Saturday, Nov. 8. The schooner Moses Waring, with a cargo of coal, from Philadelphia for Boston, is ashore at Holmes' Hole, and full of water.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 8.  Gen. Pleasanton is now engaged in a skirmish near Little Washington, Virginia.  Gen. Bayard has held the railroad bridge across the Rappahannock.  A Cavalry charge on the rebels occurred near Gaine's Cross Roads.  The ship T. B. Wales was captured by the Alabama.  LOUISVILLE, KY., Saturday, Nov. 8. About eighty rebel prisoners arrived from Lebanon, Ky., to-night, including a son of HUMPHREY MARSHALL, who had violated his parole and joined the rebels.  BOSTON, Saturday, Nov. 8 -- 1 1E2 P.M. The weather continues thick and rainy. CLEVELAND, Saturday, Nov. 8 -- 11 A.M. A snow-storm commenced at 8 o'clock.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 7.  Command of the Army of the Potomac passed to-day from Gen. McClellan to Gen. Burnside.  Gen. Bayard has been attacked at Rappahannock Station, Virginia.  An expedition up Sapelo Sound, Georgia, is partly comprised of negro troops.  POTOMAC, Tuesday Evening, Nov. 4, 1862. The telegraph ere this has informed you of the National occupation of this famous Gap in the Blue Ridge. Our forces reached here by rapid marches from Harper's Perry, Sunday morning, about 10 o'clock, much to the surprise of the citizens and soldiers, who are picketing out on the Leesburgh turnpike for several miles. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 6.  Brig. Gen. Chas. Jameson died to-day as did Commodore G. J. Pendergast of the U.S.N.  Warrenton, Virginia is now occupied by advance forces of the Army of the Potomac.  Gen. McCook's corps has arrived at Nashville.  The English schooner Dart has been captured.  GAINESVILLE, Tuesday, Nov. 4, 1862. Gen. SIGEL's corps is in its new position, and the General himself is expected to be here this morning. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 5.  Gen. Pleasanton has reportedly routed Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry and is now near Chester Gap, Virginia.  An engagement occurred to-day at New-Baltimore, Virginia.  Skirmishing also occurred to-day near Nashville, Tennessee.  NEW YORK, Nov. 5.  The United States steamship Florida, L.C. SARTORI Commander, from Port Royal in four days, arrived this morning. She brings 40 prisoners taken from the prize vessels lately captured, and the sick from the South Atlantic blockading squadron. The Florida sailed from New-York, Oct. 16, 1861, in the Port Royal expedition, and since then has been constantly employed on the blockade. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 4.  Ashby's Gap has been taken possession by Union troops.  Gen. McClellan's headquarters is now at Upperville, Virginia.  MEMPHIS, November 4.  Gen. Grant, with several divisions of the army from Bolivar, Tennessee, and Corinth, Mississippi, marched into Lagrange, Mississippi.  The rebels, under Gen. Earl Van Dorn, are in large force at Holly Springs, Mississippi.  WASHINGTON, November 4.  A spirited engagement occurred to-day at Markham, Virginia.  The salt works at Kingsbury, Georgia, are reportedly destroyed, in effecting which our forces were attacked.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 3.  Gen. Pleasanton's cavalry occupied Upperville, Virginia, after a spirited engagement with the enemy of about four hours.  Gen. Stahl's cavalry drove the enemy from Thoroughfare Gap, Virginia, which was afterward occupied by Gen. Schurz.  Maj. Gen. J.B. Richardson died at Sharpsburgh, Maryland, to-day, from wounds received in the battle of Antietam.  Commodore W.D. Porter offered the merchants of New York to take the clipper ship Drednought and pursue the pirate Alabama.  Piedmont, Virginia, was occupied by our cavalry, under Gens. Pleasanton and Averill.  Maj. Reid Sanders, C.S.A., was captured on the coast of Virginia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 2.  The artillery fight at Phillimont renewed and the rebels fell back.  Additional force of our troops took possession of Snicker's Gap, Virginia.  Gen. Foster's expedition from Newbern took up its line of march.  The schooner Alice was captured by the Alabama.  WASHINGTON, Sunday, Nov. 2. The news received here to-night from the vicinity of Aldie and Middleburgh show that no important operations have taken place, beyond skirmishing between PLEASANTON and STUART, in which the losses on our side were very slight. The Military Commission closed the testimony in the Harper's Ferry case with that of Gen. WOOL.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 1.  An artillery fight has occurred between Gen. Pleasanton's force and the rebels at Phillimont, Virginia, lasting five hours.    ST. LOUIS, November 1.  There was a grand ovation to Gen. Fremont in St. Louis.  METROPOLITAN POLICE,  NEW-YORK, Nov. 1, 1862. GENERAL ORDER No. 323. The Police telegraph instrument, after sundown on Nov. 4th inst., will be used exclusively in transmitting election returns. The only exception will be in notifying the Central Office of any serious disturbance requiring aid, the locality of a fire or the detention of lost children.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 31.  A skirmish with rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry occurred to-day at Marysville, Virginia.  The advance guard of the column for the relief of Nashville passed through Bowling Green, Kentucky.  BALTIMORE, Wednesday, Oct. 29. The loyal citizens arrested last night, were taken on board the steamer Baltimore, on which they proceeded down the bay, to Seven-foot Knoll, where they now lay at anchor. At the wharf there was much excitement. The city police, who were at the boat, were recalled, but were forced to remain by a cavalry force. Gov. BRADFORD reached the wharf before the departure of the boat, and was permitted an interview.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 30.  Brig Baron de Castine was captured by the pirate Alabama, and released on giving bonds for  SX 6,000, payable to the President of the Confederate States thirty days after peace shall be declared.  ST. LOUIS, October 30.  Gen. U.S. Grant reported that the guerrillas at Clarkston, Missouri, had been attacked, routed, and utterly dispersed.  WASHINGTON, October 30.  Gen. Rosecrans and staff arrived at Louisville, Kentucky.  Gen. O.M. Mitchell, commander of the Department of the South, died of yellow fever at Beaufort, South Carolina to-day.  The English brig Hermasa was captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 29.  To-day there was a skirmish between Gen. Walker's rebel force and Gen. Bayard's cavalry at Upperville and Paris, Virginia.  There was a great fire at Harper's Ferry. twenty six cars loaded with hay were simultaneously in flames.  A part of the railroad bridge was destroyed.  Rebels at Snicker's Gap, Virginia, are currently in force.  Gen. Richardson's division, of Gen. McClellan's army, passed Snicker's Gap into Paris, Virginia.  The corps d'armee under Gen. Cox reached Charlestown, Virginia.  On their entrance they were greeted with cheers and other demonstrations of favor.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 28.  Our troops are occupying Halltown, Virginia, and our pickets are extended beyond there.  Gen. Price's pickets have been driven from Grand Junction. A skirmish occurred at Snicker's Gap, Virginia.  The bark Laurietta has been captured and burned by the pirate Alabama.  MEMPHIS, October 28.  The Union troops under Gen. Herron attacked a rebel camp four miles from Fayetteville, Arkansas.  After a sharp engagement of an hour the enemy were completely routed, leaving all their camp equipage and a few wagons.  Gen. Herron pursued the rebels several miles into the Boston Mountains.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 27.  Gen. Jeff. C. Davis has been indicted for killing Gen. Nelson.  The English steamer Anglia, of Liverpool, was captured four miles inside of Bull's Bay, South Carolina.  She was loaded with arms, ammunition, and other contraband goods.  The rebel army under Gens. Echols, Floyd, and Jenkins retreated from Charlestown, Virginia.  ST. LOUIS, October 27.  Over 1,000 rebels have attacked and been defeated at Putnam's Ferry, Missouri.  NEW ORLEANS, October 27.  A battle occurred to-day at Labadieville, on Bayou La Fourche, Louisiana.  The rebels were put to flight after a short resistance.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 26.  There was a heavy rain overnight and a rise in the Potomac.  The advance of Gen. McClellan's army commenced.  Gen. Burnside's division crossed into Virginia.  Gen. Pleasanton's cavalry reached Purcellsville.  Gen. McClellan established his headquarters in Virginia.  The schooner Crenshaw, of New-York, was captured and burned by the pirate Alabama.  MEMPHIS, October 26.  Gen. Weitzel's expedition from New Orleans has landed at Donaldsonville, and his troops took up the line of march.  A sharp engagement ensued, in which we took over 200 prisoners and some artillery.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 25.  Slight cavalry skirmishing occurred to-day at Manassas Junction and Bristol Station.  MEMPHIS, October 25.  Gen. Sherman issued a stringent order for the Government of Memphis to-day.  ST. LOUIS, October 25.  Our forces routed the rebels at Greenville, Missouri.  PHILADELPHIA, October 25.  There has been difficulty with the coal miners, relative to the draft.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 24.  Gen. Buell has been removed from the command of the army in Kentucky, and Gen. Rosecrans has been assigned to the command.  Gen. U.S. Grant reports a skirmish at Brownsville, Tennessee, in which the rebels were defeated with a loss of 40 prisoners and some property.  A skirmish occurred with Morgan's guerrillas at Morgantown, Kentucky. 16 rebels were captured.  The English steamer Scolia, loaded with arms, powder, etc. was captured at Bull's Bay, South Carolina.  MEMPHIS, October 24.  Gen. Weitzel's brigade, 5,000 strong, left Carrollton above New Orleans.  The expedition was made up of transports and gunboats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 23.  There has been a dashing fight at Waverly, Tennessee, between a small force of rebels and Union soldiers, in which the rebels were defeated and lost many more than we did.  Skirmishing has occurred in Kentucky with Morgan's guerrillas.  The ship Lafayette, of New Haven, has been captured and burned by the pirate Alabama.  The English schooner Francis has been captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 22.  The Governor of Kentucky has to-day called on the people of Louisville to rally for the defense of the city.  Rebel Gen. Humphrey Marshall's force has retreated from Mount Stirling toward East Tennessee.  Rebel Gen. Bragg's rebel army has moved through Cumberland Gap.  Our forces attacked Pocotaligo and Coosawhatchie, South Carolina, to-day.  They succeeded in reaching the Charleston and Savannah Railroad, and did it some damage.   A battle occurred to-day at Maysville, Arkansas.  Our forces, under Gen. Blunt, attacked the enemy, supposed to be 6,000 to 7,000 strong, and after an hour of fighting totally routed them.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 21.  To-day an expedition from Gen. McClellan's army went to intercept a force of rebel cavalry foraging in London County, Virginia.  The expedition was successful.  A dashing reconnaissance has been completed in the direction of Leesburgh, Virginia.  There was considerable skirmishing with rebel cavalry.  Gen. Jefferson C. Davis was released from arrest, and ordered to report for duty at Cincinnati.  An expedition consisting of over 4,000 men, with artillery, and fifteen transports and gunboats, left Hilton Head for a reconnaissance along the Charleston and Savannah Railroad.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 20.  At 3 o'clock this morning, 300 or 400 of Morgan's men captured a Union train of 81 wagons, 51 of which were loaded, near Bardstown, Kentucky.  Morgan then went toward Bardtown and captured another train at daylight.  An interview of Gen. HALLECK to-day with the President in the presence of the Secretary of War, is significant of the events foreshadowed in our dispatches of last week.  In Missouri, a rapid change is taking place in public sentiment on the question of emancipation and it is believed to be quite certain that the President's suggestions will be adopted there, and the State speedily relieved from Slavery by peaceful measures. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 19.  The rebel John Morgan left Lawrenceburgh, Kentucky, to-day with about 1,200 men, closely pursued by Gen. Dumont.  Col. Miller, of Gen. Negley's army, had a brush with the enemy, near Nashville, and captured several.  A large force of rebels, under Ewell and Jackson, has reportedly entered Martinsburgh, and completed the destruction of the railroad property there, including the depot and workshops.  A powerful iron steamer ran the blockade at Charleston, S.C. last night.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 18.  Rebel guerrilla chief Morgan dashed into Lexington, Kentucky, at the head of over 1,200 troops and took 125 prisoners, killing six of our men.   MEMPHIS, October 18.  A Federal steamer was fired into by the rebels thirty miles below Memphis.  The steamer Gladiator was also attacked 25 miles below Memphis and set on fire by the rebels. the flames were extinguished.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 17.  Gen. Hancock's expedition has returned to Bolivar Heights from Brucetown, five miles from Winchester, Virginia, where they found the enemy in force.  Over 1,000 bushels of wheat was reportedly captured.  Gen. Humphrey's division, which crossed near Shepherdstown, returned after finding the enemy in considerable force and after some artillery skirmishing.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 16.  Gen. McClellan's army has advanced to-day from Harper's Ferry.  The pursuit of rebel Gen. Bragg's army in Kentucky is reportedly virtually abandoned.  The British steamer Wachuta has been captured, after an all-day chase, off the coast of North Carolina.  A reconnaissance u the Apalachicola River, Florida, has resulted in the capture of a sloop laden with cotton.  HEADQUARTERS GEN. STAHL's COMMAND, GUM SPRING, Thursday, Oct. 16, 1862. Reliable information was received at this place yesterday, that Gen. STUART, with cavalry and artillery, was advancing and threatening this position. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 15.  Gen. Stahl left Centreville with cavalry and artillery to find the rebel Gen. Stuart.  He had some skirmishes, but nothing decisive resulted therefrom.  A heavy fight occurred to-day between Lexington and Richmond, Kentucky, in which the rebels were repulsed.  Our army reached Crab Orchard, Kentucky, after severe skirmishing.  The bark Lamplighter, of Boston, was captured and burned by the pirate Alabama.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 14.  The first donation of  SX 100,000 to the Sanitary Commission was received to-day from San Francisco.  In Kentucky, our whole force moved in pursuit of rebel Gen. Bragg's army early in the morning.  During the day some skirmishing took place.  SEDALIA, Mo., Monday, Oct. 13. The Sixth Missouri State Militia, Col. CATHERWOOD, have, in several scouting expeditions within the last few days, broken up various bands of guerillas killing the notorious JO. KIRK. who has murdered so many private citizens lately, as well as Capt. SANDERS, of the Third Mississippi, and Lieut. ALEXANDER, of the same regiment, and fifty bushwhackers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 13.  Rebel Gen. Bragg's army has reportedly evacuated Camp Dick Robinson, Kentucky.  BALTIMORE, Monday, Oct. 13. The American has the following special dispatch from Frederick:  QN The escape of the rebels across the Potomac is fully confirmed. After they were driven from Nolan's Ford they divided, and crossed the river in small bodies at different points. Two farmers, taken prisoner by them at Mercersburg, were paroled at the river, and arrived here to-day. The farmers report that Gen. STUART and Gen. WADE HAMPTON were both with the expedition. The cavalry force was a detachment from Virginia and South Carolina regiments. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 12.  Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry is occupying Leesburgh, Virginia, returning from their raid into Pennsylvania.  Gen. Pleasanton passed a few miles from Frederick, and effected their escape b y crossing the Potomac at White's Ferry.  Here the chase ended, our troops having met the rebels near the mouth of the Monacacy.  The rebels were clothed in captured National uniforms, which misled our soldiers, who were received, when in close proximity, by a fire of carbines and pistols.  Gen. Pleasanton's cavalry marched 90 miles in 24 hours.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, October 11.  Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry destroyed two warehouses at Chambersburgh, containing military stores. also the buildings of the Cumberland Valley Railroad, including the machine shops. the rolling stock collected there was also destroyed.  They also burned the railroad bridge at Scotland, five miles from Chambersburgh.  Gen. Wool and staff arrived at Harrisburgh and assumed the command and direction of the troops for the defence of the State.   WASHINGTON, October 11.  Rebels are in large force near Nashville, Tenn.  They sent a flag of truce, demanding the surrender of the city, which was refused by Gen. Negley, in command of post.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, October 10.  Today there was a rebel invasion of Pennsylvania.  Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry reached Chambersburgh about 6 p.m., having crossed the Potomac at McCoy's between Hancock and Williamsport.  WASHINGTON, October 10.  Gen. Rosecrans returned to the pursuit of rebel Gen. Price's army, reporting it dispersed, demoralized, and incapable of further mischief.  The ship Tonawanda was captured by he pirate Alabama and released on giving bonds for  SX 80,000, payable to the President of the Confederate States thirty days after the declaration of peace.  The ship Manchester and brig Dunkirk were also captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 9.  Gen. Grant recalled Gen. Rosecrans from the pursuit of the rebels defeated at Corinth.  The rebel army under Gen. Bragg was attacked at Chaplin Creek on its retreat.  A short but sharp fight ensued, when the rebels broke and fled.  PHILIDELPHIA, October 9.  Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry has reportedly started an expedition toward Pennsylvania.  The troops rendezvoused at Darksville at 12 M., marched thence to the vicinity of Hedgeville, where they encamped for the night.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 8.  Battle severe at Perryville, Kentucky, today.  It commenced at 12 1E2 p.m. and continued furiously until dark.  The rebel army was under command of Gen. Bragg.  The battle was commenced by the rebels furiously assaulting our army.  Among Gen. Bragg's wounded were Brig. Gens. Wood, Cleburne, and Brown.  Gen. Hardee was engaged in the battle, commanding the rebel left wing.  The rebels were everywhere repulsed, but not without some momentary advantages on the left.  Union Gens. Jackson and Terrell were killed.  Gen Rosseau was in the thickest of the fight and covered himself with glory.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 7.  Gen. Buell's army has arrived within two miles of Perryville, Kentucky, where the enemy were found to be in force.  Reconnaissance has occurred to the Rappahannock, through Centreville and Manassas Junction.  Gen. McClellan has issued an order to his army, calling attention to the President's emancipation proclamation and explaining the duties of the officers and soldiers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 6.  Gen. Halleck has peremptorily ordered Gen. McClellan  QN to cross the Potomac and give battle to the enemy, or drive him south.  Your army must move now, while the roads are good. QN   The English mail steamer Merlin was brought to off the harbor of St. George,, by a shot from one of Commodore Wilkes' fleet.  Gunboat Tascarora sailed from Fayal, in search of the Alabama.  An expedition is reportedly underway to destroy the salt works of the rebels on the coast of Florida.  LOUISVILLE, Monday, Oct. 6 -- 6 P.M. Telegraphic communication with Bardstown is just reestablished. The wires will keep pace with our army, as it proceeds.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MEMPHIS, October 5.  Galveston, Texas, is reportedly now occupied by Union forces.  The rebels, retreating from Corinth, reached the Hatchee River, where they were attacked and lost two batteries and some prisoners.  MOBILE, Thursday, Oct. 2. A dispatch to the Register, dated Tupelo to- day, says: Sixty Yankee cavalry scouts penetrated to the railroad two miles south of Baldwin, and cut the telegraph wires. They were attacked by twenty-five of the Second Tennessee Cavalry, and routed, with a loss of seven killed and two prisoners.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MEMPHIS, October 4.  The attack on our troops at Corinth, Mississippi, was resumed early in the morning.  The battle ended by a retreat of the whole rebel army.  It was won with great loss on both sides.  KNOXVILLE, October 4.  Gen. Buell's troops reached Bardstown, Kentucky, driving out the enemy's rear guard of cavalry and artillery.  The pursuit was continued toward Springfield.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MEMPHIS, October 3.  Rebels reportedly attacked our army near Corinth, Mississippi, early in the morning.  The rebels succeeded in capturing some of our guns during the day, and driving our forces back three or four miles to the fortifications of the town.  WASHINGTON, October 3.  In Kentucky, rebel Gen. John Morgan was repulsed near Olive Hill.  Union Gen. George Morgan reached Greenupsburgh, Kentucky, 15 miles from Portsmouth, Ohio, with his forces from Cumberland Gap, having marched 219 miles in 16 days.  President Lincoln reviewed the Army of the Potomac.  The ship Brilliant, enroute from New York to London, was burned by the pirate Alabama.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 2.  SPIRITUOUS LIQUORS. HEADQUARTERS DEFENCES OF WASHINGTON, WASHINGTON, Sept. 25, 1862. GENERAL ORDERS NO. 4. -- On and after the 28th inst., the guards at the bridges and ferries of the Potomac will be instructed to allow no wine or spirituous liquor to cross without a pass from the Provost Marshal of Washington to cover the stores. The Provost Marshal will grant such passes only on satisfactory evidence that the articles arc for hospital stores, or the private property of an officer. All wines or liquors attempted to be taken across the bridges or ferries without such a pass, will be seized and turned over to the hospitals. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 1.  President Lincoln arrived at Harper's Ferry this morning for a brief visit.  Gen. Halleck sent to Gen. McClellan, urging him to cross the Potomac at once and give battle to the enemy.  Gen. Pleasanton crossed the Potomac on a reconnaissance, near Shepardstown.  He met the rebels and drove them to Martinsburgh.  Secretary Stanton has transferred the western gunboat fleet to the Navy department.  Gen. Buell's army has reportedly left Louisville, Kentucky.</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
