<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Monday Sept. 30.  Kansas is at this moment in most imminent danger of a second subjugation by the ProSlavery rebel-ruffians of Missouri and of the Southwest. Its fate may be said to hang upon the issue of the impending battle at Lexington, but a few miles from its eastern border. If we suffer another defeat there, Kansas falls. No wonder the settlers of that young and free, but thrice-desolated State, are preparing for defence, for the time is short. It is now known that it has all along been BEN MCCULLOCH's scheme to subjugate Kansas first. that once accomplished, he could then make Kansas the base of operations against the loyal citizens of North Missouri.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sunday, Sept. 29, 1861.  A distinguished gentleman in North Carolina has conveyed a verbal message in this city, to the effect that the great body of the people in the western half of the State, after having had six months' experience of secession, are more than ever attached to the Union. Prior to the experiment, there was some difference of opinion. but now there is none, except in two or three of the counties bordering on South Carolina, where the heresy has been nourished for thirty years past by certain politicians of the Calhoun stamp.  However, North Carolina Unionists need communication with the Government through East Tennessee. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday, Sept. 28. Munson's Hill was evacuated by the rebels this morning. About 10 o'clock our pickets reported to Gen. RICHARDSON that the rebel pickets had been drawn in, and subsequent observation confirmed the report. Information of this fact was telegraphed this afternoon to Gen. MCCLELLAN, who at once crossed the ferry at Georgetown with his Staff, and rode to Bailey's Cross Roads They then followed the course of the railroad to Upton House and Hill. They saw only half-a-dozen horsemen on Munson's Hill. Gen. WADSWORTH moved to the right and front with a body of skirmishers without encountering any of the enemy. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sept. 27.  Another important reconnoissance took place yesterday across the Potomac. In the morning, at 8 o'clock, 5,000 infantry, three companies of cavalry and three batteries, left Chain Bridge for Lewinsville. About 2 o'clock, a large party of rebels, consisting of about five regiments of infantry, a regiment of cavalry and six pieces of artillery, approached from the direction of Falls Church. They opened on our men with their battery, and their firing was immediately responded to by Captains GRIFFIN's and MOTT's guns. Thirty shots, both of shell and solid, were fired from our batteries, and the enemy immediately retired to Falls Church.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Thursday Sept. 26.  The Fall of Lexington, MO.  All accounts agree that the loss of the rebels, in killed and wounded, was from 900 to 1,200.   A leading rebel surgeon conceded their loss to be 1,130. Our men lost one hundred and thirty killed and wounded. Four hundred of Col. MARSHALL's horses were killed, it being impossible to shelter them from the cannon of the enemy. After the surrender of Lexington many of our men killed their horses, to prevent them from falling into the hands of the enemy. A large sum of money, one million five hundred thousand dollars, was secured by Gen. PRICE, after being buried by Col. MULLIGAN in the camp ground, to preserve it. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 25.  Report received that Romney, West Virginia, is now occupied by national troops.  Report from CLARKSBURG, WEST VIRGINIA.  The telegraph operator at Clarksburgh, for an unknown purpose-- unless it was to convey an impression that he was extremely attentive to his business -- changed the date and locality of a report on the battle, and made some other unwarranted alterations.  BUFFALO, Wednesday, Sept. 25 -- P.M. FLOUR quiet. WHEAT buoyant, after the receipt of the New-York market report, and prices better. Sales of 14,000 bushels Red Winter Western,  SX 1 02. 19,500 bushels Red Winter Western,  SX 1 62 1E2.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>KANSAS CITY, Thursday, Sept. 19. One thousand five hundred men, under Col. SMITH, overtook 600 as they were crossing the river at Blue Mills landing, on the 17th, and completely routed them, killing from 150 to 200, and taking 12 prisoners. The National loss is 50 killed and 25 wounded. Advices received by a private letter from Lexington to-day say that Gen. PRICE attacked the Nationals at 10 o'clock yesterday morning, with a force of 30,000. The National force was estimated at from 3,000 to 4,000. The Nationals fought them two hours, when the rebels drove them back into their intrenchments, carrying everything before them. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Sunday, Sept. 22. An office has been opened by the American Telegraph Company at Perryville, Md.  JEFFERSON CITY, MO, Friday, Sept. 20. A special dispatch to the St. Louis Democrat says: Gen. LANE is reported to have made a junction with he forces at Lexington, with 4,000 men. Reinforcements from St. Joseph have reached that place. Lexington is now considered safe. Gen. PRICE will undoubtedly be surrounded and cut off. It is feared that the reinforcements sent from here have not yet reached Lexington. Heavy batteries are planted at Glascon by the rebels, and our troops will have to disembark below the town and attack them in the rear. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OUTER STATION PACIFIC TELEGRAPH COMPANY, 170 Miles West of FORT KEARNEY, Friday, Sept. 20.  SAN FRANCISCO, Thursday, Sept. 12, Via DIAMOND SPRINGS, 225 miles east of Fort Churchill by Telegraph. Through the blunder by the Postmasters either at New-York or St. Louis or St. Joseph, all letters addressed to St. Joseph, thence to be dispatched for California by the Pony Express, have recently been put in the Overland Mail, and do not reach their destination till nearly a week after the Pony Express ought to have delivered them. The business community is much disaffected. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OUTER STATION PACIFIC TELEGRAPH COMPANY, 170 Miles West of FORT KEARNEY, Friday, Sept. 20.  The Pony Express, from San Francisco, with dates to the 11th inst., passed here to-night, with the following news for the Associated Press: SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Sept. 11. The following named ships have recently obtained charters from this port: Ship Indiana, load of spars, Puget Sound, for Spain. Pocahontas, a load of spars, Vancouvers, for London. Noonday, load of grain for London.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SAINT LOUIS, September 20.  Col. James Mulligan of the 23rd Illinois V.I.R. has surrendered at Lexington.  The combined casualties are reported to be 64 dead and 192 wounded. Pro-Confederate Missouri State Guard Maj. Gen. Sterling Price was so impressed by Mulligan's demeanor and conduct during and after the battle that he offered him his own horse and buggy, and ordered him safely escorted to Union lines.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Thursday, Sept. 19 -- Noon. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT in fair demand and market without important change. sales 6,000 bushels Chicago Spring, at 92 1E2.. 6,000 bushels do. at 93c., 6,500 bushels Red Winter at  SX 1 04. 18,000 bushels Red Winter and Chicago Spring on private terms. CORN dull and no sales. Oats steady. sales 6,000 bushels, at 25c. WHISKY firm. 220 bbls. at 16 1E2c. -- it is now held at 17c. Imports -- 1,300 bbls. Flour. 88,000 bushels Wheat, 255,000 bushels Corn. 1,000 bushels, Rye. Exports -- 19,000 bushels Wheat, 93,000 bushels Corn, and 7,000 bushels Oats</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Monday, Sept. 16, 1861 -- 6 P.M. NAVAL STORES -- The principal inquiry has been for common Resin, which is firm at  SX 4 TO  SX 4 12 1E2 310 lbs., with sales of 1,250 bbls., reported. Quotations for other articles are nominally unaltered. OILS -- A fair demand prevails for Crude Whale at from 41c. TO 45c., and Crude Sperm at  SX 1 20 TO  SX 1 25 per gallon. Linseed is dull at 59c. TO 60c. per gallon. Other descriptions remain as last noticed. PROVISIONS -- Pork is more active, and Mess is dearer, and advancing. sales 2,000 bbls., in lots, at  SX 14 TO  SX 14 50, closing at  SX 14 50 for Mess,  SX 13 50 for Soft Mess, and  SX 9 62 1E2 TO  SX 10 for Prime, bbl. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTONG, Sept. 17.  Yesterday evening, when BASIL HALL's and half a dozen other houses in the vicinity were burned by the rebels, MINER's was spared. This morning MINER, his wife, mother, three daughters and six negroes, were arrested by our troops and brought to the city. MINER professed the utmost loyalty, denying the allegations, and announcing his willingness to take the oath of allegiance. This was administered, and he was released upon his parole that he would not attempt to leave Washington without permission. A Methodist minister named COX, who was arrested at MINER's house, objected to taking the oath, and he was committed to jail. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 16 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 16.  Reports received that members of the Maryland regiment have been arrested in large number.  The telegraph wires were extended to-day from the War Department to Gen. MCCLELLAN's residence. This places him in telegraphic communication with all the brigades around the City. During several days past, our pickets stationed in the vicinity of Ball's Cross Roads have suffered much from shots fired by concealed rebels, and who seemed to be fully informed of the situation of our men. The belief prevailed in our camps that this information was furnished by a family named MINER, whose house was situated near our outposts.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday, Sept. 14. There was nothing unusual over the river to-day, and all is quiet, notwithstanding the predictions of the sensation papers. The rebels who moved in force from Fairfax Court-house fell back again, after burning a few houses, and doing a little extra foraging. It is presumed that the movement was a counterpart of that made by the Union troops on Wednesday last. Certain it is, that the rebels to-day manifest no more purpose to attack our lines than they did two weeks ago. The letter commanding Gen. FREMONT to modify his proclamation relating to the emancipation of Slaves, is published here to-day, by order of the President.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Sept. 14.  Secretary WELLES visited all of the private ship-yards in the vicinity of New-York where vessels are in the course of construction for the Government. He will no doubt also visit all the Navy-yards in the State. The purchased steamer Mercury, now fitted out as a gun-boat, arrived at the Brooklyn Navy-yard to receive her armament and stores and be put into commission. The Satellite and General Putnam sailed at 12 o'clock and the Valley City at 1 o'clock yesterday for Washington. After completing their crews they will join the Chesapeake flotilla as already announced.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CLARKSBURGH, Va., Friday, Sept. 13. The rebels commenced an advance on both pikes yesterday morning, towards Elk Water and Cheat Mountain Summit. They succeeded in surrounding the fort on the summit, and cut the telegraph wire. They continued to advance on Elk Water until within two miles of our troops, when a few shells from Loomis' Battery dispersed them. Skirmishing was kept up all night. This morning two regiments were sent to cut their way through to the summit and succeeded, the rebels retreating in all directions. Two rebel officers, spying round the camp at Elk Water, this morning, were surprised by our pickets and shot. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Thursday Sept. 12.  Hon. GIDEON WELLES, Secretary of the Navy, visited the Brooklyn Navy-yard to-day. He was received with the honors due to his position, viz.: a salute of seventeen guns. The guard was turned out and presented arms, both on his arrival and departure. The Honorable Secretary was accompanied by the Naval (vessel) Examining Board which included Chief-Engineer KIMBALL, of the Navy. The party was conducted round the Yard by Commodore BREESE and Capt. ALMEY, and spent two hours in examining with great attention the various works now going on, particularly the gun-boats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FRANKFORT, KENTUCKY, September 11.  Today the state legislature passed a resolution ordering rebel troops to leave the state.  WASHINGTON, September 11.  President Lincoln, in a letter to Gen. Fremont, to-day directed Fremont to modify the confiscation clause in Fremont's August 30 proclamation that confiscates the slaves of rebels.  OSWEGO, Wednesday, Sept. 11 -- P.M. FLOUR unchanged. sales at  SX 4 75 for fancy from Spring Wheat, Corn and other grains quiet. CANAL FREIGHTS dull. Flour 31c., Wheat 9c., and Corn 8c. to New-York. Lake Exports -- 36,000 bush. Wheat, 22,400 bush. Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 10.  Confederate Gen. John Floyd and his forces were defeated to-day near Gauley River.  PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, Sept. 10. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT firm. sales 3,000 bushels Red, at  SX 1 10 TO  SX 1 15. White,  SX 1 20 TO  SX 1 25. CORN declined. sales, 3,000 bushels, at 55c. TO 58 1E2c. WHISKY steady. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Monday, Sept. 9. FLOUR dull, and no demand for local consumption. Shipments cannot be made East, owing to the enormous amount of freight accumulated at all the railroad stations. Superfine offered at  SX 3 50 TO  SX 3 65. WHEAT is dull from the same cause. Red, 73c. TO 75c.. White, 83c. TO 85c. CORN dull at 27c. WHISKY dull at 14c. MESS PORK 13c. BACON dull. LARD firm at 8c. Money quiet. Exchange on New-York 1E4 cent. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 08 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Saturday, Sept. 7. FLOUR dull. WHEAT 1c. higher. No. 1 at 65c. TO 66c., in store. CORN declined 1E4c.. sales at 20c. for Mixed, in store. OATS quiet. Receipts -- 58,000 bbls. Flour, 85,000 bush. Wheat. 109,000 bush. Corn. Shipments -- 130,000 bush. Wheat, 254,000 bush. Corn. FREIGHTS 12 1E2c. on Wheat to Buffalo. Exchange unchanged. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Saturday, Sept. 7. FLOUR dull. WHEAT, but little doing. sales of car-loads red State, at  SX 1.6 bag white Michigan at  SX 1.27. RYE, in the street, at 65c. TO 66c. CORN dull, at 47c. for car-loads at East Albany, and 46c. for 3.70c. bushels Western mixed, afloats for cargoes afloat 45c. are offered, and some lots are going into store. OATS, 33c. TO 33 c. for State. WHISKY is held at 19c. Receipts by Central Railroad for New-York -- 4,536 bbls. Flour, 254 bbls. Highwines, 41 cases and 97 hhds. Tobacco, 70 bales Wool, 366 bags co.. for Boston and the East -- 50 bbls. Highwines, 2,367 bbls. Flour, 485 bags Seed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 6.  Confederate forces have advanced into Kentucky.  General Grant, with support of national troops, has taken possession of Paducah, Kentucky.  CHICAGO, Friday, Sept. 6. FLOUR dull. WHEAT declined 1E2c.. sales at 65 1E2c. TO 66c. for No. 1, and 61c. for No. 2, in store. CORN dull at 20 1E2c. for Mixed, in store. OATS firm. Receipts -- 7,000 bbls. Flour, 103,000 bushels Wheat, 163,000 bushels Corn. Shipments -- 5,500 bbls. Flour, 155,000 bushels Wheat, 300,000 bushels Corn. FREIGHTS declined 1E2c. Exchange on New-York 1E4 per cent. premium.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Thursday, Sept. 5. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT quiet and firm. sales 35,000 bushels Chicago Spring, at 80c. CORN dull. sales 13,000 bushels, at 35c. CANAL FREIGHTS better. Imports -- 8,000 bbls. Flour. 170,000 bushels Wheat, 205,000 bushels Corn, 46,000 bushels Oats. Canal Exports -- 2,000 bbls. Flour. 104,000 bushels Wheat, 12,000 bushels Corn, 4,500 bushels Rye. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, September 4.  A report was received to-day claiming that Jefferson Davis was killed.  It was later found to believe a false rumor.  ALBANY, Wednesday, Sept. 4. FLOUR dull. RYE 61c. TO 66c., with light receipts. CORN dull, offering light sales. 6,400 bushels Western mixed, 47c., at East Albany depot. OATS moderately active: sales, 5,000 bushels State, afloat, 32c.. 2,000 Canada, afloat, 32 1E2c. Received by Central Railroad -- for New-York: 49 hhds. tobacco, 4,548 bbls. Flour, 235 bales Wool, 1,936 bags Wheat, 115 bags Seed, 66 bbls. Highwines, 3,398 boxes Cheese, 193 bbls. Wheat. for Boston and the East: 1,830 bbls. Flour, 224 bales Wool.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Tuesday, Sept. 3 -- Noon. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT quiet. sales 6,000 bushels No. 2 Chicago Spring, at 78 1E2c. Corn firm. sales 33,000 bushels at 35 1E8c.. 13,000 bushels at 36c. FREIGHTS firm. 12c. TO 13c. on Corn and Wheat to New-York. Imports -- 10,000 bbls. Flour, 104,000 bush. Wheat, 116,000 bushels Corn, 3,000 bushels Rye Canal Exports -- 113,000 bushels Wheat, 83,000 bushels Corn, 9,000 bushels Oats. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Sept. 2. FLOUR dull. fresh ground,  SX 5. WHEAT buoyant. sales of 5,000 bushels Red,  SX 1 TO  SX 1 15. White  SX 1 22 TO  SX 1 25. CORN buoyant. sales of 2,000 bushels at 56c. PROVISIONS quiet. a contract of a quarter of millions of pounds of ribbed Sides with the Government has been made at 7 1E4c. WHISKY firm at 18c.  TO 18 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>News from California by the Pony Express, Aug. 30.  The steamer Cortes, from Portland, Oregon, with dates to the 16th, brings a report that all the Indian tribes east of the Cascade Mountains, including the Nez Perces, appeared to be preparing for war upon the whites. Miners were leaving the Nez Perces region, and a number of murders were reported. The Portland Times, commenting on the news, says that there are between 5,000 and 6,000 people in the Nez Perces section of the country, but they are poorly armed, and should the different tribes of Indians join together and make war upon the white, they will be obliged to leave the mining region for the Winter. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>News from California by the Pony Express. OUTER STATION, PACIFIC TELEGRAPH, 95 MILES WEST OF FORT KEARNEY, Aug. 30.  The Pony Express passed here at 5 A.M. SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Aug. 21. Arrivals, none. Sailed, 17th, ship Yeoman, for Sidney. 21st, steamer Uncle Sam, for Panama, carrying 193 passengers and  SX 1,100,000 specie for New-York, and  SX 138,000 for England.  The following are cabin passengers per Uncle Sam: Major Allen, U.S.A.. Major-Gen. Grier, U.S.A., and family, Capt. Gregg, U.S.A.. Capt. Myers, U.S.A.. Capt. Mason, U.S.A., andfamily. Capt. Hancock and family.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 30.  To-day, General Fremont issued a proclamation that confiscates the slaves of rebels.  BUFFALO, Friday, AUG. 30 -- P. M. FLOUR steady, and in moderate demand. WHEAT closed 2c. TO 3c. better for Red Winter. Sales 22,000 bush, Red Winter, 6,000 bush. White Winter.  SX 1 05. 6,000 bush. Chicago Spring at 77 1E2c.. 6,500 bush, do.,  SX 1 12 1E2. and 20,000 bush. Milwaukee Club on private terms. Corn steady, and in fair demand. sales 37,000 bush., at 25 1E2c. TO 26c. WHISEY held at 16 1E2c. CANAL FREIGHTS -- 12c. on Corn, and 13c. on Wheat to New-York. Imports-3,000 bbls. Flour, 73,000 hush. Wheat, 40,000 bush. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday, Aug. 29. There are rebel troops in considerable numbers a few. miles back of the Chain Bridge, on the Virginia side. They line the bank of the Potomac all the way up to the vicinity of Leesburgh. Our scouts report that there is a very large body of them at Leesburgh and its vicinity. It is believed here that they will attempt to cross the Potomac this week or not at all. Our forces are ready for them. The troops about here are in excellent condition. Only nineteen are reported on the sick list in RICHARDSON's Brigade. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 28.  To-day, reports are received that the Hatteras Inlet forts are now under the command of Commodore Stringham and Gen. Butler.  P.M. There are agitating reports of an attack of the rebels upon our lines, which have caused much excitement on the streets. But on careful examination, I have found them to be without foundation. Maj.-Gen. MCCLELLAN is on the Virginia side of the Potomac to-day. Mr. RUSSELL, of the London Times, was invited over, but no correspondent of an American newspaper was allowed to have a pass. 
? 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LEWENSVILLE Va., Tuesday, Aug. 27, 1861. The enemy has Occupied Bailey's Cross Roads in considerable force, and are intrenching, farmers are not allowed to come through to Washington now, and the boarders at Mr. BAILEY's have been scattered in consequence of the occupation by the secession force. Col. SHERMAN is in command of the enemy at Bailey's Cross Roads. Secessionists hereabouts profess to expect lively times soon in this neighborhood. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 24.  Reports received of a skirmish at Sommerville.  CHAIN BRIDGE, Tuesday, Aug. 27. Five of our men, while out scouting, about three miles above here, yesterday, were in a corn-field, and to their dismay discovered that about thirty  QN seceshcavalry were  QN circulating around the edges QN  of said field. Thinking the case was desperate, they fired into the largest group, and killed one, who was seen to fall, and seem to have wounded two others. They did not stop to investigrte, however, but scampered off in one direction, while the cavalry, just as much frightened, dashed off in the other. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORT KEARNEY, Sunday Aug. 25.  News from San Francisco.  Five companies, mostly infantry, were accepted today in this city. Military men, however, are ambitious to see active service against a civilized enemy rather than to roam over the plains. A guard of twenty-five U.S. Infantry, and a Lieutenant, went down in the last Panama steamer, to escort the treasure as far as Aspinwall. There is no State news of importance. GEORGE HUDSON, the San Francisco Justice of the Peace, who, in 1859, fined the proprietors of the Bulletin newspaper  SX 100 each for publishing the confession of Mrs. SICKLES, on the ground that it was not fit for publication.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 24.  The transmission of secession journals through the mails is now prohibited.  FORT KEARNEY, Saturday Aug. 24.  News from California by the Pony Express.  Yesterday was the first day that official advices were received from Washington, concerning who is to command the fifteen hundred troops called for from California and how they are to serve on the plains. They are to be organized agreeably at request of Mr. CAMERON, Sec. of War. The Governor has commissioned Col. CARLTON, of the United States Army, to be the chief in command, and Major J.R. WEST, of San Francisco, second in command, taking charge of the cavalry.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORT KEARNEY, Friday Aug. 23.  News from California by the Pony Express.. OUTER TELEGRAPH STATION, NINETY-FIVE MILES WEST OF FORT KEARNEY.  The Pony Express passed here at 10 o'clock this morning bringing the following intelligence from the Pacific Coast. SAN FRANCISCO, Friday, Aug. 16 -- P.M. Arrived 10th, ship Winged Racer, New-York. bark Therusia, Rio de Janeiro. Sailed 10th, ship Eureka, Melbourne. Decatur, Hong Kong. Harkaway, Melbourne. The market is slightly more active. Butter, 25c. TO  27 1E2c.. Candles. 19 1E2c.  TO 21 1E2c.. Crushed Sugar, 12 1E4c.  TO 13c.. Rio Coffee held at 19c.  TO 21c.. Whisky, 36c.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Thursday, Aug. 22. FLOUR dull and slightly declined. WHEAT 2c. TO 4c. lower. sales No. 1 at 63c. TO 65c.. No. 2, 60c. TO 61c. CORN, 1E2c. TO 1c. lower. sales of mixed, 22 1E2c. OATS easier at 15 3E4c. TO 16c. Receipts -- 4,800 bbls. Flour. 135,000 bush, Wheat. 180,000 bush. Corn, and 100,000 bush, Oats. Shipments -- 8,700 bush. Wheat. 110,000 bush. Corn. FREIGHTS easier, 12 1E2c. TO 14c. to Buffalo, Exchange unchanged.  OSWEGO, Thursday, Aug. 22. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT declining, with very little inquiry. The fresh break at Mud Lock, reported this morning, has a great influence in depressing the market. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Wednesday, Aug. 21. FLOUR steady and in moderate demand. WHEAT also in moderate demand. Market easier. Sales 15,000 bushels Red Winter at  SX 102. 13,000 bushels Chicago Spring at 88c.. 6,000 bushels Milwaukee Club at 91c. CORN lower. sales 35,000 bushels at 36c.. 8,000 bushels at 35 1E2c.. 7,000 bushels at 35c. Other grains quiet and no sales. CANAL FREIGHTS -- 10 1E2c. on Corn, 11 1E2c. on Wheat to New-York. Lake Imports -- 6,000 bbls. Flour, 348,000 bushels Wheat, 320,000 bushels Corn, 25,000 bushels Oats, 4,000 bushels Rye. Canal Exports -- 2,000 bbls. Flour, 70,000 bushels Wheat, 69,000 bushels Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Tuesday, Aug. 20. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT -- Red State,  SX 1 15 TO  SX 1 17. OATS steady at 32 1E2c. for Chicago, and 33c. for State, heated. sales 18,000 bushels. CORN -- Market closed easier. sales 10,000 bushels Western Mixed at 47c., and 6,500 bushels at 46c.. 2,000 do. at 47c., and 5,000 do., heated, 47c. WHISKY -- Sales 100 bbls. at 17 1E4c. Received by Central Railroad for New-York -- 181 bales Wool, 431 bbls. High Wines, 4,691 bbls. Flour, 64 hhds. Tobacco, 37 cases do. For Boston and the East -- 451 bbls. High Wines, 575 bales Wool, 3,371 bbls. Flour. Shipped by Tows to New-York, Aug. 19 --146,700 bushels Corn.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Monday, Aug. 19. New-York advices thoroughly depressed FLOUR, and Friday's advance was lost. Extra sold at  SX 3.75. market dall and unsettled. WHEAT 5c, lower, and unsettled. WHISKY steady, at 13 1E2c. PROVISIONS dull and unsettled. Mess Pork,  SX 14. Lard, 8 1E3c. Exchange on New-York, 1E4c.  BUFFALO, Monday, Aug. 19. FLOUR steady. WHEAT steady and in demand. sales 8,000 bushels Milwaukee Club, at 97c.. 6,000 bushels Chicago Spring, 96c.. 13,000 bushels red Winter,  SX 1 11 1E2.. 6,000 bushels do, at  SX 1 10. 3,000 bushels White Kentucky,  SX 1 15. CORN better and in fair demand. sales 20,000 bushels, at 37 1E2c.. 14,000 bushels at 38c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORT KEARNEY, Sunday, Aug. 18. The Pony Express passed here at 9 P.M., yesterday, from San Francisco, with dates to the 3d inst. for the Associated Press.  The Pony Express arrived at the outer telegraph station, last evening, with St. Louis dates of the 25th ult., bringing the first announcement of the disastrous defeat of the National forces near Manassas, the news occupying six columns of to-day's Bulletin and Alta. It has been published as fast as received, and is just completed. The effect casts a gloom over our loyal people, who realize more generally that we are engaged in a terrible war.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORT KEARNEY, Saturday Aug. 17.  Telegraph to California.  The eastern half has a Large number of men and teams engaged in hauling out poles and wire, and are putting forth their best efforts to complete their half as quickly as the western half. A work of this magnitude involves great exposure.  The operator travels with the workmen engaged east of Fort Churchill, and as fast as the line is put up he sets his instrument at the end and communicates with the office in San Francisco, so that almost every day he is further off and shortening the time of the Pony. He will reach the end of the wire in time to telegraph the news of the Pony due on Tuesday next. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 16.  President Lincoln has issued a proclamation declaring that a state of insurrection exists in Virginia, North Carolina, Tennesse, and Arkansas.  FORT KEARNEY, Aug. 16.  Telegraph to California.  Each month a day more will be gained, and if no accident happens to the teams employed in the work, the snow will not fall in the valleys before the western half of the Overland Line from San Francisco to Salt Lake will be in working order. On the other side the Eastern Company are pushing westward, and by the 1st of August the wire will be up to Julesturgh, which is 200 miles west of Fort Kearney, thus shortening the Pony time one day more.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORT KEARNEY, Thursday Aug. 15.  California telegraph line progress. Mr. JAMES STREET, the agent of the Company, at Salt Lake, is pushing forward this way, having some 250 miles of poles contracted for and which are now being cut and hauled westward from Salt Lake. The wire and insulators for that end of the line were purchased in the East, and are on the way out to Salt Lake, so as to be in readiness when the poles are set up, to put the line in working order. In a few days messages can be sent to overtake the Pony two days after it has left San Francisco, or received here two days before the arrival of the Pony in town. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Wednesday, Aug. 14. The I. and M. Telegraph Company's lines, connecting Keokuk, Montrose and Fort Mades in Iowa direct with Chicago and the East, was completed to-day.   FORT KEARNEY, Aug. 14.  Pprogress of the telegraph wires from the Alta, California, July 17. On Wednesday last the State Telegraph Company dispatched one of their best operators, Mr. JOLA YONTZ, to the end of the telegraph line now building east towards Salt Lake, to receive and transmit the Pony news from the outer station. The Company now has nearly fifty wagons engaged in transporting poles and wire out to and beyond the outer station.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday Aug. 13.  A cool and orderly return of telegraphic operator Mr. William C. Hall, of the Army Telegraph Corps, stationed at  Centreville during the late great battle, who kept up constant communication with the War Department at Washington. He remained at his post after the fight commenced, and only left it when ordered to do so by Gen. SCOTT. There was no telegraphic communication with Centreville at the time of the battle. The lines were not extended beyond Fairfax Courthouse. We know this to be so, because we brought dispatches from the Headquarters of the Army to Fairfax, to be transmitted to Gen. SCOTT the night after the battle. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Aug. 12.  Former U. S. minister to France, the Hon. C.J. Faulkner, was arrested.  SAN FRANCISCO, Tuesday, Aug. 6.  By way of Los Angeles later news of the party of Secessionists, including Gen. JOHNSON, is received. They were last heard of in Tuson, in Arizona, numbering about fifty. Several had joined the party after leaving Los Angeles, among whom were Major ARMSTEAD, Lieut. HARDCASTLE, of the Sixth Infantry, United States Army.  Some of the large ranch owners in the southern counties of the State have commenced slaughtering cattle for their hides and tallow only, there being no farming work for beef cattle. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORT KEARNEY, Tuesday, Aug. 6.   The price of passage from Sacramento to St. Joseph has been fixed at  SX 150. Passengers who come through in the mail stages seem to regard the trip as one of no great hardship, although they are compelled to ride continually night and day for eighteen days. Since the last dispatch to the Associated Press a new telegraph station has been opened 25 miles further east, with the prospect of another like extension before another Pony Express arrives there. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, Saturday Aug. 10.  To-day there was a battle at Wilson's Creek, just outside Springfield.  General Lyon was mortally wounded.  FORT KEARNEY, Tuesday, Aug. 6. The Pony Express passed this point at 3 this afternoon, with San Francisco dates of July 27.  The Pony Express arrived yesterday, with Eastern dates to the 18th inst., and with accounts of Gen. MCCLELLAN's success in Western Virginia, and the continued retreating of the rebels toward the interior of Virginia. The news is greatly inspiring the Union men. The Overland Mail continues to arrive regularly. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORTRESS MONROE, Friday, Aug. 9  The fire raged all night. The greater part or the Confederates withdrew towards morning, and at noon to-day, but seven or eight buildings were left standing.  The destruction of the town was a wanton act of cruelty to the resident Unionists, and moreover entirely useless, as Gen. BUTLER intends to Winter his army many miles beyond Hampton. An attempt will be made to fasten the act on the General, but after 10 o'clock on Wednesday there was not a National soldier in Hampton.  A flag of truce is just in from Norfolk.  Some ten days ago a battalion came down to the outskirts of Hampton and carried away a hundred and eighty negroes.  Provisions are abundant at Yorktown, and most of the regiments are receiving new uniforms for the Winter campaign.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORTRESS MONROE, Thursday, Aug. 8.  Hampton has been burnt. Scouts and fugitives, yesterday morning, brought word of the approach of a large Confederate force from Yorktown. These rumors were confirmed at 5 P.M., by an intelligent deserter from the rebels, named E.A. MAHEW, a native of Maine, but a resident of Georgia until impressed into the service, who has furnished an account of the expedition. Mr. MAHEW has been stationed at Yorktown since the 1st of June. Friday last Col. (now Gen.) MAGRUDER left Yorktown with a force of 7,000 men, including 200 cavalry and eight pieces of artillery, viz., three Parrott guns, four howitzers and one rifled cannon. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORTRESS MONROE, Wednesday, Aug. 7. Gen. BUTLER at once repaired to this end of Hampton Bridge, where he remained until 11 o'clock. Col. WEBER erected a barricade near the Hampton end of the bridge, and placed a strong guard at various points this side of the creek.  Just past midnight, Gen. MAGRUDER, with about 500 Confederates entered the town, and immediately fired the buildings with torches. A greater part of the five hundred houses were built of wood, and no rain having fallen lately, the strong south wind soon produced a terrible conflagration.   Several of the whites and also of the negroes were hurried away to be pressed into the Confederate service.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Aug. 6. FLOUR dull. WHEAT active. White,  SX 1 20. Red,  SX 1 10 TO  SX 1 13. CORN -- Yellow, 52c. TO 53c. Mess Ponk,  SX 16 50. LARD steady at 10c. TO 10 1E2c. WHISKY 20c. PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, Aug. 6. BREADSTUFFS dull. WHEAT firm. White  SX 1 20. Red  SX 1 10 TO  SX 1 13. CORN firm. Yellow, 50c. TO 52 1E2c. WHISKY firm and scarce. Small sales at 19 5E8c. TO 20c. PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, Aug. 6. Stocks dull. Pennsylvania State Fives, 78, Reading Railroad, 18 1E4. Morris Canal, 35. Long Island Railroad, --. Pennsylvania Railroad, 38 1E2. ALBANY, Tuesday, Aug. 6. FLOUR in fair demand. Not much doing. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Monday, Aug. 5.  THE SOUTHERN PRESS ON THE BATTLE.  The Charleston Mercury says: The great news from Virginia, with its incidental calamities, kept our community throughout yesterday in a state of feverish excitement and anxiety. So great was the demand for the Mercury, which was the only morning paper that published the full telegraphic account of the action, that we were obliged to run our press until late in the forenoon in order to supply the public thirst for the news.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Sunday, Aug. 4. After the close of yesterday's report, 13,000 bushels Western mixed were sold at 41 1E2c. TO 42c.. holders were asking 43c., but the demand was slack.  WHISKY -- no sales. Receipts by Central Railroad for New-York -- 150 bbls. Highwines, 10 sacks Wool, 1,400 bbls. Flour, 480 boxes Cheese, 33 hhds. Tobacco. for Boston, 470 bbls. Flour, 130 sacks Wool. Shipped by tows to New-York 2d -- 95,200 bushels Corn, 50,400 bushels Wheat, 23,300 bushels Oats, 18,800 bushels feed. NEWPORT, Aug. -- 4. The sloop Tawtameo, from New-London, with a cargo of oil, bound to Nantucket, was towed in here dismasted.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Aug. 3. FLOUR dull. WHEAT -- Declining tendency. white,  SX 1 15 SX 1 19. Red,  SX 1 08 TO  SX 1 12. CORN unchanged. old Yellow, 52c. TO 53c. WHISKY firm and scarce at 20c.  NEW YORK, Aug. 3.  FLOUR dull. WHEAT quiet and holders firmer. sales yesterday afternoon of 6,000 bushels Milwaukee Club, at 78c.. 8,000 bushels do., at 80c.. 14,000 bushels do., at 82c.. 10,400 bushels Waukeyon, at 81c.. to-day, 18,000 bushels Milwaukee on private terms. CORN better and in good demand. sales yesterday afternoon, 31,000 bushels, at 31 1E2c.. this morning, 13,000 bushels, at 31 1E2c.. 43,000 bushels, at 32c. WHISKY nominal at 15 1E2c.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OSWEGO, Friday, August 2. FLOUR steady, and demand moderate. WHEAT dull. Holders are compelled to submit to a decline in order to effect sales. Nothing done to-day. sales last night of 3,000 bushels Winter Red Western, at  SX 1 05, and 3,000 bushels Chicago Spring on private terms. CORN scarce and nominally unchanged. CANAL FREIGHTS steady, at 28c. on Flour, 7c. on Corn to New-York. Lake Imports unimportant. Canal Exports -- 2,194 bbls. Flour, 16,000 bushels Wheat, 25,300 bushels Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Thursday, August 1. FLOUR steady, and in fair demand. WHEAT quiet. sales, 5,000 bbls. Milwaukie Club at 83c. CORN steady, and in fair demand. sales, 55,000 bushels at 31 1E2c. OATS, lower. sales, 7,000 bushels at 23c. WHISKY better. sales, 320 bbls. at 15 1E2c. CANAL FREIGHTS -- firm, at 10 1E2c. on Corn, and 11 1E2c. on Wheat, to New-York. Lake Imports -- 5,000 bbls. Flour. 60,000 bushels Wheat. 347,000 bushels Corn. Canal Exports -- 3,00 bbls. Flour. 44,000 bushels Wheat. 107,000 bushels Corn. 9,000 bushels Oats. 3,000 bushels Barley.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Wednesday, July 31. FLOUR in moderate demand. Small parcel White Michigan WHEAT sold at  SX 1.25. RYE -- Sales 1,500 bushels at 60c. OATS lower. gates are all Chicago, 1,300 bushels at 29 1E2c. TO 30c. CORN dull and unchanged, 41 1E2c. for Western Mixed, afloat and in car loads. sales 4,200 bushels. WHISKY no sales. Received by Central Railroad for New-York -- 20,500 bbls. Flour. 98 bales Wool. 20 hhds. Tobacco. 450 bbls. Highwines. 15 bales Hops. For Boston and the East -- 2,207 bbls. Flour.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Tuesday, July 30 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT closed a shade easier. sales 30,000 bushels. CORN dull. sales 30,000 bushels, at 31c. CANAL FREIGHTS better -- 10 1E2c. on Corn, and 11 1E2c. on Wheat to New-York. Imports to-day -- 4,000 bbls. Flour, 125,000 bushels Wheat, 245,000 bushels Corn, 28,000 bushels Oats. Exports -- 28,000 bushels Wheat, 182,000 bushels Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, July 29 -- Arr. brigs Nantucket, St. Thomas. Eastern Star, Trapani. Boston, Halifax. schr. Carman. Turka Island. PORTLAND, July 9. -- The ship Wm: Witherbee, of Castine, arrived at this port this morning, with loss of all topmasts and rigging, 12 ds. out from Boston for London.  PHILADELPHIA, Monday, July 29. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT unchanged.  SX 1 17 TO  SX 1 20 for White, and  SX 1 12 TO  SX 1 13 for Red. CORN firm at 52c. TO 53c. WHISKY steady at 16 1E2c. TO 17c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 28.  Reports received that forces under Gen. Banks, at Harper's Ferry, have withdrawn to the Maryland side of the Potomac.  OSWEGO, Saturday, July 27. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT scarce and market quiet. CORN 1E2c. lower. Sales, 6,600 bush. Illinois at 34 1E2c. RYE in demand. Sales, 4,000 bush. Canadian at 50c. Other grains quiet. CANAL FREIGHTS steady. Flour, 28c.. Wheat, 8c.. Corn, 7c. to New-York, Lake Imports 35,000 bush. Wheat, 44,800 bush. Corn, Canal Exports 1,000 bbls. Flour. 15,400 bushels Wheat. 61,000 bushels Corn. 10,600 bushels Rye. CINCINNATI, Saturday, July 27. FLOUR dull, and hardly any demand. WHISKY at 13 1E2c., with small sales. BACON -- shoulders at 5c.. no inquiry for other provisions. EXCHANGE on New-York firmer at 3E8 cent. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 27.  The 69th Regiment along with some others has returned from Washington.  Shipped, by tows to New-York, July 27: 53,800 bush. Corn, 9,000 bush. Rye. 33,400 bush. Wheat, 20,000 bush. Oats, 13,000 bush. Feed.  ALBANY, Saturday, July 27. FLOUR very dull. No sales of WHEAT, CORN casier and salable at 40 c. TO 41c. for Western mixed afloat. sales 10,200 bush. OATS dull and lower. sales 10,000 bush. Chicago at 31c. WOOL -- the low medium grades are in good demand. sales 8,100 lbs. No. 1 pulled, and 3,000 lbs. coarse fleeces, both on private terms. Received by Central Railroad, for New-York, 49 bales Wool, 1,269 bbls. Flour, 100 bbls. Highwines. For Boston, 1,633 bbls. Flour, 155 bales Wool, </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Friday, July 26 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT quiet. parties apart and no sales. CORN steady, demand fair. sales 57,000 bushels at 31 1E2c. TO 32c., mostly at the inside figure. Other grains quiet and no sales. WHISKY steady. sales 100 bbls. at 14 1E2c. Conal Freights higher. 10 1E2c.on Corn, 11 1E2c. on Wheat to New-York. Imports -- 8,800 bbls. Flour. 15,000 bushels Wheat. 117,000 bush. Corn, Canal Exports -- 500 bbls. Flour. 33,000 bushels Wheat. 137,000 bushels Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 25.  Gov. Morgan today called for 25,000 more troops from the State of New York.  PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, July 25. FLOUR, firm and quiet. Superfine  SX 4 TO  SX 4 50. Family  SX 5 TO  SX 5 50. Fancy,  SX 6 50. WHEAT less active, Red,  SX 1 13  TO  SX 1 15. White,  SX 1 18 TO  SX 1 22. CORN, Prime Yellow in demand at 53c. WHISKY, dull at 16c.  TO 16 1E2c. MINIATURE ALMANAC -- THIS DAY. Sun rises.... 4 51 Sun sets.... 7 21 Moon rises... 9 43 HIGH WATER -- THIS DAY. Sandy Hook.11 02 Gov. Island. 11 51 Hell Gate... 1 13 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, July 24. FLOUR quiet. sales 1,500 bbls. Extra Family, at  SX 6 TO  SX 6 25. WHEAT in demand. sales 4,000 bushels Red, at  SX 1 15. White, at  SX 1 20, in store. WHISKY, 16 1E2 c.  BUFFALO, Wednesday, July 24 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR quiet. WHEAT dull and no sales. CORN lower. sales 70,000 bushels since yesterday. No. 1 at 31c. Other grains quiet and no sales. WHISKY nominal at 14c. TO 14 1E2c. CANAL FREIGHTS lower -- 10c. on Corn, 11c. on Wheat to New York. Imports -- 3,000 bbls. Flour, 2,000 bushels Wheat, 191,000 bushels Corn, 11,000 bushels Barley. Exports -- 1,600 bbls. Flour, 75,000 bushels Wheat, 94,000 bushels Corn.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OSWEGO, Tuesday, July 23. FLOUR steady at  SX 4 50 for fancy. WHEAT scarce and market firm. no sales. CORN steady. sales last night, 12,000 bush. Illinois at 34c. CANAL FREIGHTS steady. Flour, 28c.. Wheat, 8c.. Corn, 7c. to New-York. Lake Imports 65,00 bush. Corn. Canal Exports 1,044 bbls. Flour. 15,100 bushels Wheat. 60,800 bushels Corn. 62,00 bushels Rye.  CHICAGO, Tuesday, July 23. FLOUR declined 5c. TO 10c. WHEAT 2c. lower. sales 678 bush. No. 1, 62 1E4, No. 3 in store. CORN declined 1c.. sales at 23c. mixed in store. OATS steady. Receipts, 3,200 bbls. Flour, 69,000 bush. Wheat, 297,000 bush. Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Monday, July 22. FLOUR dull. No sales WHEAT. OATS dull. a small lot of stall sold at 32c., and 5,000 bush. do. damaged 28c. CORN in fair demand and steady. receipts large. sales 6,000 bush. at 40c. for damaged, 42c. for sound do. afloat. WHISKY -- sales, 60 bbls., at 16c. Received by Central Railroad, for New-York, 3,282 bbls. Flour, 150 bags Wheat, 158 cases and 16 hhds. Tobacco, 373 bbls. Highwines, 47 sacks Wool. for Boston and the East -- 150 bags Wheat, 671 bbls Flour, 130 sacks Wool.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 21.  A battle commenced today at Bull Run.  Gen. Geo. McClellan has arrived in Washington to take command of the Army of the Potomac.  OSWEGO, Saturday, July 20. FLOUR steady, at  SX 4 50 for Fancy. WHEAT scarce and firm. sales, 2,000 bushels No. 1, Milwaukee Club, on private terms. CORN firm and scarce. sales, 12,100 bushels Illinois at 36c. Other grains quiet. CANAL FREIGHTS unchanged, on Flour, 28c.. Wheat, 8c., Corn, 7 1E2c., to New-York. Imports -- 40,000 bushels Corn. 15,000 bushels Barley. 3,900 bushels Rye. Exports -- 1,664 barrels Flour. 125 bushels Wheat. 35,000 bushels Corn. Shipped to Montreal, 23,000 bu. Wheat.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, July 20. FLOUR firmer and in better demand. superand unchanged. extra to extra family,  SX 4 75 TO  SX 5 50. WHEAT steady. sales 7,000 bushels white,  SX 1 15. CORN -- Prime Yellow scarce at 52c. TO  53c. WHISKEY firm and unchanged. Passengers Arrived. In bark Ocean Home, from Matanzas -- J.W. Hayes lady and son. Mr. Williams, Mr. Parker, Mr. Hanson. MINIATURE ALMANAC -- THIS DAY. Sun rises....4 45 Sun sets.... 7 27 Moon sets.... 3 02 HIGH WATER -- THIS DAY. Sandy Hook. 6 10 Gov. Island. 6 59 Hell Gate.... 8-27 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Friday, June 19. FLOUR -- Good demand at improving rates. Common and medium brands 10c. better. extra firm .sales 1,400 bbls. CORN MEAL, 7s. 6d. TO 8s. 6d. WHEAT dull. sales of Red State,  SX 1 02. CORN very dull none here afloat, but boats are arriving. sales 2,000 bushels in lots at 42 1E2c.. RYE 64c., delivered. Received by Central Railroad for New-York -- 225 bbls. Meal. 1,553 do. Flour. 110 bbls. Highwines. 4 cases Tobacco, 453 sacks Wheat. 67 bales Wool. 921 boxes Cheese. For Boston and the East -- 121 bales Wool. 12 bbls. Beef. 659 bbls. Flour. 143 sacks Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Thursday, July 18. FLOUR in active demand at improving rates. sales 1,600 bbls. WHEAT, in lots,  SX 1.29 TO  SX 1.30 for White Michigan, CORN held at higher rates. sales 20,000 bush., afloat and to arrive. Western Mixed at 42c. OATS dull. damaged Canada East at 28c. . prime State wanted. WHISKY -- Sales of 196 bbls. at 16c. TO 16 1E4c. Received by Central Railroad for New-York: 155 cases and 115 hhds. Tobacco, 4,032 bbls. Flour, 331 bbls. High Wines, 49 bales Wool, 168 bags and 27 bbls. Wheat. for Boston and East: 73 bbls. Whisky, 951 bbls. Flour, 48 bales Wool. Shipped by tows to New-York on the 17th: 27,000 bush. Corn, 2,800 bush. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, July 17. FLOUR unchnged, at  SX 4 TO  SX 4 25 for Superfine and Extra.  SX 4 50 TO  SX 4 75 for Western Superfine. WHEAT steady. sales 4,000 bush. Red at  SX 1 12. 4,000 bush. Old Kentucky White, at  SX 1 20. CORN steady. sales 2,000 bush Yellow, at 52c. WHISKY firm, at 16c. TO 16 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 16.  Today's news is that the Army of the Potomac is advancing.  BUFFALO, Tuesday, July 16 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR, steady. WHEAT market better. sales 3,000 bush. No. 1 Milwaukee Club, at 80c.. 12,000 bush. Northwestern Club, at 80c.. 6,300 bush. Kenosha Club, 82c.. 2,000 bush. White Canada,  SX 1 05. CORN dull but unchanged. sales 40,000 bush., most of which was sold yesterday afternoon, at 32c. OATS firm. sales, 32,000 bushels, at 22c. TO 22 1E2c. RYE lower. sales, 5,000 bush. at 37c. CANAL FREIGHTS dull, at 10 1E2c. on Corn, 11 1E2c. on Wheat to New-York, Imports -- 7,000 bbls. Flour, 40,000 bush. Wheat, 42,000 bush. Corn, 2,000 bush. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 15.  Commercial news by the Hibernia from England.  LIVERPOOL, Friday, July 5. COTTON. -- Sales of the week, 158,600 bales, including 49,000 to speculators, and 25,000 to exporters. The market is active in both the trade and speculative departments, and the American advices per steamer Australasian can-ed an advance of 1E4d. lb. Sales on Friday 15,000 bales, including 6,000 bales to speculators and exporters, the market closing firm at the following quotations: Orleans fair 8 3E4d. Middling 8d. Upland fair 8 1E2d. Mobile fair 8 1E2d.  The total stock in port is estimated at 1,100,000 bales, of which 838,000 are of American descriptions. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Thursday, July 11. FLOUR steady. Little doing in Grain. WHEAT -- 4,000 bushels Red Winter State,  SX 1 06, and 1,000 bush. White Michigan at  SX 1 30. CORN is not pressed on the market. Holders at opening, were asking yesterday's figures, but at close, on account of break in canal, higher rates were paid. Cargoes of sound afloat sold at 41c. early in the day, and at the close the same price was paid for inferior parcels. Sales 30,000 bushels at 41c. for ordinary and inferior. OATS -- No sales. WHISKY, 15c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 13.  Today an engagement ensued at Corrick's Ford, Virginia.  Rebel Gen. Garnett was defeated and killed.  BUFFALO, Saturday, July 13. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT in better demand. sales moderate. Sales 6,000 bushels Kenosha Club at 78c.. 6,000 bushels No. 1 Chicago Spring at 73c., and 6,000 bushels Red Winter at 91c. CORN -- Holders asking an advance lc.. market quiet. sales 20,000 bushels at 32 1E2c. WHISKY steady at 14c.. sales 50 bbls. CANAL FREIGHTS unchanged. Imports to-day -- 62,000 bbls. Flour, 64,000 bushels Wheat, 141,000 bushels Corn, 30,000 bushels Oats, 16,000 bushels Barley. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Friday, July 12.  FLOUR dull and irregular. sales 1,500 bbls. family at  SX 5  TO  SX 5 75. WHAT lower. red,  SX 1 05 TO   SX 1 12. white,  SX 1 20  TO  SX 1 25. CORN scarce. sales 3,000 bushels mixed at 49c.  TO 49 1E2 WHISKY dull at 16c.  TO 16 1E2c.  BUFFALO, Friday July 12.-1 P.M. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT firmer -- sales last night 6,000 bushels Milwaukee Club at 72c.. 7,000 bushels Prime No. 1 Chicago Spring at 73c., and 6,900 bushels Kenosha Club at 75c. CORN dull -- sales 30,000 bushels at 30 1E2c.  TO 31c. CANAL FREIGHTS firm. Imports -- 5,000 bbls. Flour, no Wheat. 5,000 bushels Corn.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 11.  Rebel Col. Peagram was defeated today by Gen. McClellan's forces at Rich Mountain, Virginia.  The entire rebel force has surrendered.  The following is the order of Gen. SCOTT, referred to yesterday:  QN Henceforward the telegraph will convey no dispatches concerning the operations of the army not permitted by the Commanding-General. WINFIELD SCOTT. QN   QN DEPARTMENT OF WAR, July 8, 1861. The above order is confirmed. SIMON CAMERON, Secretary of War. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Wednesday, July 10. FLOUR firmer. WHEAT firm and advanced 2c. TO 3c.. sales at 62c. TO 62 3E4c. for No. 1 in store, and 58c. TO 59c. for No. 2 in store. CORN 1E2c. better. OATS firm. Receipts -- 4,000 bbls. Flour, 50,000 bushels Wheat, 103,000 bushels Corn. Shipments -- 5,000 bbls. Flour, 54,000 bushels Wheat, 290,000 bushels Corn. FREIGHTS dull. 5 3E4c. on Corn to Buffalo. EXCHANGE on New-York 1E2 cent. discount for gold. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Tuesday, July 9. Recent reports of the tornado near Freeport, Illinois, add nothing in relation to the damages done by the tornado that was telegraphed last night. The loss at Rockford is estimated at  SX 55,000. Considerable damage was also done to the growing crops in the vicinity, and grain of all kinds was leveled to the earth. We have heard of no lives being lost.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Saturday July 6 -- 6 P.M. FLOUR dull. WHEAT -- no sales. CORN lower. sales, 20,000 bush., partly on private terms, and the balance at 41 1E2 c. afloat, and in car lots at 42c. TO 43c. OATS steady, at 27 1E4c. TO 27 1E8c. for Western.. no sales of State. WHISKY -- Sales 180 bbls. at 15 1E4c. Received by Central Railroad for Boston -- 817 bbls. Flour, 50 bbls. Whisky. For New-York -- 2,116 bbls. Flour, 100 bbls. Wheat, 150 bbls. Whisky, 20 cases and 86 hhds. Tobacco. Shipped by tows to New-York July 5 -- 3,350 bushels Corn, 6,000 bush. Rye, 108,900 bushels Wheat, 28,006 bushels Oats. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Saturday, July 6. FLOUR dull and heavy. WHEAT firm and c. higher. sales at 58c. TO 59c., for No. 1, and 55c. TO 56c. for No. 2, in store. CORN dull and 1E2 c. lower. sales at 21 c., in store, for mixed, OATS steady. Receipts -- 3,500 bbls. Flour, 42,000 bushels Wheat, 167,000 bushels Corn, 320,000 bushels Oats. FREIGHTS steady, at 6 1E4c. on Wheat to Buffalo. Exchange on New-York 1E2 c. cent. discount for gold. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, July 6. FLOUR dull. WHEAT unsettled. sales at  SX 1 10 TO  SX 1 15 for Red, and  SX 1 20 TO  SX 1 25 for White. CORN dull at 52c. TO 53c. WHISKY dull at 16 1E2c. TO 17c.  BUFFALO, Saturday, July 6.  CANAL FREIGHTS firm, Lake Imports to day -- 6,000 bbls. Flour, 300,000 bushels Wheat, 110,000 bushels Corn. Canal Exports -- 2,000 bbls. Flour, 41,000 bushels Wheat, 89,000 bushels Corn, 13,000 bushels Rye. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday July 5.  Reports received of successful engagement at Brier Forks, Missouri, between the troops under Col. Siegel and the rebels under Gov. Jackson and Rains.  BUFFALO, July 5 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT dull. sales 11,000 bushels Chicago Spring at 68c.. 9,000 bushels Kenosha Club at 75c.. 6,000 bushels Red Winter at 90c. CORN steady and in fair demand. sales 33,000 bushels at 32c. TO 32 1E2c., mostly at the outside figure. Other grains quiet. WHISKY steady. sales 600 bushels at 14c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday July 4.  Congress met today to discuss the crisis.  FORT KEARNEY, Tuesday, July 2.  The Pony Express passed here at 3 o'clock A.M.  SAN FRANCISCO, Saturday, June 22.  Sailed by the Sonora, a company of United States Sappers and Miners, numbering some 30 men. No less than four fine Union flags were conveyed by this steamer to regiments in service at the East -- the tokens of sympathy and admiration or California friends. The ship Mary Robinson, for New-York, carries 1,080 bales wool as a portion of her cargo. Trade remains completely stagnant. Money is plenty, but the rates of interest to borrowers vary considerably. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Tuesday, July 3. FLOUR dull and no demand at  SX 4. WHEAT declined 5c. WHISKY firm at 12c. MESS PORK,  SX 13 50, Exchange on New-York 34 cent, and firm. BUFFALO, Monday, July 3. FLOUR quiet and unchanged. WHEAT dull and lower. sales 10,000 bushels Kenosha Spring, at 75c.. 10,000 bushels No. 2 Chicago Spring at 61c.. 6,500 bushels No. 2 Milwaukee Club, at 65c.. 7,000 bushels do., at 67c. CORN lower. sales 13,000 bushels at 33 1E4c.. 6,500 bushels Yellow, at 33 3E4c.. 6,500 bushels, at 32 1E2c. OATS dull. Grain in store here -- 218,672 bushels Wheat, 332,300 bushels Corn, 72,041 bushels Oats, 1,300 bushels Barley, 19,741 bushels Rye, 400 bushels Peas. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday July 2.  Word is received of a successful engagement of Gen. Patterson's column near Martinsborgh.  OSWEGO, Tuesday, July 2. An incessant rain storm has prevailed for the last thirty four hours, accompanied with a strong north wind, and business of the docks is suspended. GRAIN quiet. sales, last evening, 3,000 bbls. No. 1 Chicago Spring Wheat, 78c. CARAL FREIGHTS quiet in consequence of the storm: Flour, 28c.. Wheat, 8c.. Corn 7c., to New-York. Lake Imports -- 23,700 bushels Corn. Caral Exports -- 1,900 bushels Wheat, 6,600 bushels Corn. The gale up to 6 P.M. still continues. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday, July 1, 1861.  Today, the Baltimore Board of Police Commissioners was arrested.  LEXINGTON, Mo., Monday, July 1. After three weeks of interruption, telegraphic communication is again established to this and all other points west, by the old Missouri river route. The parties who have hitherto destroyed the lines as fast as it could be repaired, have been induced to forego further molestations for the present, and the telegraph company think they will be allowed to keep the line at work for the future. 
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
