<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOBILE, Friday, March 29. COTTON -- Sales to-day 2,500 bales. middling, 12 1E4c. The market has an advancing tendency. Sales of the week 10,800 bales. receipts of the week 6,100, against 8,890 bales same time last year. Decreased receipts at this port this season 238,000 bales. Exports of the week 11,000 bales. Stock in port 58,210 bales. Exchange -- Sterling 7 cent. premium. on New-York 3E4 premium. BALTIMORE, Friday, March 29. PORK dull. Mess,  SX 17. Prime,  SX 14. COFFEE firm at 12 3E4c. to 13 3E4c. WHISKY steady. PHILADELPHIA, Friday, March 29. FLOUR firm. sales 5,000 bbls. Superfine, at  SX 5 25. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NORFOLK, Thursday, March 28. CORN -- Receipts, 100,000 bush.. market active. White, 62c. to 64c.. Yellow, 63c. to 63 1E2c.. Mixed, 60c. COTTON is firm and active, with large sales . good running lots, 12 1E4c.. Select, 12 1E2c.. Inferior dull at 10 1E2c. to 11 1E2c. NAVAL STORES in limited demand. Tar dull at  SX 1.50 to 1.60. STAVES active. red oak hhds., 37c.. white, 66c. FLOUR quiet . family brands,  SX 7.75 to  SX 8.35. superfine,  SX 6 to  SX 6.50. BALTIMORE, Thursday, March 28. FLOUR steady. Ohio,  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. WHEAT steady. red,  SX 1 27 to  SX 1 30. white,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 65. CORN firm, at 53c. to 57c.. yellow, 56c. to 58c. PROVISIONS dull and unchanged. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. PAUL, March 16.  The St. Paul Pioneer of March 16, says:  QN This evening, for the first time, the wires were connected through direct from St. Paul to New-York City, and compliments exchanged between the operators of the two cities. The New-York operator reported that the steamer Arabia was just coming up, 9 P.M., New-York time, and the captain had telegraphed from Sandy Hook, the gratifying intelligence that the Australasian was safe and the Arabia had her mails and passengers. The lines were in excellent working condition, and communications passed speedily. Difference in time was found to be one hour and fifteen minutes, New-York being 8:40, St. Paul 7:25. QN  
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, March 27. FLOUR quiet. sales 3,000 bbls. at  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2 for Superfine. WHEAT active. Red,  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 45 to   SX 1 48. CORN firm. sales 1,000 bushels at 58 1E2c. MESS PORK,  SX 17 25. WHISKY dull but firm at 18c. CINCINNATI, Tuesday, March 26. FLOUR dull at  SX 4 50. WHISKY dull at a decline of 1E2c.. quoted 13 1E4c  to 13 3E3c. PROVISIONS firm. LARD dull at 9c. MONEY easy. Exchange on New-York firm at 1E2 cent. NEW-ORLEANS, Wednesday, March 27. COTTON -- Sales, to-day, 9,000 bales. Middling Uplands, 12 1E2c. to 13c. SUGAR firm. fair to fully fair, 5c. to 6c. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 7-16d. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NORFOLK, Tuesday, March 26. COTTON -- Sales at 11 1E2c. to 12 1E4 c. for middling. strictly prime 1E8c. higher. CORN -- Sales, to-day, 20 000 bushels mixed at 61c. to 63c.. yellow, 63c. MOBILE, Tuesday, March 26. COTTON -- Sales, to-day, 2,500 bales Middling uplands, 12c. Sales of three days. 5,600. Receipts, 3,000. Sterling Exchange, 6 1E2 to 7 cent. premium. PHILADELHIA, Tuesday, March 26. FLOOR quiet. Superfine  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. CORN buoyant. sales 10 000 bushels. new Southern yellow, 60c.. old, 62 1E2c. LARD, 10c. to 11 1E4c. NEW-ORLEANS, Monday, March 25. COTTON firm. sales, to-day. 12,000 bales, at 12c.  to  12 1E2c.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 25. -- Arr. ship Santa Claus, from Liverpool. bark Shasta, from Iquique. brig Speedaway, from Savannah.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, March 25. FLOUR dull at  SX 5 for Superfine. WHEAT dull. sales 10,000 bushels. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 30. White,  SX 140 to  SX 1 50. CORN buoyant. sales 12,000 bushels New Yellow at 60c. COFFEE -- Rio, 12c. to 14c. MESS PORK,  SX 17 25. LARD, 11c. to 11 1E4c. WHISKY dull, 18c. to 18 1E2c. BALTIMORE, Monday, March 25. FLOUR steady. Howard-street and Ohio superfine  SX 5 to 5 12 1E2. WHEAT active and firm. red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 30. white,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 65. CORN firm. yellow, 59c. to 60c. PROVISIONS steady. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOBILE, Saturday, March 23. COTTON -- Sales to-day 3,500 bales Middling, at 11 3E4c. to 12 1E4c.. sales of the week. 16,700 bales. receipts for the same time. 6,405 bales, against 10,000 bales for the same time last year. decreased receipts, 255,290 bales. exports, 22,830 bales. stock in port 63,000bales. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 1E2 d. to Havre, 1c. Sterling Exchange, 106 to 106 1E2. Sight Exchange on New-York 3E8 per cent. premium. CINCINNATI, Saturday, March 23. FLOUR very dull and declining. Superfine at  SX 4 40 to  SX 4 50. WHEAT -- Red,  SX 1. White,  SX 1 12 WHISKY dull, at 13 5E8c. PROVISIONS quiet.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Saturday, March 23. FLOUR active. Howard street  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. Ohio held at  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills, at  SX 5, no sales. WHEAT quiet. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1.40 to   SX 1.60. CORN steady. Yellow, 55c to 59c.. Mixed, 59c.  to 62c.. White, 63c. to 64c. PROVISIONS steady. Mess Pork,  SX 17. COFFEE, 12 1E4c. to 12 c. WHISKY steady, at 17c. PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, March 23. FLOUR quiet. WHEAT -- Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 30. White.  SX 1 35 to 1 45. CORN firm. sales 1,600 bushels. New, 58c. to 58 1E2c. COFFEE -- Rio, 11 1E2c. to 14c. WHISKY steady at 18c. to 18 1E2c.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Thursday, March 21. COTTON -- Sales of 6,000 bales at 12c. to 12 1E4c. for Middling. SUGAR quiet at 4 3E4c. to 5c. MOLASSES, 24c. to 26c. FLOUR quiet at  SX 5 50. Mixed CORN, 56c. to 57c. PORK quiet at  SX 18 for Mess. Other articles are generally unchanged. MOBILE, Thursday, March 21. COTTON -- Sales of 2,700 bales at 11 3E4c. to 12c. for Middling. There is a good demand, and prices advancing. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, March 21. FLOUR quiet. sales 2,000 bbls. superfine at  SX 5 to   SX 5 50. WHEAT advanced 2c. to 3c.. sales 3,000 bushels Red at  SX 1 26 to  SX 1 29. White.  SX 1 50. CORN advanced 3c.. sales 14,000 bushels at 59c. to 60c. WHISKY steady at 18c. to 18 1E2c. NORFOLK, Thursday, March 21. COTTON -- The market is firm. sales of 1,000 bales, good, 12c.. inferior 10 1E2c. to 11c. CORN is active. sales of 40,000 bushels at 65c. to 67c. NAVAL STORES dull. Tar  SX 1 50. Staves active. R.O. hhds., 37c.. White, 66c. to 67c.. Pipe, 75c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 21.  A vessel with supplies for the United States fleet has been seized by rebels off Pensacola.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, March 20. -- Arr. ship St. Paul, from Boston.  CINCINNATI, Thursday, March 21. FLOUR dull, and not much doing. prices unchanged. WHISKY dull at 13 3E4c. PROVISIONS quiet, but firm. Mess Pork,  SX 16 75 to  SX 17. Bacon 7 1E8c. for Shoulders, 9 3E8c. for Sides, and 10 7E8c. for Hams. sales 100,000 lbs. Bulk Sides, at 8 1E2c. Lard quiet, 9 1E4c. to 10c. Sight Exchange on New-York firm, at 1E2 cent. premium. BALTIMORE, Thursday, March 21. FLOUR dull and heavy. Howard-street and Ohio  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills,  SX 5 -- no sales. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 20.  Arkansas has seceded from the Union.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, March 19. FLOUR dull. superfine,  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. WHEAT active at  SX 1 26 to  SX 1 28 for red. CORN quiet. sales 3,000 bushels new yellow at 55c. to 56c.. old, 58c. to 58 1E2c. WHISKY firm, 17 1E2c. to 18 1E2c. CINCINNATI, Tuesday, March 19. FLOUR is in fair demand. superfine,  SX 4 50 to  SX 4 60. WHISKY firm at 13 1E4c. PROVISIONS are quiet.  MOBILE, Tuesday, March 19. COTTON -- Sales to-day, 2,500 bales Middling, at 11 1E2c. Sales the past three days, 5,200 bales. receipts, 4,600. FREIGHTS, 9-16d. Sterling Exchange, 5 to 6 premium. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 19 -- Arr bark Ocean Pearl, Liverpool: brig Chatham, Malta. PHILADELPHIA, March 19 -- Arr. at breakwater, hark St. James, New-York. brig Osmus, New-Belford. NEW-ORLEANS, March 19. -- Arr. ship Golden Cross, Liverpool. bark Sartelle, New-York.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Tuesday, March 19. FLOUR dull. Howard street and Ohio,  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills,  SX 5. small sales. WHEAT steady. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 60. CORN dull. Mixed, 55c. to 56c.. Yellow, 57c. to 59c.. White, 60c. to 64c. PROVISIONS dull. COFFEE quiet at 12 1E4c. to 13c. WHISKY, 17c. to 17 1E4c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON,  Monday, March 18.   To-day, President Lincoln has made important diplomatic appointments.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 18. -- Ship King Philip, from London, for New-York, was off Highland Light, Cape Cod, to-day. NEW-ORLEANS, March 18. -- Arr. ships, Thomas H. Perkins, and Levi Woodbury, Liverpool. Picayune, Havre. bark Atlantic, Marseilles.  BALTIMORE, Monday, March 18. FLOUR dull. Howard street and Ohio are held at  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills at  SX 5. WHEAT buoyant. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 70. CORN active. Mixed, 53c. to 56. PROVISIONS dull. COFFEE firm at 12 1E4c to 13c. WHISKY dull at 17 1E4c 3 3E4c. [???] at 7c. for Shoulders, and [???]c. for Sides. Bulk Sides in good demand at 8 1E2c. MESS [???] and LARD -- Sales trifling. Money Market unchanged. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK.... SATURDAY, March 16. Schr. Truro, Cartlin, Halifax 15 ds., with fish to Whitmore  ES  Bros. March 6, lat. 41 14, lon. 65 17, took a heavy gale from N.W., which carried away foretopmast and foresail, March 10, lat. 41 06. lon. 68 54, Joseph Bond, a native of Halifax, fell overboard, and was drowned.  Ship Palestine, Warner, London, and Portland Roads Feb. 8, with mdse. and 30 passengers to E.E. Morgan. 2d inst, has experienced very heavy weather. Has been blown off the Highlands three times. Had a pilot on board three days 12th inst. lat. 37 43, lon. 71 28, spoke brig Moncello, of and for Boston. had mainboom carried away. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MONTGOMERY,  Saturday, March 16.  The Confederate States Congress adjourned today.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 15. -- Arr. ship Speedwell, Liverpool. barks John, Messina. Smyrinote, Smyrnia. Abbi, London. brigs Betsey Ames, Buenos Ayres. Renfrew, St. Martins.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Friday, March 15. FLOUR quiet. superfine,  SX 5 to  SX 5 25. WHEAT active. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 35 to  SX 1 45. CORN firm. sales 1,600 bushels new Yellow at 55c. to 57c. COFFEE -- Rio, 12 3E4c. to 14c. WHISKY, 18c. to 18 1E2c. BALTIMORE, Friday, March 15.  CORN steady. Mixed, 53c. to 55c. PROVISIONS dull and unchanged. COFFEE firm at 12 1E4c. to 13 1E4c.


</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Thursday, March 14. FLOUR dull and heavy. Howard-street,  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills,  SX 5. no sales. WHEAT firm. Red,  SX 1 25  SX 1 27. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 65. Corn dull. Mixed, 53c.  to 55c.. Yellow, 56c. to 59c. PORK steady. Mess, 17: Rump,  SX 13. LARD, 9 3E4c. COFFEE quiet at 12 1E4c. to  13 1E4c. WHISKY, 17 1E2c. PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, March 14. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT firm. sales 4,000 bushels Red at  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 30. White,  SX 1 35 to  SX 1 45. CORN dull: sales 5,000 bushels new Yellow at 57c. MESS PORK,  SX 17 50. BACON -- Hams, 11c. to 13c. WHISKY, 18c. to 18 1E2c. MOBILE, Thursday, March 14. COTTON firm. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Wednesday, March 13. FLOUR dull and heavy. Ohio and Howard-street,  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills,  SX 5, with no buyers. WHEAT active. Red at  SX 1 23 to  SX 1 27. White,  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 65. CORN declined 2c.. Mixed. 53c. to 55c. PROVISIONS dull and unchanged. COFFEE firm at 12 1E4c. to 13 1E4c. WHISKY dull at 17 1E2c. to 18c. PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, March 13. FLOUR -- Superfine,  SX 5. WHEAT is in demand. White.  SX 1 35 to  SX 1 45. Red,  SX 1 27 to  SX 1 28. CORN steady. new Yellow, 56c. COFFEE -- Rio, 12 1E2c. to 13 1E4c. WHISKY declined 1E2c., at 18c. to 18 1E2c.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOREHEAD, N.C., Monday, March 12 -- Arr. steamer Daylight, 50 hours from New-York.  NEW-ORLEANS March 12 -- Arr. ship George Washington, Liverpool. bark Texan Star, Galveston.   BOSTON, March 13. -- Arr. brigs J.  ES  H. Crowley, Matanzas. Robert Wing, Africa: Georgia, Buenos Ayres. Belle of the Bay, Mobile. Below -- brig New-World, Cardenas.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOBILE, Wednesday, March 13. COTTON -- sales, to-day, 3,000 bales, at 11 1E2c. for Middling. sales of three days, 8,500 bales. Receipts, 3,600 bales. Sight Exchange on New-York at par. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Monday, March 11. FLOUR quiet at  SX 4 50 to  SX 4 60. WHISKY declined. quoted 13 1E2c. PROVISIONS quiet, and accurate quotations cannot be given. BACON -- Shoulders, 7 1E8c.. Sides, 9 1E2c. LARD dull at 9c. NEW-ORLEANS, Friday, March 8. COTTON -- The market closed with an advancing tendency. sales to-day, 20,000 bales. middling is nowquoted 11 1E2c. Sales of the week, 81,000 bales. receipts of the week, 35,500 bales, against 66,000 in corresponding period last year. exports of the week, 84,000 bales. total to date, 1,401,050 bales. stock in port, 365 500 bales. NEW-ORLEANS, Monday, March 11. COTTON -- The market is firm.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PROVIDENCE, March 9 -- Arr at Newport, brig Baltic,  Hooper, from Manzanilla. Cuba, from Havre.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Friday, March 8. COTTON -- The market closed with an advancing tendency. sales, to-day, 20,000 bales, at 11 1E2c. for Middling. sales of the week, 81,000 bales. total sales, 141,650 bales. stock in port, 365,500 bales. COFFEE -- Sales of the week, 8,750 bags, at 10 1E2c. to 13c.. imports, 3,800 bags. stock in port, 45,000 bags, against 39,500 bags in the corresponding time last year. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 5E8d. PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, March 9. FLOUR drooping, at  SX 5 to  SX 5 12 1E2. WHEAT unchanged.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Friday, March 8. FLOUR declined 12 1E2c.. Howard-street and Ohio at  SX 5 12 1E2. no sales. WHEAT active. Red,  SX 1 23 to   SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 65. CORN active. Yellow, 59c. to 61c. PROVISIONS dull. Mess Pork,  SX 17. Prime,  SX 12 50. Lard, 9 3E4 c.  PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, March 8. FLOUR dull and prices weak at  SX 5 12 1E2 to  SX 5 50 for superfine. WHEAT quiet. White  SX 1 35 to  SX 1 40. Red  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 26. CORN declined 1c.. New Yellow 56c., Old White 65c. OATS dull. COFFEE quiet. Rio at 12 1E8c.  to 13c. PROVISIONS dull. LARD dull. WHISKY dull at 19c. to 19 1E2c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Thursday March 7. -- Arr. ships Adelaide, and Simoda from Havre. Stephen Baldwin, from Bordeaux.Indiana, from New-York. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Wednesday, March 8.  COTTON -- The market is active, and the sales today reach 30,000 bales. Middling is quoted at 11 1E8c. to 11 3E8c. SUGAR The market is steady at 4 3E4c. to 5 3E4c. lb. for fair to fully fair. MOLASSES, 26c. to 28c. gallon. FLOUR dull, Ohio  SX 5 12 1E2 to  SX 5 50. CORN -- Mixed 55c. to 58c. bush. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 3E4d.. to Havre, 1 1E4c. PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, March 8. FLOUR dull and prices weak at  SX 5 12 1E2 to  SX 5 50 for superfine. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>TURIN, Thursday, Feb. 20. The number of troops made prisoners at Gaeta was 11,000. The Sardinians found between 700 and 800 cannons and 60,000 muskets. Three Generals accompanied FRANCIS II, to Rome. Twenty-five are prisoners.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>P NEW-ORLEANS, Wednesday, March 6. COTTON steady. sales to-day 12,000 bales at 11c.  to 11 1E4c. for Middling. SUGAR steady at 4 1E4c.  to  5 1E4c. for fair to fully fair. MOLASSAS. 26c. to 28c. Freight on, Cotton to Liverpool, 5E8 d. Exchange on London, 4 to 5 premium. Sight Exchange on New-York, 1E4 discount to par.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 6. -- Arr. bark Gen. Warren, Algoa Bay: brigs A.J. Ross, Cienfuegos. Lincoln, Cardenas, J.H. Jones, Charleston. NEW-ORLEANS, March 6. -- Arr. ship Orondates, Liverpool. Transit, and Amity, Glasgow. bark Actalon, Glasgow.   BOSTON, March 6. -- Arr. bark Gen. Warren, Algoa Bay: brigs A.J. Ross, Cienfuegos. Lincoln, Cardenas, J.H. Jones, Charleston. NEW-ORLEANS, March 6. -- Arr. ship Orondates, Liverpool. Transit, and Amity, Glasgow. bark Actalon, Glasgow.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Wednesday, March 6. COTTON steady. sales to-day 12,000 bales at 11c.  to 11 1E4c. for Middling. SUGAR steady at 4 1E4c.  to  5 1E4c. for fair to fully fair. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Tuesday, March 5.  COTTON quiet. sales to-day, 8,500 bales, at 10 3E4c.  to 11 1E4c. for mideling. sales of three days, 19,000 bales. receipts of three days, 20,500 bales, against 29,500 bales last year. Decreased receipts at this port, 214,100 bales. do, at all the ports. 634,500 bales. SUGAR steady at 4 3E4c,  to  5 1E4c, for fair to fully fair. No change in other articles. PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, March 5. FLOUR is dull. WHEAT steady at  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 32 1E2 for Red and  SX 1 35 to  SX 1 45 for White. CORN declined. sales 3,000 bush, at 56 1E8c. COFFEE steady. WHISKY firm at 19c. to 19 1E2c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 05 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Tuesday, March 5.  The manner in which President LINCOLN'S Inaugural was transmitted by telegraph is deserving of especial commendation. The American Telegraph Company placed at the disposal of the Associated Press three wires between Washington and this City. The delivery of the Inaugural commenced at 1 1E2 o'clock, Washington time. The first words of the Message were received at 1 3E4 o'clock, and the last about 3 1E2 o'clock, while the entire document was furnished to the different newspers by 4 o'clock. Such rapidity in telegraphic communication has never before been reached in this country.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday, March 4.  President Lincoln was inaugurated today.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 4 -- Arr. steamship Joseph Whitney, from Baltimore: brigs Orello, Palermo. Northern Belle, from Messina. Evergreen, from Cienfuegos. schrs. Tilly, Jennie, Morton, and J.J. Spencer, from Mobile. East Wind, Jeremie, and Geo. Davis, from Savannah.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, Monday, March 4, 1861. Mr. CHAMBLISS, of Greenville, introduced a resolution asserting that as the Peace Conference proposition fails of the assurance of an equitable settlement of the Slavery controversy, Virginia should offer no more propositions, but withdraw from the Federal Compact and adopt measures to protect their rights, in concert with the other Southern States. Mr. CHAMBLISS made a secession speech.  Mr. CARLISLE replied in a strong Union speech. He believed the Conference propositions acceptable to the people. The resolution was referred to the Committee on Federal Relations. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, March 1, 1861. -- Arr. barks Mary Baker, Newport England. Tres Amigos, Turks Island. brigs Susan Duncan, Matanzas. S. P. Smith, Galveston. Arabell, Guadalome. schr. J. Nickerson. Cape Haytien. NEW ORLEANS, Feb. 28. -- Arr. ships Idaho. Liverpool: Richard Alsop, Glasgow. Rufus Choate, Havrebarks Fanny Buck, Messina. Sarah Nichols, Rio Janeiro. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday, March 2, 1861.  Reports from Texas indicate the revenue cutter Dodge has been seized by the Texan authorities.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Thursday, Feb. 28, 1861. COTTON -- Sales to-day 11,500 bales middling at 10 3E4c. to 11 1E4c. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool 3E4d. MOBILE, Thursday, Feb. 28. COTTON -- Sales of 15,000 bales at 10 3E4c. to 11c. for Middling. The market is dull and unchanged. CHICAGO, Thursday, Feb. 28. Exchange on New-York advanced to 8 cent. premium. BALTIMORE, Thursday, Feb. 28. FLOUR dull and heavy. WHEAT firm. CORN steady but quiet. COFFEE firm and active. WHISKY firm at 19 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Feb. 27. -- Arr. barks Ella, Palermo. Franklin Trinidad. brig M.T. Ellsworth, Matanzas. schr. C. Allsrum, Miragoane. NEW-ORLEANS, Feb. 27. -- Arr. ships old England, and Mongolia, Liverpool. Joseph Holmes, Havre. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, Feb. 27. FLOUR unchanged at  SX 5 25. WHEAT advanced 3c. to 5c.. sales 3 000 bushels. red,  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 35. white,  SX 1 45. CORN dull. sales 2,000 bushels at 62 1E2c. for old. COFFEE -- Rio, 11 3E4. to 13c. WHISKY advanced 1E2c.. sales at 18c. to 19c.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MONTGOMERY, Thursday, Feb. 28.  President Davis has vetoed the bill legalizing the African Slave-trade.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Tuesday, Feb. 26. -- Arr. steamers S.R. Spaulding, Baltimore. Kensington, Philadelphia. ships John Mandeville, Calcutta. barks Laura Russ, New-Orleans. brigs American Union, Galveston: P.A. Page, Havana. Forest City, Cardenas. J. McIntyre, New-Orleans. Below -- ship Clifton, New-Orleans. bark R. Pennell, Cardenas.  NEW-ORLEANS, Feb. 26. -- Arr. ship B.D. Metcalf, Liverpool: bark Ivanhoe, Rio Janeiro.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Wednesday, Feb. 27.  CORN active. mixed 55c. to 57c.. Yellow 57c. to 60c. PROVISIONS dull. Mess Pork  SX 17 25. LARD 10c. COFFEE firm at 12 1E4c. to 13c. WHISKY buoyant at 19c. to 19 1E4c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Tuesday, Feb. 26. COTTON -- Sales to-day 9,000 bales. Middling, 10 7E8c. to 11 1E4c. Sales of the last three days, 30,000 bales. receipts of the three days 28,000, against 59,000 bales during the same period last year. receipts less than last year, 197,000 bales. do. at all Southern port, 601,400 bales. SUGAR buoyant at 4 1E4c. to 5 1E4c. MOLASSES, 24 1E2c. to 27c. Exchange on London, 33 3E4 to  4 1E4 premium. on New York, 1E2 to 3E4 discount.  NEW-ORLEANS. Monday, Feb. 25 -- Arr. ship Great Britain, Liverpool. bark Wakefield, Havana. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON,  Monday, Feb. 25.  From Texas, reports indicate General Twiggs has committed treason and federal forts in Texas are surrendered to the State Government along with a large body of United States troops.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Saturday, Feb. 23. COTTON -- The market has a declining tendency. The sales to-day reach 4,000 bales. Middling Uplands 10 7E8c. to 12 1E4c. SUGAR steady, at 1 1E4c. to 5 1E4c. MOLASSES, 25c. to 16c. gallon. FLOUR -- Ohio  SX 5 37 1E8 bbl. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool 3E4d. CHARLESTON, Saturday, Feb. 23. COTTON -- Sales of 740 bales at 9c. to 11 1E2c. for Middling, being a decline of 1E4c. to 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, Saturday, Feb. 23. -- Arr. ships Ocean Queen, Susan Hincks and Wild Cat, Boston. barks G.W. Horton, do.. Wm. Wilson. Providence. schr. Dew Drop, Honduras PORTLAND, Feb. 24. -- The steamship North American, for Liverpool via Londonderry, sailed from here at 11 1E4 A.M. to-day.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Feb. 23. FLOUR firm, and 12 1E2c. higher. Super,  SX 5 12 1E2 to   SX 5 25. WHEAT advanced 2c.. sales at  SX 1 32 to  SX 1 50 for White, and  SX 1 29 to  SX 1 32 for Red. CORN steady. sales of new Yellow at 60c., and old at 63c. OATS steady. PROVISIONS dull. COFFEE firm. sales of Rio at 12c. to 13 1E4c. t. premium. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday, Feb. 23.  Mr. Lincoln arrived in this city to-day following quiet passage through Baltimore.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LONDON MONEY MARKET -- SATURDAY. Consols for Money, 91 3E4 to 91 7E8. for Account, 92 1E4 to 92 3E8. The Bullion in the Bank of England has increased L215,000. The market is slightly more stringent, and very active. no transactions in Discounts below 7 cent. AMERICAN SECURITIES. BARING reports the market very dull, and accurate quotations cannot be given. The latest sales were: Illinois Central 29 1E4 to 29 discount. New-York Central, 72 to 74. Erie, 28 3E4 to 29 1E4. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Friday Feb. 22. The steamer's news caused no effect on the market. COTTON -- Sales to-day, 20,000 bales Middling 11c. to 11 1E4c.. sales of three days, 52,500 bales. Receipts of three days, 38,500 bales. Decreased receipts at this port, port, 173,500 bales. do at all ports. 581,500 bales. FLOUR  SX 5 35 to   SX 5 40 for superfine. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 3E4d. PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, Feb. 20. FLOUR unchanged. Supreme  SX 5. WHEAT firm. sales 2,600 bushels at  SX 1 24 to 1 30 for Red and  SX 1 32 to  SX  1 50 for White. CORN advanced. sales 1,600 bushels new at 58c. to 59c. COFFEE buoyant at 11 3E4c. to 13c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, Feb. 21.  President-elect Lincoln is to-day in this city.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>AUGUSTA, Tuesday, Feb. 19. COTTON advanced 1E4c. to 1E2c. on better grades. sales to-day 1,100 bales. CHARLESTON, Tuesday, Feb. 19. COTTON -- Sales to-day 1,100 bales, at 7 1E2c. to  12 1-16c. MOBILE, Tuesday, Feb. 19. COTTON quiet. sales to-day 2,000 bales, at 11c. for Middling. NEW-ORLEANS, Tuesday, Feb. 19. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Tuesday, Feb. 19. FLOUR dull. Howard-street and Ohio are held at  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills, at  SX 5. WHEAT active and firmer. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 30. White,  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 65. CORN active, but declined: sales 25,000 bushels Mixed, at 57c. to 58c.. Yellow, 55c. to 60c. PROVISIONS steady. COFFEE firm, at 12c. to 13c. WHISKY dull, at 17 1E2c.  to 17 3E4c. CINCINNATI, Tuesday, Feb. 19. FLOUR firm, and holders demand an advance. WHISKY active, at 13 1E2c. PROVISIONS dull. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday Feb. 19.  The report in relation to a telegraphic survey provides for a careful survey of the route for a line of magnetic telegraph from San Francisco, via Oregon, Washington territory, the British North American possessions, Russian America and Behring Straits. The two national vessels of the United States which are to assist in the survey, will necessarily fit out and start from San Francisco. The telegraph proposed, in connection with the Sibley Telegraph line, from Missouri to San Francisco, and the Russian line, building from Moscow, will connect the whole civilized world by continuous telegraphic communication. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday, Feb. 18.  Reports received that a secessionist movement in Missouri has been defeated.  MONTGOMERY,   Feb. 18.  To-day, President Davis was inaugurated.  WASHINGTON, Monday, Feb. 18. The Peace Conference were in session, to-day, upwards of five hours. The debate was the most animated of any since the commencement of the Convention. The two reports from the Committee were under consideration. The propositions respecting the Territories, establishing or permitting Slavery south of 36 deg 30 min, were opposed earnestly by gentlemen from New-York, Massachusetts, New-Hampshire, Ohio, Illinois and Wisconsin. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MONTGOMERY, Sunday, Feb. 17.  Mr. Davis has to-day made his first speech after being elected President of the Confederate States.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, FEB. 17 -- Arr. ships Dublin. Gottenburg, Galena, New-Orleans. barks F.H. Cushing, Buesnos Ayres. John Kerr, do.. Lyander, Trinidad. Col. Ledyard, Apalachicola. John Griffin, Messina. Caroline Ellems, New-Orleans. Mustang, Mobile. brigs Minerva, Rotterdam. Poinsett, Galveston. The steamship Jamestown, Skinner, which arrived yesterday, from Richmond and Norfolk, brought on freight 20 bbls. of shad, the first of the season.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SANDY HOOK, Feb. 15 -- 11:15 P.M. -- There as yet no signs of the steamship Africa, from Liverpool Feb. 2, Wind moderate, W. Weather hazy off shore.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Friday, Feb. 15. FLOUR more active. City Mills at  SX 5. Ohio and Howard-street at  SX 5 12 1E2. WHEAT steady. Red at  SX 1 27 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 60. CORN dull. Yellow, 53c. to 56c. PROVISIONS steady. Mess PORK.  SX 17 75. Rump  SX 13 50. LARD 10c. COFFEE steady at 12 1E4c. to  13c. WHISKY dull at 18c. CINCINNATI, Friday, Feb. 15. FLOUR dull. WHISKY dull, at 14c. PROVISIONS quiet. MESS PORK,  SX 16 75 to  SX 17. BULK MEATS 6 1E4c.  to 8 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, Feb. 14. FLOUR quiet, at  SX 5 25 to  SX 5 50. WHEAT unchanged. CORN firmer. Yellow, 51c.. Old, 65c. PROVISIONS dull. BACON -- Hams, 11c. to 13c.. Sides, 10 1E2c.: Shoulders, 8 1E2c. WHISKY steady, at 17 1E2c. BALTIMORE, Thursday, Feb. 14. FLOUR active. Howard street and Ohio,  SX 5 12 1E2. City Mills,  SX 5 WHEAT firmer. Red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 60. CORN active: Yellow, 55c. to 57c.. Mixed, 55c.. White, 65c. to 67c. PROVISIONS quiet and unchanged. COFFEE steady, at 12 1E4c. to 13c. WHISKY nominal, at 17 1E2c. to 18c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Wednesday, Feb. 13. FLOUR dull and heavy. Ohio and Howard-street are held at  SX 5 12 no sales. City Mills, nominally at  to 5. WHEAT dull. Red  SX 1.20 to  SX 1.28. White,  SX 1.35 to  SX 1.55 CORN dull and heavy. Yellow, at 55c. 57c. PROVISIONS quiet, steady, and unchanged. COFFEE active, at 12 c. to 13c WHISEY dull, at 17 c. to 18c. CINCINNATI, Wednesday, Feb. 13. FLOUR dull and drooping, at  SX 4 50 for Superfine. WHISKY steady, at 13 3E4c. MESS PORK,  SX 16 75 to  SX 17. LARD, 9 1E4c to 10c. Money market and Sight Exchange on New-York unchanged. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOBILE, Saturday, Feb 9. COTTON -- Sales of 1.000 bales at 10 3E4c. for Middling. The market is very dull. NEW-ORLEANS, Saturday, Feb. 9. COTTON closed with a declining tendency. sales to-day 4,500 bales, at 10 3E4c. for Middling. SUGAR steady, at 4 3E8c.  to 5 3E4c. for fair to fully fair. MOLASSES 23c  to 26c. FLOUR at  SX 5 90 to  SX 6 for superfine. CORN, 61c. to 65c. WHISKY at 18 1E2c  to 19c. Exchange on London 102 1E2 to 103 1E2. FREIGHTS unaltered.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MONTGOMERY, Tuesday Feb. 12.  The Confederate States Government to-day announced it will address all questions pending between the Confederate States and the United States Government.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Feb. 11. FLOUR dull, at  SX 5 for superfine. WHEAT dull. sales 3,000 bushels. Red at  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White  SX 1 35  to  SX 1 40. CORN dull. sales 2,000 bushels at 56c. to 66c. MESS PORK at  SX 18 25 to  SX 18 50. LARD 10 1E2c. WHISKY steady at 18c.  BALTIMORE, Saturday, Feb 9. FLOUR dull and heavy. Ohio and Howard-street,  SX 5 25. City Mills at  SX 5 12c. WHEAT dull. Red.  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 28. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 60. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Monday, Feb. 11.  Mr. Lincoln, president elect, leaves Springfield and commences his journey to Washington.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Feb. 9 FLOUR drooping, at  SX 5 for superfine. WHEAT dull. sales, 2,000 bushels. red,  SX 1 25 to  SX 1 27. white,  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 40. CORN dull, at 56c. to 65c. PROVISIONS dull. COFFEE -- Rio, 12 1E2c. to 13 3E4c. WHISKY steady, at 17 1E2c. CINCINNATI, Saturday, Feb. 9. FLOUR very dull at  SX 4 60 to  SX 4 70 for Superfine, WHISKY at 13 3E4c. PROVISIONS quiet and firm. BACON firm and quiet. PORK quiet and firm at  SX 17 to  SX 17 25 to Mess. LARD dull at 9 1E4c. Sight Exchange on New-York firm at 1E2 cent. premium. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, SUNDAY Feb. 10.  Reports received that yesterday, Arkansas arsenals were seized by the State Government.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK....SATURDAY, Feb. 9.  Steamship Patapsco, Vale, Portland, with mdse. and passengers to H.B. Cromwell  ES  Co. Feb. 8, at 4 P.M., off Quick's Hole, passed a schr., of about 175 tons, sunk. had about 15 feet of her lower masts out of water. The P. has experienced heavy S.S.W. and N.N.W. gales during the passage. Is completely iced up. The first officer and some of the crew are badly frostbitten.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MONTGOMERY, Saturday, Feb. 9.  Jefferson Davis has been elected President and A.H. Stevens, of Georgia, Vice President of the Southern Confederacy, by a unanimous vote.   The regular passenger train from West Point, due here at near noon, when within about three miles of this City, met with a serious accident to cars and wheels, but no person was injured. The track was broken up for about fifty feet. the baggage and express cars were considerably smashed, and thrown disengaged from their tracks. On the train were several delegates to the Convention. Hons. A. H. STEPHENS, ROBERT TOOMBS, JAS. CHISWELL, T. J. WITHERS, T. R. R. COBB. all escaped unhurt.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MONTGOMERY, Friday, Feb. 8.  The Montgomery Convention adopted the Constitution of the United States for the Provisional Governemnt of the  QN Confederate States of America. QN   There have been unusually heavy rains within the past few days throughout South Carolina, Georgia and Alabama, and, as a consequence, the creeks and rivers are full, and some of the rivers mark a higher stage of water than has been known for many years. It is unnecessary to state that much damage has been caused. At Atlanta, Georgia, on Saturday night, the trains on the railroad were twelve hours behind time, and fears were entertained that some of the bridges on that route had been damaged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Thursday, Feb. 7, 1861.  One of the most furious gales that have visited this region for many months past commenced in this City last evening. Beginning with a slight snow-squall about 5 o'clock P.M., which soon blew over and left a cloudless sky, the wind continued to increase in violence until late in the night, and even at the time of going to press, it has scarcely abated any of its fury. Simultaneously with the commencement of the gale, the mercury suddenly fell several degrees, and the weather continued to grow colder as the gale increased. We have heard of no serious damage being done in the City.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Feb. 6, 1861.  The Pacific Telegraph.  Private letters by the last mail from California leave little room to doubt that under the judicious diplomacy of Mr. WADE, the representative of the Western Union Telegraph Company, all the telegraph interests in California will be consolidated and a strong Company formed on the Pacific to cooperate with the Western Union Company on the Atlantic side, in the rapid completion of the Pacific under the recent Congressional grant. We understand from well-informed parties that an earnest and persevering effort will be made to extend the telegraphic facilities to Oregon and beyond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Feb. 5, 1861.  The Louisiana Delegation has to-day withdrawn from Congress.  The Senate Finance Committee have recommended the passage of an act reducing the charge for coinage to one-fifth of one per cent. It is likely to pass. The present charge is one-half per cent. The Morrill tariff bill, as reported by the Senate Special Committee, seems to have excited much alarm among mercantile classes, and quite a delegation of merchants is here begging Senators not to rush the bill through in hot haste, but give time for exposure of its many fallacies, and unjust and unwise provisions. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday Feb. 3.  A Peace Convention has to-day been assembled in this city.   MONTGOMERY, Monday Feb. 3.  The Southern Convention has been organized to-day.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Saturday, Feb. 2. WHEAT dull. Red  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 33. White  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 60. CORN steady. Yellow 62c. to 67c. LARD 10 1E2c. COFFEE steady, at 12c. to 13c. WHISKY nominal at 18c. PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Feb. 2. FLOUR dull at  SX 5 25 for superfine. WHEAT dull. sales 2,000 bushels Red at  SX 1 26 to  SX 1 30. Kentucky White,  SX 1 50. CORN declined 1c.. sales, 3,000 bushels at 69c. to 70c. Mess PORK,  SX 18 25. WHISKY steady at 17 1E2c. to 18c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Wednesday, Jan. 30, 1861. FLOUR firm at  SX 4 50 to  SX 1 60. WHISKY firm at 14c. gallon. HOGS nominal. receipts to-day, 300. BULK MEATS active. sales 1.500,000 tbs. at 6 1E2c. for Shoulders, and 8 1E2c for Sides. PORK -- Mess,  SX 17 to  SX 17 12 1E2. LARD dull at 9 1E2. Exchange on New-YORK steady at 1E2 cent. The Money Market is easier. NEW-ORLEANS, Wednesday, Jan. 30. COTTON firm. sales, to-day, 18,000 bales at 11c.  to 11 1E2c. for middling. SUGAR steady, at 4 1E2c. to 5 1E2c. for fair to fully fair. MOLASSES, 23c. to  25c. PORK very dull. mess.  SX 19 50.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOBILE, Saturday Feb. 2, 1861.  The cutter Lewis Cass surrendered to the State of Alabama.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, Jan. 30, 1861. FLOUR dull at  SX 5 25 for Superfine. WHEAT firm. sales 3,000 bushels Red at  SX 1 28 to 8 SX 1 30. White at  SX 1 35 to  SX 1 45. CORN -- Yellow declined 2c. at 70c. COFFEE -- Rio 12 1E2c.  to 13 1E2c. PROVISIONS closed with an advancing tendency. Mess Pork  SX 18 50. WHISKY dull at 17 3E4c. to 18c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday Feb. 1, 1861.  To-day, Texas seceded from the Union.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON, Friday Feb. 1, 1861.  Preparations for war are underway.  BALTIMORE, Wednesday, Jan. 30, 1861. FLOUR, dull. Howard-street and Ohio,  SX 5 37 1E4. City Mills,  SX 5 25. no sales. WHEAT closed generally with an advancing tendency. Red,  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 35: White,  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 65. CORN firmer. Yellow, 61c. to  65c.. White, 70c to 73c., PROVISIONS steady. MESS PORK,  SX 18 25. LARD, 10 1E2c. COFFEE steady at 11 1E2c.  to 12 1E2c. WHISKY steady at 18c. to 18 1E2c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  Thursday, January 31, 1861.  The annual meeting of the stockholders of the American telegraph Company took place yesterday at No. 4 Wall-street. The annual report was read, from which it appears that stock had been issued to the amount of  SX 1,458,100. During the past year there has been expended for materials, repairs, reconstructions of the lines, etc.,  SX 135,503 73, and for instruments and fixtures  SX 17,370 56. The Company has invested in the purchase of the Cape Cod Telegraph Company's stock and lines, and a lease of the Nova Scotia line for ten years has been obtained. The line between Atlanta and Macon, Ga., has been leased for five years. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 30. Death of a telegraph operator.  Mr. JAMES MITCHELL of this city, and long connected with the Southern and American Telegraph Companies' lines at different points, died here this morning, after a brief illness of typhoid fever. Mr. MITCHELL was an accurate and accomplished operator, and enjoyed in the highest degree the confidence and respect of his employers. Among his brother operators and those of the profession with whom his duties brought him in daily intercourse, he was greatly beloved and esteemed for his amiable and gentlemanly deportment, and by them his loss is most sincerely deplored. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Jan. 28. FLOUR dull and declined 12 1E2c.. Superfine at  SX 5 25 to 35 50. WHEAT steady. White at  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 45. Red  SX 1 26 to  SX 1 30. CORN firm. sales 5,000 bush, new at 64c.. old at 70c. PROVISIONS unchanged. WHISKY declined: Ohio 18c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Tuesday Jan. 29.   The New York Times reports that President Buchanan has evinced an unsteadiness of purpose, and an indisposition to deal vigorously with the rebellion.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday Jan. 28.  The Georgia delegation has withdrawn from Congress.  The South Carolina legislature has resolved to demand the surrender of Sumter.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Monday, Jan. 28. COTTON steady. sales to-day 8,500 bales. Middling Uplands, 10 3E4c. to 11 1E4c. SUGAR buoyant at 4c.  to 5 1E4c. MOLASSES, 21c. to 23c. PORK firm at  SX 21 50 for Mess. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 1d.. to Havre, 2d. PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Jan. 28. FLOUR dull and declined 12 1E2c.. Superfine at  SX 5 25 to 35 50. WHEAT steady. White at  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 45. Red  SX 1 26 to  SX 1 30. CORN firm. sales 5,000 bush, new at 64c.. old at 70c. PROVISIONS unchanged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON, Thursday, Jan. 24, 1861.  A Cotton Convention is to be held at Atlanta, Ga., on the 13th of February. The object is to enable the South to export spun Cotton to the leading powers of Europe. This fearful agitation has some good points. It is certainly teaching the South their vast natural resources and forcing them to develope them. The famous Jockey Club of South Carolina will hold their annual meeting on the 2d of February. Their ball and dinner will be dispensed with this season. The reason is obvious. This Club is patronized by the flower of the Palmetto State, and the races are graced by the presence, usually, of all the leading ladies. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK....SATURDAY, Jan. 26. Ship Mameluke, of Boston. Pike, Baker's Island Oct. 18, passed Cape Horn Nov. 25, with guano to Wm. H. Webb. Nov. 26, lat. 55 S., lon. 60 spoke ship Crest of the Wave, hence for Valparaiso. Dec. 8, Briggs C. Wadsworth, seaman, of Duxbury, Mass., fell overboard from the bowsprits arouds, and was lost. Dec. 25 lat 6 S., lon. 33 W. spoke ship Panama, hence for San Francisco. Same day, exchanged signals with ship Gentos. Ship Anna Kimball, Marsh, Sunderland Oct 13, via Bermuda S ds., with coal to H.  ES  F. W. Meyer, Sld. from Bermuda in co, with brig Princess Royal, for New-York, Jan. 22. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday Jan. 25.  Ex-Secretary Floyd has been presented by the Grand Jury for malfeasance in office.  To-day, Louisiana seceded from the Union.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Jan. 24 -- Arr. steamer Cambridge, Philadelphia. bark Surinam, Surmain. Below, ship Crusader, Valparaiso, and bark Island City from Galveston. FORFOLK. Jan. 25. -- Arr. in Hampton Roads, 24th, -barks N.W. Bridge and W.J. Colcord, with guano from the ship John Colton, which put into Matanzas in distrees. NEW ORLEANS, Jan. 25. -- Arr. bark Citizen, from Aspinwall. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LONDON, Saturday Evening, Jan. 5. It is stated that the English Government has sent a strong note to the Emperor of France, protesting against the extension of the occupation of Syria by the French forces. No reply had yet been received. The latest sales of American stocks were: Erie Railroad, 35 to 35 3E8. New-York Central, 76 to 80 . Illinois Central, 27% to 28 discount. LIVERPOOL, Sunday, Jan. 6. The sales of Cotton, yesterday, were 8,000 bales, including 1,000 bales to speculators and exporters. The market closed steady. The Breadstuffs Market closed steady. The market for Provisions closed dull. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Wednesday Jan. 23.  There has been a second seizure of arms destined for Alabama.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, Jan. 22. FLOUR dull at  SX 5 62 1E2.  QN WHEAT steady. white,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 50. red,  SX 1 30 to  SX  1 32. CORN active. yellow, now, 64c. to 65c. old, 71C to 72c. MESS PORK.  SX 18  to  SX 17 50. BACON -- Shoulders, 91E4c.. Sides, 11 1E4C. WHISKY steady at 18 1E2c. to 19c. CHICAGO, Tuesday, Jan. 22. FLOUR, quiet. WHEAT dull and 1c. lower. sales 54,000 bushels at 80 1E2c. for No. 1. 76c  to 76 1E2c. for No. 2, in store. CORN dull. OATS steady. Receipts -- 2,800 bbls. Flour, 13,000 bush. Wheat, 7,000 bush. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Tuesday Jan. 22.  Arms destined for Alabama have been seized to-day in this city.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Tuesday, Jan. 22. FLOUR steady. Howard street and Ohio,  SX 5 50  to  SX 5 62 1E2. WHEAT dull. Red,  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 35. White,  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 60. CORN firm. Yellow, 62c  to 65c.. White, 68c.  to 70c.. Old White, 72c. to 74c. PROVISIONS steady. Mess PORK,  SX 18. LARD, 10 1E8c. COFFEE steady, at 12c. to  13c.. stock in port, 25,000b ags. market firm. WHISKY dull, at 18 1E2c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday Jan. 21.  The Alabama, Florida, and Mississippi delegations have withdrawn from the city. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Saturday, Jan. 19. FLOUR dull at  SX 4 50 for superfine. WHISKY in good demand at 13 1E2c. HOGS in good demand at  SX 6 40  to  SX 6 60. PROVISIONS firm and quiet. Money market quiet. Sight Exchange on New-York 1E2 B cent. premium. PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Jan. 19. WHEAT steady. Red,  SX 1 50. White,  SX 1 31 to  SX 1 32, CORN firm. new Yellow, 65c.. old, 71c. to 72c. WHISKY steady at 18c. to 19c. AUGUSTA, Ga., Friday, Jan. 18. COTTON -- Sales to-day, 3,500 bales. Middling, 10 1E2c. to 10 1E2c. There is a good demand.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, SUNDAY Jan. 20 --Brig Jochin, for New-York to Galveston, has been towed into Pensacola.  SX 10,000 have been awarded. Vessel and cargo advertised for sale. Bark Pilgrim, lately ashore on Florida Reef, is now on the dry dock for repairs.  New-ORLEANS, Saturday, Jan. 19. COTTON quiet. sales to-day 2,500 bales, at like, for Middling, SUGAR quiet at 4 1E2c. to 5 1E4c. for fair to fully fair. MOLASSES, 22c. to 24c. FLOUR steady at  SX 4 50 to   SX 5 25 for supertine. CORN 60c. to 70c. PORK firm. mess  SX 18 50 to  SX 19. LAND in bbls., 11 1E4c. WHISKY, 16c. to  17c. FREIGHTS of Motion to Liverpool, 3E4d. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday Jan. 19.  To-day, Georgia seceded from the Union.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOBILE, Friday, Jan. 18. COTTON Sales to-day 3,500 bales at 10 e. to 10 c. for Middling. Sales of the week, 17,700 bales. receipts of the week, 32,500 bales against 35,910 bales in corresponding period last year. decreased receipts at this port, 161,195 bales. exports of the week, 20,290 bales. stock, 60,705 bales. Freight to Liverpool d.  to 7E8d.. to Havre, 2e. Sterling Exchange, 2  to 5 premium. Sight Exchange on New-York,  to 3E8 cent. premium. NEW-ORLEANS, Saturday, Jan. 19. COTTON -- Sales to-day, 8,500 bales, at 10 1E4c.11 1E4c.for Middling. SUGAR dull at 4 1E2c. to 5c. for fair. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday Jan. 18.  The Debate on the Crisis in the House has today been closed.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Jan. 18, 1861.  NOTICE TO MARINERS -- CHARLESTON HARBOR. -- According to intelligence received from reliable sources, three old schooners and a brig have been filled with stones, and sunk on Charleston Bar -- main ship channel -- which greatly endangers vessels attempting to ester that port. The steamship Nashville is said to have gone in by carefully passing between the obstructions. The report of the removal or displacement of the channel buoys, the quenching of the lights, and destruction of the range beacons, have also been authoritatively confirmed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday Jan. 17.  Mr. Holt has been nominated Secretary of War.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, THURSDAY, Jan. 17, 1861.  Steamship Revaly, Plummer, Padang Oct. 14, with mdse. to Wm. A. Sale  ES  Co. Bark Ann, Munro, Amoy Sept. 9, with teas, etc., to W.H. Bazard.  Jan. 14. passed an Am. ship steering N.N.E., with a bright, waist, showing a signal with red lull, white letter N., and white swallow tail. Same day, lat. 36 42. lon. 74 45, spoke bark Dency, of Boston, from Laguna for New-York. Bark Jacob Merrill, Foss, St. Marks 14 ds., with cotton and tobacco to Smallwood, Earl  ES  Co. Jan. 16. 6 1E4 A.M. during a thick fog, went ashore on the Point of Sandy Book. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Wednesday, Jan. 16. Schooner Lucy Amres, from New-York, is ashore at Tarpaulin Cove. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, Wednesday, Jan. 16. Sight Exchange on New-York declined 1 per cent, and is quoted at 6 per cent, premium for Missouri paper. CHICAGO, Wednesday, Jan. 16. Sight Exchange on New-York declined to 5 per cent, premium. CINCINNATI, Wednesday, Jan. 16. WHEAT advanced 3c. to 5c., with large export inquiry at  SX 1 05 to  SX 1 12. WHISKY declined 1E4c., but quotations are nominal at 13 1E4c. HOGS are firmer and in improved demand at  SX 6 10 to  SX 6 40. receipts today, 4,500. MESS PORK buoyant at  SX 16 50. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Tuesday, Jan. 15.  Today, a secession meeting will be held in this city. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Tuesday, Jan. 15. FLOUR firm. Howard-street and Ohio held at  SX 5 62 1E2. City Mills at  SX 5 50. WHEAT firm. Red, at  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 38. White, at  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 65. CORN advanced 3c.. Mixed 67c.. PROVISIONS firm. COFFEE steady, at 12 1E2c. to 13c. WHISKY steady at 19c. AUGUSTA, Tuesday, Jan. 15. COTTON -- Sales, to-day, 2,000 bales. market firm. CHARLESTON, Tuesday, Jan. 15. COTTON firm. sales, to-day, 660 bales. CHICAGO, Tuesday, Jan. 15. Exchange on New-York has declined to 6 cent.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK....MONDAY, Jan. 14.  Steamship R. R. Cuyler, Crocker, Savannah, with mdse. and passengers to H. B. Cromwell  ES  Co. Jan. 11, 8 P. M., 20 miles N. of Charleston, spoke U. S. sloop-of war Brooklyn, for Charleston. Jan. 13, exchanged signals with steamship Parkersburgh, bound S.  Schr. Eleanor B. Cromwell, of Provincetown, Lawson, Grand Cayman Dec. 28, with mahogany, etc., to master. Has experienced very heavy weather, split sails, etc. Has been 9 ds. N. of Hatteras, with heavy northerly gales. Dec 12, while taking in sail, part of the crew were badly frost-bitten. Left no Am. vessels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sunday, Jan. 13.  Reports received that the Pensacola Navy-yard has been seized by Secessionists.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Sunday Jan. 13.  Bark Warren A. Fisher, of and for Philadelphia, for New-York, in ballast. Was built in Eastport in 1853, is 365 tons burden, and rated A2. Went ashore on the morning of the 11th at 5 o'clock, and still remains. Was perfectly tight when last heard from. weather calm and cloudy, with prospect of snow. A telegraphic dispatch received by Messrs. Spofford, Tileston  ES  Co, dated Charleston, Jan. 13, states that the wind was blowing a sale from N. E., with a heavy sea on the Bar, and that the steamship Marion is detained.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday, Jan. 12.  Today, Mr. Seward spoke in the Senate in regard to the national troubles.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Friday, Jan. 11. COTTON -- Sales, to-day, 27,000 bales. The steamer's news caused an advance to 11 3E4c  to 12 1E4c. for Middling. SUGAR dull, at 4 1E2c. to 5 1E8c. MOLASSES, 23c. to 24c. FLOUR quiet, at  SX 5 62 1E4. CORN, 70C. to 76C. PORK quiet, at  SX 17 25 to  SX 17 50. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 11-16d. MONTGOMERY, Ala., Thursday, Jan. 10. COTTON easier, at 10c. to 10 1E2c. for Middling. MOBILE, Wednesday, Jan. 9. COTTON -- Sales, to-day, 8,500 bales, at 11c. for Middling. Market active and firm. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday, Jan. 11.  Alabama has seceded from the Union.  Secretary Thomas has resigned.  General Dix has been appointed Secretary of the Treasury.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Thurs., Jan. 10. FLOUR very dull at  SX 4 60 for Superfine. WHEAT dull. CORN firm. WHISKY dull at 14c. HOGS declined 10c. to 15c., market closing heavy at  SX 6 1 to  SX 6 35.Mess Pork in good demand at  SX 16 to  SX 16 25. LARD dull at 9 1E2c. BULK MEATS dull at 6c. to 8c.  PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, Jan. 10. FLOUR steady, at  SX 5 37E2 to  SX 5 62 1E2. WHEAT steady. white,  SX 1 45 to  SX 1 50. COFFEE advanced 1E4c,: Rio 11 1E2c. to 12 3E4c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday, Jan. 10.  Today, Florida and Mississippi have seceded from the Union.  The arsenals and forts of Louisiana are now controlled by the State Government.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, THURSDAY, Jan. 10, 1861.  Steamship Roanoke, Couch, Richmond and Norfolk, with mdse. and passengers to Ludlam  ES  Heineken. Brings to this port, the fires and second mates, and 14 seamen, belonging to Br. ship Emma, wrecked at New-Inlet, N.C., Dec. 28.  Ship George Hurlbut, Masson, Liverpool Nov. 22, with mdse. and 25 passengers to J.  ES  N. Smith  ES  Co. Experienced heavy westerly gales, carried away main yard, lost sails, etc.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 9.  The President has sent a special message to Congress.  The Star of the West, from New York with reinforcements, arrived at Fort Sumter.  Endeavoring to enter Charleston, it was fired upon from Morris Island and Fort Moultrie and was compelled to return.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NORFOLK, Jan. 9. Schr. Coermine, of Savannah, bound to New Bedford, put in distress, was seized by the Inspector for violating the Virginia Inspection laws.  NEW-ORLEANS, Jan. 9. -- The ship Cincinnatus, after discharging cargo, was taken on the Sectional Dock yesterday morning for repairs. She will be stripped, recaulked and newly coppered.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Jan. 8.  Secretary Thompson has resigned.  Reports received that North Carolina forts have been seized by the State Government.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, TUESDAY, Jan. 8. Ship Pampero, Lester, San Francisco Sept. 28, with mdse. to Willetts  ES  Co. Dec. 1, lat. 24, lon. 30 W., spoke ship Champion, Lamson, from San Francisco for New-York. Dec. 3, lat. 22 S., lon. 29 W., spoke Spanish bark Hoppatt, from River Plate for Havana. Dec. 11, off Cape St. Augustine, Brazil, passed a ship supposed to be the George, from San Francisco. Dec. 23, lat. 20 11, lon. 58 18, spoke ship John Stuart, from Callao for Hampton Roads. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday, Jan. 7.  Mr. Toombs today delivered a violent secession speech in the Senate.  Major Anderson's course in evacuating Fort Moultrie has been sustained by the House of Representatives.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Monday, Jan 7. FLOUR dull. Howard-street and Ohio,  SX 5 50. City Mills,  SX 5. WHEAT firm. Red,  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 36. White,  SX 1 40 to 1 60. CORN firm at 63c. to 66c. for new, and 68c. to 72c. for old White, PROVISIONS firmer. Mess Pork,  SX 17. LARD, 10 1E4c. COFFEE active at 12 1E2c. to 13c. WHISKY dull at 18c. to 19c. PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Jan. 7. FLOUR very firm at  SX 5 25 to  SX 5 50 for superfine. WHEAT steady. white  SX 1 45.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, SUNDAY, Jan. 6.  Maryland Governor Hicks has refused to convene the Maryland Legislature.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Jan. 5. -- The schooner Adda, of Milwaukee, hence for Aspinwall, Nov. 28, with a cargo of coal, sprung a leak Dec. 4. in lat. 36 25, lon. 70, and sunk. The Captain and crew were taken off by bark Linda Stewart, hence for Sagua la Grande, and landed at that port. The ship Rainbow is now on the large Sectional Dock for the purpose of being coppered. The bark Lucy Johnson is also on the small Sectional Dock. She will be stripped, recaulked and newly coppered. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Saturday, January 5.  Reports are received that the South Carolina Convention is adjourned.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Saturday, Jan. 5. FLOUR in good demand, at  SX 4 75 for Superfine. WHISKY dull at 13 1E2c.  PROVISIONS buoyant -- all articles higher, and holders demand an advance. MESS PORK,  SX 15 50. BULK PORK, 5 1E2c. to 7 1E2c. GREEN MEATS, 5c. to 7c. LARD, 9 1E2c., but holders are asking an advance of 1E4c., for all articles.  MOBILE, FRIDAY, Jan. 4. COTTON -- Sales to-day 3,500 bales at 11c. to 11 1E4c. for Middling. PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Jan, 5.  COFFEE, Rio at 12c. to 13 5E8c. WHISKY steady at 18c. to 18 1E2c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday, Jan. 4.  The President, having sent back the last communication of the South Carolina Commissioners unopened, they returned to Charleston.  The United States arsenal at Mobile has been taken by local troops.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Friday, Jan. 4. COTTON firm. sales to-day 10,000 bales, at 11etc..  to 12 1E4c. for Middlings. Sales of the week 70,000 bales. receipts do, 60,500 bales, against 68,000 bales the same time last year. receipts less than last year 220,500 bales: receipts at all Southern ports less than last year 543,000 bales. exports 48,000 bales. total exports 717,500 bales. stock in port 854,500 bales. SUGAR steady at 4 3E4c. to 5 1E8c., for fair to fully fair. MOLASSES23c. to 24c. FLOUR  SX 5 for superfine, WHEAT  SX 1 62 3E4  SX 175. CORN, yellow mixed, 71c. to 76c. COFFEE, sales of the week 10,000 bags, at 10c to 12c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, Jan. 2. FLOUR -- Holders demand an advance of 12 1E2c.. Superfine  SX 5 12 1E2 to  SX 5. WHEAT buoyant. sales, 5 000 bush. Reg, at  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 32. White,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 55. CORN firm. sales, 6,000 bush., at 70c.. new at 60c. WHISKY firm, at 18c. to 18 1E8c. BALTIMORE, Wednesday, Jan. 2. FLOUR dull. Howard-street and Ohio,  SX 5 50. City Mills,  SX 5. WHEAT,  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 60. CORN firm. New White, 61c. to 64c.. Yellow, 70c. to 73c. PROVISIONS firm. MESS PORK,  SX 16 50: Rump,  SX 13. LARD, 10 1E4c. COFFEE dull, at 12b  to 13c. WHISKY firm, at 19c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 2, 1861.  Yesterday, two war vessels were ordered to Charleston.  Today, Fort Pulaski, at Savannah, was taken by order of the Governor of Georgia.   </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON, Wednesday, Jan. 2.  Intimations have appeared in several papers, of late, that the State authorities of South Carolina have placed restrictions upon the Charleston Telegraph Office, and otherwise control the lines. I wish to correct this impression, and to state that the authorities of South Carolina have not yet found it necessary to interfere in any manner with the business of this Company. J. KENDALL. General Superintendent. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday, Dec. 31, 1860.  Mr. Benjamin, of Louisiana, delivered a violent secession speech in the Senate.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Monday, Dec. 31, 1860.  Ship Dreadnought, Samuels, Liverpool Dec. 2, with mdse. and 275 passengers to David Ogden. Experienced frightful weather from the westward Dec. 10, blew away the close-reefed topsails and storm-staysail. ship lay 40 hours without canvas.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, Dec. 31, 1860.  FLOUR very firm, at  SX 5 12 1E2 to  SX 5 37 1E2 for superfine. WHEAT in fair demand. white at  SX 1 40 to  SX 1 55. red  SX 1 30 to  SX 1 35. CORN active, and advanced. all yellow at 68c. to 70c.. new 5 1E2c. COPPER firm, and stock much reduced, at 11 1E2c. to 13 1E2c.</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
