<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, DEC. 31. Mr. CYRUS W. FIELD's plan for establishing telegraphic communication between the seat of Government and the different naval and military stations on the Southern coast has received the cordial approval of Gen. MCCLELLAN, who earnestly advises its being carried into execution by the Government. It is understood that the President and Cabinet fully approve of the measure, and the enterprise will be commenced at an early day. To bring Fortress Monroe and Newport's News in telegraphic communication with Washington less than thirty miles of submarine cable are needed, and this part of the line will be completed at an early day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 30.  Senator WILSON's bill affecting sutlerships empowers the commissioned officers of each regiment to elect a sutler. It prescribes that the articles to be sold by the sutler shall be determined by a Board consisting of the Quartermaster, Commissary and Inspector-Generals of the army. It prescribes that any sutler charging higher than the approved rates, or who shall give false weight, or in any other way cheat the soldiers, shall upon proof of the fact before the Colonel, Quartermaster and Commissary of the regiment, be fined fifty dollars, one-half of the fine accruing to the informer, and all his property confiscated to the use of the Government.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 29.  A private of the Seventh Wisconsin Regiment was arrested and sent home to be tried for a murder committed in Iowa County. He was identified by means of a daguerreotype. Over thirty vessels are now waiting in the Lower Potomac for a dark night or fog, that they may pass the rebel batteries. They are mostly laden with forage, provisions and coal. Among them is the new steam ferry-boat for the Georgetown ferry. One day last week, the body of a Virginia Lieutenant was taken from the river near Budd's Ferry by the pickets of the First Sickles Regiment, and interred with the honors of war. In his pockets were money and other valuables.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 28.  Applicants for bounty and back pay of deceased soldiers should remember that their claims are adjusted as rapidly as the inadequate clerical force of the Second Auditor can attend to them. In all cases when the papers presented are insufficient, the applicants are notified immediately. Those who hear nothing from their papers may know that they are correct, and their claims will be allowed as soon as practicable.  CHICAGO, Sunday, Dec. 28. The Cairo operator says that a fight is going on at Paducah, Ky., to-day, but that the Adjutant-General refuses to allow reports to be sent. We will probably hear something to-morrow. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 27.  A board of medical inspectors have examined MCCALL's, SMITH's and PORTER's divisions, and found them in good sanitary condition. Not one case of typhus fever was found, and but half a dozen cases of typhoid, among near forty thousand men. There are some cases of remittent bilious fever, caused by malaria from the river. The regiments from the country are found to suffer most from sickness. It is a singular fact that those regiments which the Sanitary Commission predicted would be most afflicted with disease, are most healthy, indicating that the expensive prophecies of that charitable association are of little practical value.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 26.  The United States Sanitary Commission has just dispatched an Inspector to Hilton Head and Beaufort with 130 boxes of hospital stores, including 1,260 blankets, hospital garments, etc., and vaccine virus for the entire force. Visitors at the camps in Virginia are astonished to find them laid out in such beauty and neatness, and to see that amid the trials of a soldier's life, so much care and taste is displayed in the ornamentation of their quarters. With rare exceptions the streets between the rows of tents are neatly graded, with drains on either side, and with tent drainage communicating with them. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Dec. 25. The Cabinet is alleged to have had a special session to-day, to consider the demands of Lord LYONS in behalf of the British Government in the Trent affair. These demands are said to be an apology, and the restitution of MASON and SLIDELL to British custody. It is understood that our Government is ready to disavow the act of Capt. WILKES, and to deliver up MASON and SLIDELL, if that be the only means of purchasing peace with England. but, as a condition of this disavowal and restitution, it is said that our Government will require Great Britain to concede this in regard to the right of search at sea.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Dec. 24. Extensive preparations have been made in nearly all the camps for the celebration of Christmas. Dinners, fetes, balls, and games are to be the order of the day and night. Many officers have obtained three days' furlough to visit their homes. Gen. SICKLES left for New-York to-night. The President and members of the Cabinet will proceed down the Potomac to-morrow, in the steamer Pensacola, as far as Indian Head. The Presidential party will visit Gens. HOOKER's and SICKLES' Divisions, returning in the evening. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Dec. 23.  CHARLOTTESTOWN, P.E.I., Thursday, Dec. 19, Via PICTON, N.S., Friday, Dec. 20. The submarine cable across the Straits of Northumberland, connecting Prince Edward's Island with the Continent, and belonging to the Newfoundland Telegraph Company, is again broken, and it is believed cannot be repaired. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 22.  The House Judiciary Committee will take up at its next meeting the subject referred to them by Mr. GURLEY's resolution, as to whether the Government's Telegraphic Censor interferes in the transmission of dispatches to the Northern Press beyond what is or was required by the military authorities. A large number of newspaper men are already subpoenaed. Some rich developments are anticipated. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 21.  A REBEL MAIL FOUND. This morning a small ducking schooner, belonging to Capt. HEWITT, of Alexandria, was searched by Lieut. WILLIAMS, of the brig Perry, and a rebel mail, containing a large number of letters, was found concealed in a small boat. Some were written in cipher, others had only the names of the writers and others in Alexandria referred to, thus written. HEWITT was placed under arrest. This exhibition of rebel enterprise in Alexandria excites much interest. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Charleston, December 20.  Sixteen vessels were sunk to-day at the mouth of Charleston Harbor.  WASHINGTON, Dec. 20.  A resolution offered in the Washington City Council favoring the abolition of Slavery in the District of Columbia, was laid on the table by a vote of nine to four. The Navy Department has sent orders to have the Constellation, at Portsmouth, and the Macedonian, at Boston, when they shall have been refitted, to cruise in foreign seas, for the protection of our commerce from privateers. Both are sailing vessels. Similar orders will be sent to the steamer Wyoming in the Pacific squadron to cruise on the coast of China.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Dec. 19.  CONGRESS AND THE HOLIDAYS. The question was to-day informally discussed among a number of Senators as to the propriety of an adjournment for two weeks, and the sentiment was very generally expressed that, owing to the present alarming condition of affairs abroad, Congress ought not to adjourn for more than three or four days. The extraordinary Proclamation of Gen. PHELPS at Ship Island excited the indignation of the President. Its revolutionary and fanatical spirit, and total disregard of the policy of the Administration, render his instant removal imperative.  The only excuse offered for Gen. PHELPS is that he is crazy. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Dec. 18.  A Cabinet meeting was held to-day, at which the English question was discussed -- of course informally, as the nature of the dispatches brought by the Royal messenger have not been divulged. There was but one sentiment prevalent, and that was that no quarrel with England must be permitted to interfere at this moment to stay the reduction of the Southern rebels. The Government is probably satisfied that the clamor for a war with England originates with, and is propagated by, sympathizers with the Southern rebellion.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW York, Dec. 17, from Liverpool, Dec. 4.  At a recent banquet at Rochdale, Mr. BRIGHT made an elaborate speech on American affairs.  He strongly condemned warlike feelings and scouted the idea that the American Cabinet resolved to pick a quarrel with England.  He made an eloquent peroration in favor of the North.  A letter from Gen. SCOTT, in favor of maintaining friendly relations between England and America attracts much attention. The export of arms, ammunition and lead has been prohibited. The Paris Patrie has an editorial foreshadowing at disposition of France to recognize the South, if England sets the example. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Monday Dec. 16.  On Thanksgiving Day -- the 28th ult. -- a large party of the workmen engaged in constructing the Pacific Telegraph from the western borders to Salt Lake City, under the direction of Mr. CREIGHTON, arrived at Omaha on their return. Among them was SAMUEL P. STARR, of this city, who reached home on Thursday last. Mr. STARR, was one engaged in the practical work of construction, in the different branches, and he gives an interesting account of the manner in which the enterprise was conducted. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Sunday, Dec. 15.  The Court-martial in the case of Col. KERRIGAN met to-day, on the corner of Pennsylvania-avenue and Seventeenth-street. Gen. CASEY presides, and Col. MCCORL is Judge-Advocate. EDMUND L. HEARNE, of New-York, appeared in behalf of the prisoner. The charges are five in number, and they and the specifications, when formal verbiage is taken from them, include: FIRST CHARGE -- Reputed neglect of duty. Specification -- That from June 28 to Oct. 18, in New-York and Virginia, he failed and neglected to give to his officers and men practical or theoretical instructions in the tactics and in the school of the battalion and company. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Saturday, Dec. 14.  The soldiers have not been paid since the beginning of the war, and on this account are dissatisfied. A great desire to desert is manifested, many of the men being Unionists impressed into service.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Friday, Dec. 13.  BALLOON RECONNOISSANCE ON THE LOWER Yesterday, a protracted balloon reconnoissance was made from the river opposite Gen. HOOKER's headquarters. While the balloon was up, the rebel batteries fired at it with shell, many of which burst directly under it, though none within less than 200 feet. As the shells exploded the occupant of the car defiantly waved the American flag. A deserter from the rebel forces on the Lower Potomac crossed to Gen. HOOKER's Division yesterday and says the rebel army between the river batteries and Manassas Junction numbers twenty-five or thirty thousand, is well armed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Thursday, Dec. 12.  A branch telegraph line is proposed to extend from Cedar Keys to Key West and the Tortugas. The length of the main wire will be about fifteen hundred miles, and the branch for Cedar Keys to Key West and Tortugas and Tortugas about four hundred miles. About two hundred prisoners of war in Washington and the Northern cities have been released by order of the Government, and will be forwarded from Fortress Monroe under a flag of truce. Each prisoner gave his parole not to take up arms against the United States Government until exchanged, and it is understood that each is to procure an exchange from among our prisoners in the South.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Wednesday, Dec. 11. Mr. CYRUS W. FIELD has been in the city for several days, consulting with the Government in reference to establishing a line of telegraphic communication from Washington, to extend along the lines of the coast. He proposes that the wires be extended to Fortress Monroe and Newport News from our present lines, and thence by submarine cable across to Cape Charles, and along the coast to Hatteras Inlet, Bull Bay and Port Royal. Then as soon as Fernandina shall be taken, that it be extended to that port and crossing the peninsula of Florida to Cedar Keys, and thence to Fort Pickens, Ship Island, and Chandeleur Island.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PROCEEDINGS OF THE REPUBLICAN CAUCUS WASHINGTON, Monday, Dec 9. THE REPUBLICAN CAUCUS. The caucus of the Republicans last night was attended by about forty members. A large number have deliberately determined not to compromise themselves by engaging in a mere party movement in regard to the policy of the war. Of course the most ultra men of the party were present. All newspaper men and outsiders were carefully excluded, and I am consequently enabled to give to the public only a sketch of the proceedings. My informant in some cases declining to furnish me with the names of speakers, though giving me the substance of the debate. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Monday Dec. 9.  Correspondence of the New-York Times. GREAT SALT LAKE CITY, Saturday, Nov. 16, 1861. The Salt Lake country does not seem to be a favorite place of residence for National officers, even those whose destinies are officially connected, for a term, with the Territory. A short time ago, we had not a single United States Judge in Utah, though her complement was full as to appointments, each incumbent being absent on business or pleasure, or both -- one at the East, the other two at the West. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Saturday, Dec. 7. FLOUR firm. Wheat dull. 70 1E4c. TO 70 1E2c. for No. 1. 64 1E4c. TO 64 1E4c. for No. 2, in store. CORN dull. mixed in store 23 3E4c. OATS steady. Receipts -- 4,900 bbls. Flour. 39,000 bushels Wheat. 21,000 bushels Corn. Exchange on New-York unaltered. OSWEGO, Saturday, Dec. 7. FLOUR steady. Wheat in limited demand, and the market is without material change. sales of 3,000 bush. Chicago Spring at 99c.. 2,500 bush. do. at 98c., afloat. 500 bush. choice Canada Club at  SX 1 05. CORN and OATS quiet. No receipts by Lake. Canal Exports -- 8,600 bush. Wheat. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Dec. 7.  TREASURY DEPARTMENT.  Regulations relating to property found in disloyal States.  An inventory of all horses, mules and other stock, vehicles of transportation, and other property will be carefully made, and a copy transmitted to the Secretary of the Treasury signed by such agent. A record of all products taken possession of will be made, and those of each plantation kept distinct. When prepared for shipment, the packages from the several plantations will be plainly marked and numbered, so as to be easily distinguished. An account of all provisions, of whatever character, found on such plantation, will be taken.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Dec. 6.  TREASURY DEPARTMENT, Saturday, Nov. 30, 1861. The Secretary of the Treasury has just issued the following general regulations relative to securing and disposing of the property found within the territory now occupied by the United States forces in the disloyal States.  There shall be appointed by the Secretary of the Treasury agents to reside at such points or places as are occupied by the forces of the United States, whose duties shall be to secure and prepare for market the cotton and such other products and property as may be found or brought within the lines of the army or under the control of the Federal authorities.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Dec. 5.  ST. JOHN, N.F., Nov. 19. -- The brig Salman, from New-York about Oct. 22, went ashore at Cape Spear, three miles from this port, early on the morning of the 17th lost., and became a total loss, no cargo being saved. Three persons were drowned. She drifted on the calm, after a heavy blow, when an unusually heavy swell caused the above result. The S. was built at Maitland. N.S., 173 tons, rated A 2, and owned by J. Crow and others, of Maitland.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Wednesday Dec. 4.  The Message of President LINCOLN was telegraphed yesterday to all parts of the loyal States. The Message contains 7,578 words, and was all received in this City in 1 hour and 32 minutes, a feat of telegraphing unparalleled in the Old or New World. Mr. SANFORD, the President of the American Telegraph Company, and his able Superintendents and subordinate operators, are entitled to the highest credit for thus accomplishing such a work in such a short space of time. The Message was manifolded by the Associated Press Agency in this City, and placed in the hands of the printers of the various newspapers in less than two hours.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, TUESDAY, Dec. 3.  U.S. steam transport Patapsco, Bearse, Port Royal 6 ds. 1st inst., off Charleston, spoke U.S. gunboat Penguin, cruising. The Patapsco sailed a few hours after the steamship McClellan from Port Royal. Nothing new had transpired of interest since her sailing. The health of the troops was good. French steam gunboat Gassendi, Commander Gautier, Halifax 4 ds. She mounts 6 guns, and has a crew of 127 men.  CHICAGO, Saturday, Nov. 30. FLOUR dull and heavy. WHEAT firm, at 70c. TO  70 1E2c. for No. 1, 65c. TO 66 1E2c, for No. 2, in store. CORN decline 1E2c. Receipts, 6,700 bbls. Flour, 52,000 bushels Wheat, 35,000 bushels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, MONDAY Dec. 2. Received by Central Railroad for New-York, 1,361 boxes Cheese, 25 bbls. and 636 bags Wheat, 6,204 bbls. Flour, 300 bbls. Highwines. For Boston, 7,095 bbls. Flour, 250 bbls. Highwines. Shipped by tows to New-York, Nov. 29, 177,200 bushels Corn, 258,800 bushels Wheat, 8,800 bushels Oats, 38,000 bushels Feed, 18,200 bushels Barley. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Sunday Dec. 1.  The Secretary of the Navy reported today that 160 prizes have been captured since the commencement of the blockade, by 43 vessels of the squadron.  ALBANY, Saturday, Nov. 30. FLOUR dull. WHEAT -- No sales. RYE -- Sales 2,400 bushels at 84 1E2c. for 56 pounds. CORN -- No sales of moment. OATS -- Sales at 43 1E2c. for car lots, afloat. BARLEY -- Nothing afloat. unsold in store 3,000 bushels State four-rowed at 70c.. 3,500 bushels do at the Central Railroad at 63c., and 7,500 bushels Canada West, in store, at 80c. HOPS -- Sales 30 bales prime Otsegos at 19c. TO 20c. WHISKY steady at 19 1E2c.: sales 100 bbls.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Saturday, Nov. 30 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT dull and no sales. CORN dull and unchanged. sales 6,000 bush. at 40c. WHISKY steady. sales 120 bbls. at 16 1E2c. TO 17c. FREIGHTS dull. Wheat to Rochester 6c. Imports -- 8,000 bbls. Flour, 40,000 bush. Wheat, 15,000 bush. Corn. Exports -- 24,000 bush. Wheat, 16,000 bush. Corn. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Friday, Nov. 29. FLOUR dull at  SX 5 37 1E2. WHEAT -- Sales 6,000 bushels at  SX 1 33 TO  SX 1 36 for red, and  SX 1 43 TO  SX 1 45 for white. CORN -- Sales 5,000 bushels at 63c. MESS PORK unchanged. LARD, 9c. TO 9 1E2c. Rio COFFEE, 16 1E2. TO 17c. WHISKY dull.  OSWEGO, Friday, Nov. 29. FOUR unchanged, but in moderate demand for the interior and Eastern trade. WHEAT quiet and generally held above the views of buyers. sales last night, 1,800 bushels Red State, at  SX 1 08. 2,500 bushels Red Winter Ohio, at  SX 1 15. and 1,200 bushels Ohio, at  SX 1 21. CORN unchanged. sales, 7,200 bushels Ohio, at 46c. Other grains quiet, Lake imports -- 650 bbls. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LIVERPOOL, Thursday, Nov. 21. COTTON. -- The sales for two days have been 14,000 bales, including 5,000 bales to speculators and exporters. The market closed firm at unchanged quotations. BREADSTUFFS. -- The market remains steady. PROVISIONS. -- The market is quiet but steady. LONDON, Thursday, Nov. 21. CONSOLS 94 1E2 for money. AMERICAN STOCKS. -- Sates of Illinois Central shares at 39 3E4 discount. Erie, 27 3E4 TO 28 1E4. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  The Penguin has captured the schooner Albion, of Nassau, N.P., with a cargo valued at  SX 100,000.  The privateer Sumter escaped the Iroquois which was watching for her off Martinique.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LYNCHBURG. Monday, Nov. 11, via NEW-ORLEANS. A bridge of about 260 feet span, of the East Tennessee Railroad, ten miles beyond Bristol, was burned about 4 o'clock this morning by the Unionists. A half a mile of the track was also destroyed. It is reported that several other bridges are burnt on the road south of Knoxville. No trains are arriving, and the wires being destroyed, makes it difficult to ascertain the extent of damage. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NASHVILLE, Monday, Nov. 11. Five railroad bridges were burned in East Tennessee on Friday night by the Union men, and two on the Georgia State Railroad, over Chickamauga Creek, Hamilton County, heretofore reported. One also on the East Tennessee and Georgia road, over Hiawassee River, in Bradley County. Five minutes after the guard had passed through, the whole bridge was in flames, showing the use of combustibles. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Sunday Nov. 11. The Lynchburgh bridge, about two hundred feet in span, on the East Tennessee railway, ten miles beyond Bristol, was burned about 4 o'clock this morning by the Unionists, and a half mile of the track destroyed. It is also reported that several other bridges have been burnt on this road south of Knoxville. No trains arriving, and the wires having been torn down, the extent of the damage is yet difficult to be ascertained. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Rebel batteries have been bombarded by Fort Pickens and the ships-of-war Niagara and Richmond.  ALBANY, Friday, Nov. 22 -- P.M. FLOUR steady. WHEAT -- sales 2,500 bushels Milwaukee Club at  SX 1 25, and car lots at  SX 1 22 for State Spring.  SX 1 27 for red Winter.  SX 1 24 for mixed State.  SX 1 46 for white Michigan. Sales 1,500 bushels RYE, in car lots, at 84c., delivered. OAYS a shade weaker, with little doing. sales 10,000 bushels State, afloat, at 46 1E2c. TO 47c. There is more doing in BARLEY. receipts moderate. sales of 7,000 bushels two-rowed at 63c. TO 65c.. 7,800 bushels Bay Quinte, 75c.. 1,000 bushels Winter, 61 1E2c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  P. T. Barnum reports that in August last he succeeded in bringing to the Museum, two living white whales from Labrador. Both died within two days.  Since August two more whales were brought but both died. A fifth living whale has now arrived here, and will remain in the Museum as long as he lives. Perhaps this will be but a few hours, but in order to prolong his life as long as possible, Barnum has, at an expense of  SX 7,000, laid a six-inch cast-iron pipe from the river to the Museum, and by means of a powerful steam-engine working night and day, the whale is constantly supplied with pure salt water at the rate of three hundred gallons per minute. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  The pirate Nashville has entered the British port of Southampton.  PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, Nov. 21. FLOUR firm. sales 3,500 bbls. Superfine at  SX 5 62 1E3. WHEAT firm. sales 12,000 bush. Red at  SX 1 34 TO  SX 136. White,  SX 145 TO  SX 1 53. CORN quiet. sates 3,000 bush, at 63c. TO 65c. OATS, 41c. MESS PORK declined 25c., at  SX 14 25. COFFEE -- Rio unchanged. WHISKY dull, at 21c. TO 21 1E2c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Twenty-five vessels, laden with stone, are now sailing from New-Bedford to be sunk at the mouth of Charleston Harbor.  Rebel troops have disbanded in Accomac and Northampton County, Virginia.  The population of those counties have returned their allegiance to the United States.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  To-day, American ship Harvey Birch was burnt at sea by the pirate Nashville.   It has been agreed that all official documents of whatever kind, emanating from the Departments, shall be delivered to the general agent of the Associated Press at Washington, -- and to him alone, -- for prompt and simultaneous transmission to such papers as may desire to receive the, by telegraph. This will put an end at once to complaints or suspicions of favoritism on the one side, and of bad faith or the betrayal of confidence on the other. It will relieve the Secretaries from the annoyance of being dogged every day by an army of reporters.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND.  To-day, President Jefferson Davis delivered a message to the C. S. Congress.  BY TELEGRAPH TO QUEENSTOWN. LIVERPOOL, Thursday, Nov. 7. COTTON -- The sales yesterday and to-day reach 35,000 bales. The market is firmer, with an upward tendency, and a trifling advance on all qualities. The sales to speculators and exporters reached 17,000 bales. Middling Orleans is quoted at 12 1E4 d. BREADSTUFFS -- The market is quiet and steady. Corn very dull, and declined 6d. TO 1s. quarter. Mixed 32s. 6d. PROVISIONS -- The market is dull. PRODUCE -- Resin advancing. common, 14s. 3d.  TO  14s. 6d. Spirits Turpentine firmer.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  AN APPEAL FOR THE WORKMEN OF BALTIMORE. A delegation of prominent citizens of Baltimore have visited Washington to make an appeal in behalf of the workingmen of that city. They say:  QN By the violence and factious opposition of a treasonable minority, Baltimore has been involved in disaster and distress beyond what is due to the mere existence of a state of war, and their troubles have been still further aggravated by the disabled condition of the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, the principal artery of their trade and source of their prosperity.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  The organization of a brigade of loyal Virginians, which was announced to have been begun recently, is progressing rapidly. Along the Potomac and in Washington are over a thousand refugees, and the suggestion has met with their hearty cooperation. Over a dozen men are engaged in recruiting, and already over six hundred Virginians have enrolled their names. In Alexandria the work is progressing well, and within a for night one regiment will be in the field. Two infantry and one cavalry regiment will be successfully recruited for the service of the Government. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday, Nov. 15. The volunteer service now numbers four hundred and eighty thousand men, leaving but twenty thousand more enlistments to reach the number authorized by Congress.   Gen. BURNSIDE arrived in the city this morning from Annapolis. MOSES H. GRINNELL and FRANCIS B. CUTTING are in the city. Gov. ANDREWS, of Massachusetts, arrived this morning, and during the day visited the War Department. Col. FITZ HENRY WARREN, of Iowa, reached town to-day. His command is in Missouri. The Naval Ordnance Department is unusually active in the manufacture of projectiles. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  The Navy Department has recently extended the time for receiving students at the Naval Academy at Newport, R.I., to the 30th inst. Vacancies exist in many Congressional Districts.  No notice can be taken of applications made by candidates directly to the Department, as the law gives their nomination to Members of Congress. The law does not authorize appointments to be made by either the President or Secretary of the Navy, and there is no way to secure an appointment, excepting through a nomination by the Member of Congress from the District in which the applicant actually resides. Candidates are required to be between 14 and 18 years.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  The proposals to furnish the Government with beef cattle on the hoof were opened to-day by the Commissary Department. The advertisement called for three lots of four thousand cattle each, to be delived by the 30th of November, or as soon thereafter as the Government may direct, at Washington, at Harrisburgh and at Chambersburgh or York. The bids for Washington ranged from  SX 3 30 to  SX 5 01. But three bidders were below  SX 4, and the lowest prices offered at which the bidders responded were  SX 3 70 and  SX 3 90. For the Harrisburgh lot, the bids ranged from  SX 3 39 to  SX 6 --  SX 3 55 being the lowest sum in which the bidder responded.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  SUPERINTENDENT OF GOVERNMENT TELEGRAPHS. ANSON STAGER, of Ohio, having received the military appointment of General Superintendent of the Government Telegraph, has, in accordance with his instructions, entered upon the organization of that Department. Thus the Government, under this popular and efficient gentleman, will soon have in operation a complete system of telegraphs for the transmission and reception of official intelligence from all available important points. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  The vigorous meaqsures set on foot by the new Administration, for the suppression of the slave trade, have already succeeded in reducing that infamouts traffic to its last extremity.  It was one of the first points to which Mr. Lincoln and Mr. Seward gave their attention, and they have followed it up with vigor and success.  The meeting of the United States Marshals, some weeks since, did a great deal to infuse vigor and harmony into their action, and the conviction last week of Captain Gordon, will satisfy the parties who have hitherto grown rich on the profits of this nefarious trade, that the law is no longer to be a dead letter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LOUISEVILLE.  An interview with exchange prisoner Mr. P. H. Lippert, of the twenty-fourth Illinois Regiment, who was taken prisoner some months ago, about twenty miles from Centerville, Missouri, while acting as a messenger bearing dispatches.  With twenty other Union prisoners he was lodged in a horse-thief jail at Bloomfield, for nearly a month.  This place was an apartment 16 by 18 feet in dimensions, and 7 feet high, with two air holes on two sides.  In this cage the twenty were cooped during the hottest weather, without any effort being made to remove their excrement.  Their food was dough and water, and they were never once taken into fresh air.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  How to deal with slaves in the Southern States must speedily become a practical question.  Hitherto it has been mainly a theme for speculation.  The landing of troops uppon the Southern coast, however, in the very midst of the densest slave population, and in the heart of the Cotton region, where the treatment of slaves is the most severe, and their desire to escape the strongest, will compel prompt and decisive action on the subject.  WASHIGNTON.  Rebel commissioners Slidell and Mason, on the British mail steamer Trent, were captured by the U. S. war sloop San Jacinto.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORTRESS MONROE, Thursday, Nov. 7. By a flag of truce, just from Norfolk, we have news of the fleet, but provokingly meagre, as the only person who came down was bound by parole not to reveal any particulars. The steamer Union, with a cargo of horses and stores, and another transport, whose name is not given, were lost during the gale, one at Kill Devil Shoal and the other on Rogues' Beach, on the coast of North Carolina. The crews of both vessels, 73 in number, are now prisoners at Raleigh, N.C. It is not known whether any were lost, but 15 horses were saved.  The above reached Norfolk, to-day, by telegraph. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SPRINGFIELD, MISSOURI.  Today, there was an engagement at Belmont.  WASHINGTON.  The United States squadron to-day captured the forts at Port Royal entrance.  The frigate Santee destroyed privateer Royal Yacht off Galveston.   CINCINNATI, Wednesday, Nov. 6. The operator at Camp Tompkins at that time reported lighting going on at Gauley Bridge, but gave no particulars, and immediately afterwards the wires were broken. The Kanawha River line was working to Camp Enyart, twelve miles above Charleston, on Saturday, but nothing was known there of the affair at Gauley.  
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Nov. 6.  Gen. McClellan heartily approves the proposition for an exchange of prisoners.  This has been his sentiment from the start and the majority of the Cabinet have always taken the same side.  Gen. McClellan's views are sustained by his confidential friend, the distinguished Ex-Attorney-General, Edwin M. Stanton, who, notwithstanding his connection with the Buchanan Administration, now maintains, as during his association with that Adminstration, the most decided and uncompromising Union doctrines.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Monday, Nov. 4.  Gen. FLOYD opened fire on Gen. ROSECRANS' forces yesterday morning, from two points -- one opposite Gauley Bridge, and the other opposite Camp Tompkins. The telegraph office, and the Quartermaster's store, are no doubt destroyed.  The enemy has heavy guns and a large body of infantry. Gen. FLOYD's forces opposite Camp Tompkins are not less than 4,000. How many of the rebels are at Gauley Bridge and four miles this side is not known. Telegraphic communication by the Kanawha line is interrupted. There has been no communication by telegraph with Gen. ROSECRANS' headquarters since Friday afternoon. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  DISPATCHES FOR EUROPE. -- The steamship City of Baltimore, which sailed from this port early Sunday morning for Liverpool, will arrive off Cape Race on Wednesday morning, and our merchants wishing to end messages to Europe later than those taken by her mails, can have them forwarded by telegraph by leaving them with GEORGE STOKER, Commercial Agent, No. 145 Broadway, up to 6 P.M., Tuesday.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  The pickets of the New-York Thirty-second we been extended to Anandale, six miles fromtheir camp near Alexandria. They found the bodies of three negroes near their outposts in an advanced state of decomposition. Accounts by telegraph, up to 4 o'clock this afternoon, report all quiet on the entire line of the Potomac. A reconnoissance was made yesterday by Gen. SICKLES and Staff, accompanied by a squad of Indiana cavalry, along the shore of the Potomac, about forty miles from Washington, when they were fired on by a rebel battery on the Virginia shore. One of the shots fell short, and another passed over them.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  To-day, Gen Fremont was removed from command in the West.  The rebel steamer Bermuda, laden with cotton for Liverpool, successfully ran the blockade today at Savannah.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday, Oct. 31. NEWS FROM CENTREVILLE. Yesterday Gen. BUTTERFIELD dispatched Brig ade-Quartermaster NORTON with ten wagons and an escort of the New-York Forty-fourth to Shreve's Farm, four miles northwest of Fall's Church and west of the Leesburgh Pike, to obtain forage. A short distance north of Fall's Church they captured a rebel picket, who had left his post to forage for whisky. Capt. NORTON at once sent him to headquarters, though he learned from the prisoner that the rebel pickets were stationed not far back of SHREVE's place. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  To-day, General Winfield Scott retired.  General George McClellan has been appointed Commander-in-Chief.  PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, Oct. 30. The extensive factory on the corner of Twelfth and Washington streets, belonging to the estate of CRAIG, was burnt this afternoon. A number of floors were occupied by various contractors of army cloths, haversacks, etc. A large amount of goods were saved, but the loss to the contractors will be serious. The loss by the destruction of the building, amounts to  SX 20,000, but is insured. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Wednesday, Oct. 30. An accident occurred last night on the Northern Central Railroad, near York. The train ran over a cow, smashing the cars. Two passengers were killed and several wounded. One of the killed is named VALENTINE, and belongs to this city. The name of the other is unknown.  He is a man of about 35 years of age, with the initials of E.V. on his watch. He had in his possession one of PERHAM's Excursion tickets, for New-York to Baltimore and back. He is of fair complexion, with blue eyes, light hair and moustache, and goatee of the same color. He has also an anchor in India ink on his left arm.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Oct. 29 -- Arr. steamer Kensington, Philadelphia. ship Rambler, Liverpool. brig P.R. Curtis, from Sagua.  POOLESVILLE, Tuesday, Oct. 29, 1861. It is now a week since the battle took place between the opposing forces which met this side of Leesburgh. During that time many versions of the affair have been given, all more or loss incorrect, and the country has been balancing between the blame which certain correspendents insist should fall upon Gen. STONE and the unbounded praise which the same parties lavish upon the late Col. BAKER.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MOVEMENTS AT EDWARDS' FERRY, Thursday, Oct. 24 -- P.M. Having completed the list of the wounded, in the hospitals at Camp Observation and Poolesville, the author hastened down to see what was going on. The frequent firing from this direction indicated that a battle was progressing on the Virginia side opposite to this place on Sunday, the day before the action near Conrad's Ferry. During Sunday night, the Second New-York State Militia crossed over the river at this point, for the purpose, as was supposed, of holding the Ferry on the opposite bank of the Potomac. They soon commenced scouting, but met with only a few of the rebels. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>POOLESVILLE.  The list of wounded, which, in a less correct form, has been sent by telegraph through the Associated Press: OCT. 21, 1861. 2d Lieut., F. Wade, 1st California, Co. D, shoulder. Private A.F. Hooper, 1st California, Co. A, side. Private G.N. Hooper, 1st Cal., Co. A, shoulder, (dead.) Private S. Randal, 1st Cal., Co. D, shoulder, (dead.) Private C. Schaefer, 1st Cal., Co. C, shoulder. Private F. Ellis, 1st Cal., Co. A, shoulder. Private W. Brunt, 1st California, Co. G, left eye. Private J. Stearnbuck, 1st California, Co. G, leg. Private W.F. Holland, 1st California, Co. G, leg. Private W.F. Poole, 15th Massachusetts, Co. H, side. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  To-day there was brilliant success of National troops under Gen. Kelley at Romney.  The situation in the vicinity of Washington continues much the same as reported yesterday. The most important military movement has been the extension of the picket lines of FRANKLIN'S Division a mile beyond Annandale, on the Little River Turnpike, leading direct to Fairfax Court House. The rebel steamer Page was yesterday again cruising on the Lower Potomac, but was closely watched by two or three National gunboats. The rebels threw several shells, one to the Maryland shore, more by way of testing the range of their guns, probably.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SPRINGFIELD, MISSOURI.  To-day there was a gallant charge of the Fremont guard, under Maj. Zagonyi, against a superior body of rebels.  WASHINGTON, Friday, Oct. 25. The following list of wounded in the engagement of Tuesday, at Edwards' Ferry, was received to-day at headquarters, from Pooleville, by telegraph: FIRST CALIFORNIA REGIMENT. Lieut.-Col. Wistar, in the right elbow joint. Capt. Lewis Biensall, Co. K, contused wound of the back. Lieut. Robert Templeton, Co. K, in the right shoulder. Lieut. Frank Wade, Co. D, right shoulder. Lieut. J. Templeton, Co. K, left shoulder. Sergeant-Major Herbert Bastion, Co. K, right side and elbow.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  Government advices from Europe by the last mail represent the public sentiment as growing decidedly in favor of the United States. Even the English advices, it is stated, are much improved in character. Gen. MCCLELLAN is taking all necessary measures to inform himself of the exact meaning of the recent rebel movements. Yesterday morning he accompanied a heavy detachment from Gen. SMITH's Division.  He proceeded as far as Flint Hill, only two and a-half miles this side of the village, and which overlooks it. The pickets of the enemy were discovered in considerable force--indicating that a large body was not far distant. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LIVERPOOL, Thursday Evening. COTTON. -- Sales yesterday and to-day of 60,000 bales, including 30,000 bales to speculators and exporters. The market is excited and firm, and closes with a trifling advance. BREADSTUFFS firm. Corn active. mixed 31s. 6d. PROVISIONS quiet and steady. LONDON, Thursday Evening. Consols closed to-day at 92 5E8 TO 92 3E4. American Securities are quiet and steady. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Gen. MCCLELLAN is taking all necessary measures to inform himself of the exact meaning of the reeent rebel movements. On Friday a reconnaissance was pushed towards Occoquan, taking the telegraph road as far as Acatink Creek, and parties were sent to Acatink, Pohick, and on the road leading up the Ocatink. The latter encountered the rebel pickets, who immediately fell back and gave the alarm, and the long roll was beaten at the rebel camp on the other side of the Acatink Creek. This reconnaissance established the fact that there are no rebels between the telegraph road and the Potomac, above the Occoquan River. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Part of Gen. Stone's division crossed the Potomac to-day at Ball's Bluff, and after severe fighting were driven back, with great loss, by the enemy.  On this occasion Gen. Baker fell.  There was an engagement near Frederickstown, Missouri.  Rebels under Jefferson Thompson were defeated.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  A partial blockade of the Potomac occurred to-day by rebel batteries.  The rebels have adopted another expedient for obstructing the navigation of the Lower Potomac, and to some purpose, as it enabled them yesterday to make a capture. They have stretched a chain across the channel at Pasawamsic Creek, and when the Resolute, with the schooners Fairfax and Lady Ann in tow, passed up, she ran against it, and was unable to proceed until the Fairfax broke loose and drifted toward the shore, when the rebels in boats started out and captured her.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS.  To-day there was engagement between the Massachusetts and a rebel steamboat at the mouth of the Mississippi.  BOSTON, Saturday, Oct. 19. The Board of Trade and the Committee of the Associated Banks have protested to the Government against the purchase of army clothing in England, for which purpose United States Quartermaster THOMAS left in the steamship Niagara with letters of credit amounting to five millions of pounds sterling. It is rumored that the Government has countermanded the order by telegraph to Halifax or Cape Race, at which latter point the Niagara will call to-night. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SYRACUSE, Missouri, Monday, Oct. 14, 1861. Gen. CAMERON, accompanied by Adjutant-Gen. THOMASand Mr. WILKINSON, of the New-York Tribune, spent Saturday night at Jefferson, and arrived in Tipton about 9 o'clock yesterday morning. After breakfasting in camp, they rode over to this place (six miles) on horseback, accompanied by Gen. FREMONT and Staff. On the way, one of the younger officers bantered Gen. CAMERON for a race, upon which the Secretary of War put spurs to his horse and showed that he was at least a superior equestrian, -- an accomplishment not very common in our army. He left all competitors behind.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON.  The Nashville ran the blockade at Charleston to-day.  ALBANY, Thursday. Oct. 17 -- P.M. FLOUR has improving demand. BECKWHEAT FLOUR in the street, 12s. 6d. TO 13s. 3d. WHEAT sells readily in car-lots for milling here at  SX 1 18 TO  SX 1 21 for Red State.  SX 1 25 for Red Western.  SX 1 30 for White Genesee, and  SX 1 38 TO  SX 1 39 for White Michigan. OATS. 36c. is paid for car-lots of State delivered, and 25,000 bush. State afloat, 37c.. 3,000 bush. Quinte, 64c.. 17,300 bush, part at 70c., part on private terms, and 80c. for 6,000 bush, very choice to arrive. 14,000 bush. Canada West, 70c., and 6,000 bush. Canada East on private terms, and 4,500 bush. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST"	WASHINGTON.  To-day there was a successful skirmish near Harper's Ferry.  Col. Geary's troops captured a rebel cannon.
"Sat, 15 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON.  The ship Thomas Watson, attempting to get into Charleston, was burnt to the water's edge to-day by the blockading squadron.  The schooner Emily Tenrook ran the blockade at Savannah and got into St. Thomas.  At Quantico, there has been engagement between Seminole and rebel batteries.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  The paucity of news from Missouri, relating to the movements of the army, may be accounted for, by the fact that Gen. FREMONT has forbidden the transmission of such intelligence by telegraph. Chicago papers report interesting news from Kansas City. On the 6th of October LANE and STURGIS were still there, the former with three thousand and the latter with four thousand men. A serious misunderstanding existed between the two Generals, owing, it is asserted, to Gen. STURGIS' unfortunate habits. The whole circumstance is greatly to be deplored, as Gen. STURGIS has proved himself on more than one occasion to be an excellent officer. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  A movement of the rebels threatening our lines across the Potomac, was noted in yesterday's TIMES. They advanced a large force on Saturday in the direction of Prospect Hill, driving in the National pickets to that point. The Division of Gen. McCALL, stationed at Langley, was immediately formed in line of battle and got in readiness to advance, supported by cavalry and artillery, and the Divisions of Gens. SMITH, PORTER and MCDOWELL were also rapidly prepared for any emergency. The rebels attempted nothing further, and finally retired. Yesterday morning they again appeared in some force on Prospect Hill.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  A telegraphic dispatch, from Halifax, to HENRY GRINNELL, Esq., from Dr. HAYES, announces the arrival of the exploring schooner United States at that port where he had put in to repair, and to obtain supplies. The voyage from Greenland is represented as having been very stormy. The gratification experienced by the return of this enterprising Arctic voyager, will be somewhat saddened by the intelligence of the death of two of the party. Dr. AUGUST SONTAG, the Astronomer of the Expedition, and Mr. GIBSON CARUTHERS, both of whom accompanied Dr. KANE on his last voyage to the Arctic regions. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  To-day there was a naval collision between rebel gunboats and National vessels at the head of the Mississippi passes.  Unsuccessful attempt of the steam ram  QN Turtle QN  to sink one of the National ships.  The Theodora has escaped from Charleston harbor with Mason and Slidell on board.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK.  The war in Virginia seems to have caught the infections sluggishness which rests on everything in that sleepy old Commonwealth. The daily report,  QN all quiet along the line, QN  applies not only to the neighborhood of the Potomac, but to Fortress Monroe and Newport's News.   There is movement, if not battle, in Kentucky. There are both movements and battles and incident inexhaustible in Missouri. But beyond extremely occasional spasms of energy along the water line, which, beginning at the source of the Greenbrier River, extends to the junction of the New River with the Kanawha, the war in Virginia may be said to languish, and apparently to have fallen asleep. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>JEFFERSON CITY, Tuesday, Oct. 9, 1861.  Col. MCDOWELL, a brother of him who distinguished himself at Bull Run, is here, and commands the Iowa Sixth.  His camp, men, their morals, drill, etc., are perfect models in the highest sense of the word. Not a drop of whisky, a pack of cards or word of profanity can be seen or heard in the camp -- the men gathered and listened reverently, and with uncovered heads, to the evening exercises of the chaplain. and better than all, the men, who are splendid specimens of physical perfection, have the utmost confidence in their officers' both as to their military knowledge and courage. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Rebels to-day attacked Santa Rosa Island.  They were repulsed by regulars and Wilson's Zouaves.  Mobile is said to be thoroughly blockaded.  OSWEGO, Monday, Oct. 7 -- P.M. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT scarce and no sales. Corn scarce and quit. BARLEY dull. sales, 1,400 bushels Toronto, 58c. RYE scare, and nominally at 60c. for prime lots. CANAL FREIGHTS unsettled on Grain. Flour 42c., Wheat 13c., Corn 11 1E2c. TO 12c. to New-York. Imports -- 10,000 bush. Wheat, 30,000 bush. Corn, 41,000 bush. Barley. Exports -- 5,210 bbls. Flour, 5,300 bush. Wheat, 22,000 bush. Corn, 21,500 bush. Barley. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Gen. Fremont and his army departed Jefferson City, Missouri, to-day in pursuit of Rice.  There was an unsuccessful attempt to cut out a privateer at Beaufort, S.C.  ALBANY, Monday, Oct. 7 -- P.M. FLOUR Light supply and in active demand. Less doing in WHEAT, but quotations show an upward tendency. sales 1,000 bushes White Michigan at  SX 1 40. Red State, in car lots, at  SX 1 24 TO  SX 1 25, and White Genesee at  SX 1 30. RYE steady at 70c., for car lots, delivered. CORN without change to note, with a moderate business doing. Receivers do not press the market. sales 28,000 bushels, at 53 1E8c. for Western Mixed, afloat, and 54c. in car lots.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, Oct. 5. FLOUR buoyant. sales 5,000 bbls. Wheat advanced. sales 20,000 bushels. Red  SX 1 25 TO  SX 1 30. Corn buoyant, at 59c. TO 60c. Coffee -- Rio, 15 1E2c. TO 16 1E2c. Whisky firm, 22c. TO 22 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON.  Rebels were unsuccessful to-day in retaking the Hatteras Inlet forts.  There was great slaughter at Hatteras by Monticello's guns.  MONTREAL, Saturday, Oct. 5. A. HEWARDO reports: FLOUR in demand, but small receipts check business. Sales of No. 1 Superfine, which is equal to the best Extra State, at  SX 5 60 TO  SX 5 65. 3,000 bbls. for last half of October, at  SX 5 75. Wheat steady but less active. sales 20,000 bushels No. 1 Chicago Spring, at  SX 1 20: 28,000 bushels Milwaukee at  SX 1 21 TO 1 22. 23,000 bushels White Michigan at  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 37 1E2. 18,000 bushels Red Winter at  SX 1 30. Corn dull. Sellers at 54c, and buyers at 52c. 56 lbs.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday, October 4.  There are ten thousand troops between Fairfax and Leesburgh.  It is supposed that they either intend to go into Winter quarters at Manasses or Richmond, and also to send a large quota of their forces to Kentucky. A lady who has just arrived from Winchester states that all classes of society favoring secession felt the vital necessity of the rebels winning a victory opposite Washington. She adds that, the rebel retreat will have the most, depressing effect. The frosty nights occasion much discontent and murmuring in the rebel camps. It has all along been a part of their programme to spend the Winter in Washington and Baltimore.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Oct. 2. All is intensely quite along the lines. Information has been received by telegraph up to to-night from all our camps on the Virginia side of the river, and from Gen. BANKS' command, representing everything as void of interest. Strong fortifications have already been completed on Munson's and adjoining hills by our troops, which will be made still stronger. The enemy are no longer seen in the vicinity of Falls Church, but have fallen back towards Fairfax and the line between there and Springfield Station. Their advanced column from Leesburgh to the Junction is slowly retreating.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, October 2.  SWEET WATER STATION PACIFIC TELEGRAPH, 340 MILES EAST OF SALT LAKE CITY, Saturday, Sept. 21.  The Pony Express, giving account of the burning of the bridges on the Hannibal and St. Joseph Railroad, and consequent interruption of telegraph, mail and Pony Express communication with the East, reached San Francisco. This stoppage of the mails and Pony Express makes our California newspapers very dry reading. The last Pony Express brought through no letters on account of the blundering of Eastern postmasters. Eastern correspondents must exercise much judgment in choosing means to convey dispatches during these troubled times. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, October 1.  News from SWEET WATER STATION PACIFIC TELEGRAPH, 340 MILES EAST OF SALT LAKE CITY, Saturday, Sept. 21. The Pony Express passed here at 8 o'clock this morning, bringing the following for the Press: SAN FRANCISCO, Saturday, Sept. 14.  There is no California news for this Express. The enlistment of troops for the five regiments last called for goes on moderately well. The pay of the soldiers being so much below California wages, seems to discourage volunteering at this time, when the State is prospering and the people well employed. still the number of volunteers now called for will be obtained.</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
