<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 31.  Gen. Hunter assumed command of the Department of the South.  The prospects of getting a submarine inter-continental telegraph cable in operation before very long are encouraging. Mr. CYRUS FIELD, whose name is traditionally associated with this great project, went to England bearing a dispatch from Mr. SEWARD to Mr. ADAMS, to the effect that the United States Government is prepared to ask Congress to guarantee two per cent. upon a capital of three or three and a half million dollars for twenty or twenty-five years, if England will do the same.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, March 30.  Private advices from London, of the 15th inst., state that Mr. FIELD, with other leading gentlemen and capitalists, interested in the Atlantic Telegraph Cable enterprise, were to meet Lord PALMERSTON at noon on the 21st inst., and that the prospect of a satisfactory termination of negotiations with the Government, in regard to raising the necessary capital to secure the proposed new cable, were very encouraging. Mr. FIELD confidently expected to return to New-York with assurances of the earnest cooperation of the British Government in the great undertaking which he has so long and ably endeavored to bring to a successful issue. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 29.  The  QN Middle QN  Department has been constituted.  A charge has occurred through Middleburgh, Virginia, in pursuit of rebels fleeing from the place.  The schooners Lydia and Mary have been captured.  RICHMOND, March 29.  At Corinth, Mississippi, the Confederate Army of the Kentucky and that of the Mississippi have been consolidated under command of Gen. Albert Johnston.  CHICAGO, Saturday, March 29. FLOUR dull. WHEAT quiet and unchanged. CORN neglected. MESS PORK held at  SX 10 79, without buyers. Hogs -- Dressed quiet. live, 10c. lower. BEEF CATTLE firm. Receipts -3,100 bbls. Flour. 4,500 bush.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHIGTON, March 28.  Shipping Point, Virginia, is now occupied by Union forces.  A reconnaissance beyond Warrenton, Virginia, has occurred.  ST. LOUIS, March 28.  Word has been received of a battle 20 miles from Santa Fe, New-Mexico.  CINCINNATI, Friday, March 28. FLOUR unchanged. WHISKY active and in speculative demand at 18c., but closing buoyant, MESS PORK dull, and no demand. LARD 1E8c. higher, closing at 7 1E4c.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHIGTON, March 27.  The schooner Julia Warden has been captured near Charleston, South Carolina.   RICHMOND, March 25.  Yesterday the Federals made their appearance at Brunswick, but as as the telegraphic instruments were immediately removed to the interior, we could hear nothing of later particulars. We presume they took possession of the place, which had previously been deserted by both troops and citizens. There were seventeen Federals vessels entering the mouth of the St. John's on Saturday, and it is presumed they want up the river to Jacksonville yesterday. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Wednesday, March 26. FLOUR 10c. TO 15c. lower. WHEAT firm at 76c. CORN inactive. MESS PORK rather more inquiry, at  SX 10 50. HOGS, dressed, quiet. live, dull and drooping. Receipts, 1,800 bbls., Flour, 4,400 bushels Wheat, 5,900 bushels Corn. Exchange and gold unaltered.  
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Thursday, March 27, FLOUR, in fair demand and at unchanged rate WHISKY, active at 16c. BULK SIDES are active. sales of 600,000 lbs at 4 1E2c. SHOULDERS are quiet at 3c. LARD, quiet at 7c. MESS PORK, nominal, at 10 1E4c. TO 10 1E2c. BACON dull at 3 3E4c. TO 5c. Exchange firm.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NASHVILLE, March 24.  An engagement has reportedly occurred between the gunboats Tyler and Lexington, and a masked rebel battery, near Eastport, Tennessee.  CINCINNATI. Monday, March 24. FLOUR in fair demand at  SX 4 25 TO  SX 1 30. WHISKY unsettled. no sales: 18c. are asked and 15c. are offered. PROVISIONS less firm. First-class city brands of Mess Pork are offered at  SX 10 75, Country at  SX 10 50  TO  SX 10 52. 50,000 lbs. Bulk Sides at 4 1E2c. LARD easy at 7c. Exchange firm at 1E4 cent. premium. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHIGNTON, March 23. The Battle of Winchester, Virginia, occurred to-day.  The rebels have been defeated with a loss of 869 killed, wounded, and missing.  The Union loss is 115 killed, 450 wounded.  The surrender of Fort Macon, North Carolina, has been demanded but so far refused.  FORTRESS MONROE, March 22, via BALTIMORE, 23d. All is quiet here. A flag of truce was sent out this morning for the accommodation of an officer of the French Navy desiring to go South. The rebel officers and crew were very uncommunicative, and we gathered no news from them.  Hopes are entertained that the telegraph cable will be repaired to-day or to-morrow.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 22.  A reconnaissance force is reportedly sent to Cumberland Gap.  FORTRESS MONROE, March 22.  The United States bark Young Rover, from the mouth of the Rappahannock River, arrived last evening. She brought no news from that vicinity. It has been discovered that the telegraph cable was cut about ten miles from the eastern shore. A man has been arrested who is supposed to have been the culprit. He has been sent to Gen. LOOKWOOD. An example will be made of him. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 21.  Gen. Butler arrived at Ship Island to-day.  Washington, North Carolina, is now occupied by Gen. Burnside's troops.  The Departments of the Gulf and of the South are constituted.  Gen. Butler is assigned to the former, and Gen. T. W. Sherman to the latter.  ST. LOUIS, March 21. Flag Officer Foote's guns are still pounding Island No. 10, which is still holding out. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, March 20.  An expedition of engineers from Gen. Pope's army, having reached Commodore Foote above Island No. 10, started on its return and commenced cutting a canal for the passage of gunboats to New Madrid.  At Ship Island, Mississippi, Maj. Gen. Benjamin Butler has assumed command of the troops.  WASHINGTON, March 20.  Federals near Strasburg, Virginia, have been threatened by rebel cavalry and have moved back toward Winchester.  Gen. Burnside's troops have moved from New Bern towards Washington, North Carolina, without opposition.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, March 19.  The rebel defenders of Island No. 10 in the Mississippi River are still providing strong resistance to Flag Officer Foote's floating artillery.  FORTRESS MONROE, Saturday, March 15, via BALTIMORE, Sunday, March 16. In pursuance of orders from the War Department, for the separation of the administration of the affairs of contrabands from military authority, a general order was issued to-day by Gen. WOOL, appointing CHARLES B. WILDER to the office of Superintendent of Vagrants or Contrabands in this Department. Food, clothing and shelter will be furnished as heretofore, until further orders. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 18.  The steamer Nashville reportedly escaped from Beaufort, North Carolina.  The ship Emily St. Pierre has been captured near Charleston, South Carolina.  A rebel gunboat was sunk near New Madrid by a masked battery.  Gen. Dix has been assigned to the command of the  QN Middle QN  Department.  Aquia Creek, Virginia, has been evacuated by the rebels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 17.  The Gunboat Cimerone is now launched.  Gen. Grant has arrived at Pittsburg Landing and assumed command, placing his headquarters at Savannah, north of the Landing.  In Alexandria, Virginia, long lines of Union troops are assembled, waiting for transport to York Peninsula for a pending assault on Richmond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 16.  Gen. Garfield has defeated the rebels in the Cumberland Mountains of East Tennessee.  LOUISVILLE, Ky., Saturday, March 15. The Telegraph Line is now open for business between here and Nashville, Clarksville and Gallatin, Tenn. Dispatches can now be sent to these places, from all parts of the loyal States. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 15.  A naval expedition has reportedly left Cairo for Hickman, Kentucky, to-day.  Gens. Sherman and Hurlbut forces arrived at the land docks of Pittsburg Landing on the Tennessee River.  Maj. Gen. Don Buell was ordered from Nashville to the area around Savannah, Tennessee.   ST. LOUIS, March 15.  Flag Officer Foote's flotilla of gunboats and mortar boats reached the area above Island No. 10, but dense fog and rain prevented any action.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 14.  The Battle of Newburn, North Carolina, commenced to-day.  Gen. Brunside's men, numbering 11,000, moved on the town and captured it from a force of about 4,000 Confederates after some minor fighting.  The attack was carried out in pouring rain and over muddy roads.  Another useful port and supply point has been established.  ST. LOUIS, March 14.  The rebels evacuated New Madrid, Missouri, leaving immense stores in our hands.  The rebels evacuated to Island No. 10 or across the Mississippi River.  Gen. Pope is attacking the island.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, Thursday, March 13. From Gen. Halleck to Hon. E.M. Stanton, Washington: Our artillery and cavalry yesterday attacked the enemy's works-one half mile west of Paris, Tenn. The enemy was driven out with a loss of 100 killed, wounded and prisoners. Our loss is Capt. BULL, of the Artillery, and four men killed and four wounded. A cavalry force sent out from Lebanon, Mo., attacked one of PRICE's guerrilla parties, killing thirteen' wounding five, and capturing over twenty prisoners, among whom was Brig.-Gen. CAMPBELL, the commander. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 12.  Jackson, Florida, is reportedly occupied by our troops.  Gen. Banks has reached Winchester, Virginia.  Forts in New York harbor are now garrisoned.  The schooner Fair Play is captured off South Carolina.  RICHMOND, March 12.  McClellan's proximity to Richmond has created a rush to the  QN passport QN  office of those wanting to leave the city.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 11.  Our troops entered the works at Manassas Junction to-day.  Gen McClellan has taken to the field with the Army of the Potomac. the President has relieved him of command of the other military departments.  Gen. Halleck is assigned to the command of the Department of the Mississippi.  Gen. Fremont is assigned to the command of the Mountain Department.  RICHMOND, March 11.  President Davis refused to accept reports sent by Generals Floyd and Pillow, who fled Fort Donelson.  Both are relieved of command.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 10.  Centreville, Virginia, is occupied by our forces.  The Gunboat Whitehall has been destroyed by fire in Hampton Roads.  The last of the rebels left Manassas and our scouts approached the place.  WASHINGTON, Sunday, March 9. The telegraph line to Fortress Monroe was built by order of the Secretary of War, under the direction of the General Manager of Military Telegraph Lines. The extension of the Government line from Harrington, Del., to Cape Charles, was constructed in twenty-three days. Thirty miles of the submarine cable was manufactured for the channel crossing in twenty days from the date of the order, by S.C. BISHOP, of New-York.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 9.  The battle between the Merrimac and our vessels continued to-day.  The Monitor, having arrived on the evening of the 8th, entered into the contest and fought the Merrimac, the two vessels touching each other part of the time.  The Merrimac retired, the Monitor being undamaged.  Lieut.-Commanding Worden, of the Monitor, was injured.  Cockpit Point, Virginia, was occupied by our troops.  The rebel steamer Geo. Page was burned by the rebels.  ST. LOUIS, March 9.  Point Pleasant, Missouri, has been taken by a brigade of Union troops.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 8.  The battle at Pea Ridge ended to-day.  The rebels were entirely routed.  The Army of the Potomac has been divided up into five Corps.  RICHMOND, March 8.  Gen. Beauregard has requested that bells be sent to depots for conversion to cannon.  The Merrimac, from Norfolk, has attacked the Union fleet at Hampton Roads.  The Cumberland was sunk. the Minnesota grounded, the Congress burned, the gunboats Oregon and Zouave badly damaged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 7.  A battle at Pea Ridge, Arkansas, is continuing to-day.  Our forces are under command of Gen. Curtis, those of the rebels under Ben McCulloch.  Rebels are retreating from Centreville, Virginia.  LONDON, Sunday, Feb. 23. The anniversary of the birthday of WASHINGTON was celebrated, yesterday, at a public breakfast at Freemason's Tavern. The Bishop of Ohio presided, and two hundred ladies and gentlemen were present. Hon. C.F. ADAMS, United States Minister, in proposing a toast to the memory of WASHINGTON, referred to the present crisis in America.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 6.  President Lincoln's emancipation message was sent to Congress to-day.  Smithfield, Virginia, is occupied by our troops.  A battle at Pea Ridge, Arkansas, is reportedly commenced.  HALIFAX, Thursday, March 6. Steamship City of Washington, from New-York, reached Liverpool at 5.30 A.M., and the Anglo-Saxon, from Portland, at noon on the 21st. The Canada reports fine weather on the passage. On the 1st, lat. 47 deg lon. 4 min, passed bark Alexander McNeil, of Philadelphia, bound west. on the 2d, passed an English ship bound east, supposed the Queen of the Lakes. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 5.  Bunker Hill, Virginia, is now occupied by Union forces.  The rebel schooner Wm. Mallory has been captured.  Reports received that Gen. Beauregard has assumed command of the rebel army of the Mississippi.  CHICAGO, Wednesday, March 5. FLOUR dull. WHEAT in limited request, and 1E2c. lower. sales at 79c. for No. 1. CORN firm and steady. MESS PORK quiet and firm, at  SX 11 50. BULK MEATS scarce and firm. LARD dull, at 7c. HOGS Dressed, quiet and unchanged. Live, quiet and firm,  SX 2 75 TO  SX 3. BEEF CATTLE firm, at  SX 2 80 TO  SX 3 10 for good prime. Exchange and Gold unchanged. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Tuesday, March 4. FLOUR unchanged. superfine,  SX 4 TO  SX 4 25. WHISKY firm at 20c. PROVISIONS are a shade firmer. the best brands of Mess Pork are quoted at  SX 11 75 for present delivery, and  SX 12 for April. Bulk Shoulders, loose,  SX 3 25 TO  SX 3 37 1E2. Hams,  SX 4 25 TO  SX 4 37 1E2. Sides,  SX 4 75. Exchange on New-York, par TO 1E8 cent. premium. Gold, 2 1E4 cent. premium. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 3.  Columbus, Kentucky, is reportedly occupied by northern forces after having been deserted.  Martinsburgh, VA is occupied by Gen. Bank's forces.  Gen. Pope's forces are reportedly engaged with the enemy near New-Madrid, MO.  Fernandina, Florida, surrendered today to Commodore DuPont and Gen. Wright.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 2.  Gen. F. W. Lander died to-day.  A gunboat engagement with rebel batteries commenced at Pittsburgh, Tenn.  Messrs. GLASS, ELLIOTT  ES  Co., in a letter to CYRUS W. FIELD, Esq., say that they would not be willing to manufacture and lay the Atlantic Telegraph Cable, and assume the entire risk, as they believe it is too great for one firm, but are so confident of satisfactory results that they are willing to contract for the work and stake a large sum on its successful laying and working. They state that they will make a definite offer in a few days, and will furnish a list of 3 500 miles of cable already laid by them and nearly all working successfully.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, March 1.  John Minor Botts has been arrested in this city on charges of treason to the Confederacy.  The schooner British Queen was captured to-day, endeavoring to run the blockade at Wilmington, N.C.  CHICAGO, Saturday, March 1. FLOUR quiet, WHEAT unchanged. CORN steady. MESS PORK is held at  SX 11 50, without buyers. BULK MEATS are scarce, firm and unchanged. LARD dull and nominal, at 7c. HOGS, dressed -- Holders are firm and quotations unchanged. live in active demand, but prices unchanged. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 28.  The steamer Nashville ran the blockade at Beaufort, N.C.  This is Fast Day in the  QN Confederate QN  States.  A skirmish occurred at Sikeston, Mo.  Charleston, Va., is occupied by Union troops.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 27.  The rebels began to evacuate Columbus, Ky.  The Monitor has sailed from New York.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 26.  The Loan and Treasury Bills, legal tender, are approved by the President.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Nashville, Feb. 25.  This city is now occupied by the Union army.  Washington, Feb. 25.  An order is issued by the War Department forbidding the publication of war news not authorized by the Government.  The telegraph lines are taken possession by the Government.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 24.  Harper's Ferry is occupied by Gen. Bank's troops.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 23.  Rebels have evacuated Nashville.  Gen. Curtis captured Fayetteville, Ark. And the rebels fled in confusion.  Gen. Buell now occupies Gallatin, Tenn.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 22.  National troops were defeated yesterday on the Rio Grande, New-Mexico.  Martial law has been proclaimed over West Tennessee.  Richmond, Feb. 22.  Jefferson Davis was inaugurated to-day in this city.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>New York, Feb. 21.  Capt. Nathaniel P. Gordon, a slave trader, was executed in this city to-day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 20.  There has been a gunboat reconnaissance up the Occoquan Creek, Va.  Winton, N.C. has been burned by Gen. Burnside's troops.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Nashville, Feb. 19.  Com. Foote has taken possession of Clarksville, Tenn.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 18.  A proclamation has been issued by Gen. Burnside and Flag-Officer Goldsborough in North Carolina.  The rebel congress met at Richmond.  St. Louis, Feb. 18.  A skirmish occurred at Independence, Mo.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 17.  Two rebel regiments, marching to reinforce Fort Donelson, have been captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 16.  Fort Donelson has surrendered to Gen. Grant.  Between 12,000 and 15,000 prisoners and large quantities of stores and artillery have been captured.  Rebel Gens. Floyd and Pillow escaped.  Gens. Buckner and Tilghman were captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 15.  Bowling Green, Ky. Has been evacuated by the rebels and is now occupied by Gen. Buell's army.  An engagement has occurred between rebel gunboats and our batteries near Fort Pulaski, Georgia.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 14.  The Sec. of War ordered the release of all political prisoners, on condition of their taking an oath not to aid the rebellion.  Amnesty has been granted to such by the President.  Messrs. Ames and Fish have returned from Fort Monroe.  The rebels refused to allow them within their lines for the object on which they went, but agreed to exchange all the prisoners, releaseing 300 Union prisoners more than we released rebels, on condition of the release of the next 300 falling into our hands.  Cavalry reconnaisance has occurred at Blooming Gap, Va.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>St. Louis, Feb. 13.  Springfield is occupied by Union troops under Gen. Curtis.  Gen. Price hastily evacuated the place in the morning.   Washington, Feb. 13.  The Chesapeake and Albermarle Canal in N.C. has been destroyed by an expedition.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 12.  Edenton, N.C., has been taken by Lieut. Maury, U.S.N.  St. Louis, Feb. 12.  Gen. Price has retreated from Springfield.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 11.  A Sawyer gun has burst at Newport's News, Va.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 10.  Word has been received that the rebel steamer Nashville was sent from Southampton, England, on the 3rd inst.  The Union gunboat Tuscarora started in pursuit and was stopped by British frigate Shannon.  The rebel squadron from Roanoke Island has been attacked and destroyed.  Elizabeth City, N.C. has surrendered.  Martial law has been proclaimed in Kansas.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 9.  Brig. Gen. C. P. Stone, U. S. Volunteers, was arrested and sent to Fort Lafayette.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 8.  The battle of Roanoke Island is continuing.  The Island, with all its fortifications has been captured with 3,000 stand of small arms, 3,000 prisoners, 6 forts and large quantities of military supplies taken by Gen. Burnside's force.  Capt. O. Jenningswise was mortally wounded.  Rebel boats Sallie Wood and Muscle have been captured at Chickasaw, Miss.  Three steamboats were burned at Florence, Ala.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 7.  To-day a battle occurred at Roanoke Island, N.C.  Harper's Ferry, Va. Was shelled by our batteries by order of Col. Geary, on account of the rebels firing on a boat under flag of truce.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 6.  Fort Henry, on the Tennessee River, has been taken by our western gunboat fleet under command of Flag-Officer A. H. Foote.  The gunboat expedition left Fort Henry.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 5.  Gen. Thos. Meagher took command of the Irish Brigade in McClellan's army.  The British schooner Mars is reportedly captured off Florida.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 4.  A brisk skirmish occurred to-day on the Potomac, near the Occoquan.  Discussion is underway in the rebel Virginia house of Delegates on the subject of enrolling free negroes.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>New York, Feb. 3.  Privateersmen who, up to this date, were confined in the city jails were released therefrom and imprisoned in Fort Lafayette.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 2.  A cavalry charge of the rebels occurred to-day on a small force of Union infantry in Morgan County, Tenn.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Feb. 1, 1862.  A skirmish occurred to-day near Bowling Green, Ky.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, Feb. 1. Mr. WILSON, of Missouri. (Union,) presented the credentials of JOHN B. HENDERSON, appointed Senator from Missouri, to fill the vacancy caused by the expulsion of Mr. POLK. The credentials were read and Mr. HENDERSON took the oath. Mr. HALE, of New-Hampshire, (Rep.,) from the Naval Committee, made a report on the memorial for a steam mail line to San Francisco, and asked to be discharged. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 31.  The President has been authorized by Congress to take possession of the railroad and telegraph lines of the United States.  Sec. Seward has ordered the release of prisoners in Fort Lafayette who were taken on vessels which had violated the blockade.    New York, Jan. 31.  Queen Victoria has declared anew her intention to observe neutrality in the American war.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>New York, Jan. 30.  The Monitor was launched to-day at the Brooklyn Navy Yard.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Jan. 28.  Lieut. BOOTH, of the Second Wisconsin Regiment, made prisoner at Bull Run, and Lieut. HOOPER, of the First California Regiment, captured at Ball's Bluff, arrived here to-day from Richmond. Fewer soldiers are now seen in Washington than at any previous time since the commencement of the rebellion, owing to the execution of a recently promulgated military order. Gen. STURGIS, of Misseuri, reported himself here yesterday, in obedience to orders</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Jan. 29. Overland from SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Dec. 11, 1861.  I will proceed to give the Telegraph a  QN first-rate notice. QN  Anybody who has sent a message that required an immediate answer, can readily understand how amiable it is calculated to make one feel to be told that the wires are down. The fact is the institution was built in a hurry. John Bull would not have finished it for two years yet. but then it would have stood until every Indian on the Plains had become an operator. They show a little disposition occasionally as it is, to  QN pull wires. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 28.  A gunboat expedition to reconnoitre in the neighborhood of Fort Pulaski, below Savannah, has been completed.  An engagement has occurred between our boats and those of rebel Commander Tatnall.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Jan. 28. The House Committee on Commerce, at their meeting to-day, authorized Gen. WARD to report on the Canadian Reciprocity Treaty. The report will suggest a number of important changes, making it more equal and favorable to the United States. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 27.  Bishop Ames and Hon. Hamilton Fish have been appointed Commissioners to visit Richmond.  CHICAGO, Monday, Jan. 27. FLOUR steady. WHEAT firm and advanced 1E4c. TO 1E2c. CORN quiet, but firm. MESS PORK firm and active, at  SX 9 25. HOGS, dressed, 5c. TO 10c. lower, at  SX 2 26. live dull, at  SX 2 30 TO  SX 2 35. Receipts 3,000 bbls. Flour, 2,000 bushels Wheat, 24,000 bushels Corn, Exchange unchanged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>New Orleans, Jan. 26.  This is the anniversary of the secession of Louisiana.  The day was celebrated in this city.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 25.  Mr. STANTON held his conference with the Military Committees of the House and Senate to-day, at the Capitol. It was of a general and initiatory character only, the Secretary's object being, as he said, to become personally acquainted with the members of the two committees, with whom his official relations would be so intimate. Mr. STANTON stated, in a general way, his purpose to consult with the Committees on all important subjects affecting his Department, so as to secure perfect accord between the army and the representatives of the people. This assurance was in the highest degree gratifying to the Committees.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 24.  Two rebel vessels have been grounded and burned in attempting to run the blockade at the mouth of the Mississippi.  The President to-day nominated NOAR A. SWAYNE, of Ohio, as Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States, to fill the vacancy caused by the death of Justice MCLEAN.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 23.  A second fleet of stone-laden vessels has been sunk in Charleston, S.C. harbor.  The steamer Calhoun has been captured off Southwest Pass at the mouth of the Mississippi. A telegraphic dispatch from an officer in the National army to a prominent friend in Washington, dated Somerset, Ky., Jan. 21, and received here at 8 o'clock last night, says:  QN ZOLLICOPPER is killed. I saw him, and know it. We have achieved one of the most glorious victories on record. Rebels dispersed, leaving everything be hind -- about fourteen hundred horses and eighty wagons. QN  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 22. The bill reported from the Committee on Ways and Means, to-day, provides that for temporary purposes the Secretary of the Treasury is authorized to issue' on the credit of the United States, one hundred mullions of dollars of United States Notes, not bearing interest, payable to bearer at the Treasury, or at the office of the Assistant-Treasurer, in the City of NewYork, at the pleasure of the United States, and of such denominations as he may deem expedient, not less than five dollars each, </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>St. Louis, Jan. 21.  To-day, Gen. McClernand's expedition returned to Cairo, from reconnoitering in the vicinity of Columbus, Ky.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 20.  An order has been issued for the appointment of Commissioners to visit Richmond, to provide for the welfare of our troops imprisoned there.  The Rebel schooner Wilder has been captured in Mobile Bay.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 19.  A battle occurred to-day at Mill Springs, Ky., in which rebel Gen. Zollicoffer was killed.  Rebel schooner Lizzie Weston was captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Richmond, Jan. 18.  Ex-President John Tyler died in this city to-day.  Washington, Jan. 18.  Reconnaissance up the Tennessee River has been completed by the gunboat Conesloga.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 17.  Gen. Burnside's expedition arrived at Hatteras, N.C. after meeting with heavy gales.  PHILADELPHIA, Friday, Jan. 17. Operations were suspended by rain. FLOUR dull. sales 2,000 bbls. Wheat declined 1c.. sales 5,000 bush. Red at  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 36. White,  SX 1 45 TO  SX 1 50. CORN firm. sales 4,000 bushels at unchanged rates. COFFEE -- Rio, 19c. TO 21c. MESS PORK,  SX 12 50, LARD, 8c. Whisky, 24c. TO 25c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>St. Louis, Jan. 16.  Reconnaisance has occurred from Lexington, Mo.  Washington, Jan. 16.  The army telegraph now consists of over one thousand miles of wire stretched through the different camps, from the headquarters of Gen. HOOKER on the left, running towards the right wing till it reaches Hancock, Md. One hundred and ten operators are now in the employ of the Government. Mr. ECKERT, the Assistant Superintendent in charge of this Department, has run a separate line to the headquarters of each General commanding a division. For instance, Gen. MCCLELLAN can sit at the table in his private house, and talk to the different Generals, all at one and the same time.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 15.  A rebel schooner has been burned by the men on vessels blockading the Rappahannock.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 14.  Gunboat reconaissance has occurred to within a mile and a half of Columbus, Ky.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 13.  Secretary Cameron to-day resigned.  Edwin M. Stanton has been appointed by Mr. Lincoln to be Secretary of War.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 12.  The Sloop-of-War Pensacola ran past rebel batteries long the Potomac to-day.  Gen Burnside's advance forces sailed from Fort Monroe.  A nephew of rebel Gen Polk has been captured and is reportedly bearing dispatches.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 11.  Gunboat action has reportedly occurred near Columbus, Ky.  Bridges on the Louisville and Nashville Railroad have been burned by rebels.  CHICAGO, Saturday, Jan. 11. FLOUR is inactive. Wheat closed dull at 71c. TO  71 1E2c. for No. 1, and 65 1E2c. TO 66c. for No. 2 in store. CORN is unchanged. OATS firm. Mrss PORK steady-at  SX 8 75 TO  SX 9. HOGS -- Dressed are steady at 92 65 TO   SX 2 85: Live are quiet at  SX 2 20 TO  SX 2 35. Recerpte - 6,000 bbls. Flour, 18,000 bush. Wheat, 18,000 bush. Corn, 3,400 live Hogs, 3,700 dressed do. Exchange on New-York unaltered. TORONTO, Saturday, Jan. 11. Exchange on New-York has been reduced to 1 1E2 cent.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>St. Louis, Jan. 10.  An expedition bound down the Mississippi left Cairo this morning.  Washington, Jan. 10.  Humphrey Marshall is reportedly defeated near Prestonburgh, Ky.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Thursday, Jan. 9. FLOUR and GRAIN unchanged. WHISKY held at 16c. this morning, but after the receipt of the New-York report, advanced to 18c., closing buoyant. HOGS dull, at  SX 3 TO  SX 3 14. receipts, 7,000. PORK dull. mess,  SX 9 TO  SX 9 25. LARD in fair demand, at 6 3E4c. GREEN MEATS, 1E8c. TO 1E4c. lower. SHOULDERS, 2 1E3c. TO 2 1E4c. HAMS, 3 1E4c. SIDES, 3 1E2c. Large offerings of Hogs to come in some days ahead, but no buyers. Exchange very dull, at 1E4c. discount 1E4c. premium. Gold 3  TO  4 premium. not much demand.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Jan. 8.  Rebels in Randolph County, Mo., have reportedly been routed.  CINCINNATI, Wednesday, Jan. 8. FLOUR dull at  SX 4 for Superfine. WHISKY, active speculative demand, 15c. HOGS closed dull and heavy at  SX 3 25 TO  SX 3 35. MESS PORK,  SX 9 12 1E2 TO  SX 9 37. LARD dull at 6 3E4c. EXCHANGE unsettled. bankers not buying, but anxious to sell at par to 1E4 premium.  RICHFIELD SPRINGS, N.Y., Monday, Jan. 6. The Richfield Springs and Herkimer telegraph line is now in operation. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Boston, Tuesday Jan. 7.  Kentucky Ex-Governor Morehead has been released from Fort Warren.  Washington, Jan. 7.  A gunboat reconaissance has reportedly occurred to within two miles of Columbus, Ky.  CHICAGO, Tuesday, Jan. 7. FLOUR quiet and firmer. WHEAT 1c. higher. 70c. TO 70 1E2c. for No. 1. 64 1E2c. TO 65 1E4c. for No. 2, in store. CORN a shade better. 22 1E2c. TO 23c. for mixed, in store. OATS dull. MESS PORK dull. buyers offer  SX 8 75 TO  SX 8 87 1E2. a lot of 250 bbls. prime City packed sold at  SX 9. HOGS -- dressed firmer, at unchanged prices. Live -- supply exceeds the demand, and market dull, at  SX 2 10 TO  SX 2 40. Receipts -- 3,200 bbls. Flour, 19,000 bushels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Monday, Jan. 6.  FLOUR dull and neglected. WHEAT dull and lower. sales at 70c. TO 71c. for No. 1. and 65c. TO 65 1E2c. for No. 2, in store. CORN dull at 23c. for Mixed, in store. OATS dull and 1E2c. lower. Miss PORK,  SX 9 TO  SX 9 25. HOGS, dressed, dull and 10c. lower, at  SX 2 60 TO  SX 3. live, dull and 5c. TO 10c. lower at  SX 2 10 TO  SX 2. Receipts -- 2,700 bbls. Flour, 16,000 bush. Wheat, 10,000 bush. Corn, 7,500 live Hogs, 1,600 dressed. Exchange unchanged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Sunday Jan. 5.  POINT OF ROCK, Sunday, Jan. 5. Six thousand rebels attacked the Fifth Connecticut Regiment, near Hancock, yesterday. They were protecting the railroad. After a slight skirmish, our men crossed to this side of the Potomac, to await reinforcements. Meanwhile the rebels destroyed the railroad and telegraph lines, breaking our communication with Cumberland. Gen. Lander is marching to the relief of the Fifth with a sufficient force. The loss in the affair on either side is not known here, but it is believed to be trifling. The rebels have been shelling at intervals all day. Our artillery responded. Their shells did no mischief. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Richmond, Saturday Jan. 4.  Huntersville has been attacked by Union troops and Confederate stores have been captured or destroyed.  Washington, Jan. 4.  The Army Telegraph Corps have returned from Hancock, having completed telegraphic connection between Frederick and Wheeling. They will next proceed to Budd's Ferry, and extend the telegraph line from thence to Point Lookout. A cable will be run from there to Fortress Monroe. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Washington, Friday Jan. 3.  A reconnaisance mission has been successfully completed to Big Bethel, Va.  NEW YORK, Friday Jan. 3.  The City Board concurred in allowing the Independent Telegraph Company to erect poles in the streets, subject to the usual regulations. The resolution from the Board of Councilmen, making the TIMES a Corporation paper, was read, and laid over under the rule. The Board concurred in donating  SX 800 to Mary J. Hall, for an unjust tax upon her property for the building of a sewer. After disposing of some unimportant papers, the Board adjourned to 3 o'clock this afternoon. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Jan. 1. At the President's reception to-day was the greatest jam ever witnessed on any similar occasion, Several hours before the time appointed for the opening of the gates, the avenue and sidewalks about them were so crowded at to render all access nearly impossible.  Provincetown, Thursday Jan. 2.  The British steam gunboat Rinaldo left here at five P.M., yesterday, with Messrs. MASON and SLIDELL and their Secretaries on board. The wind blew a hurricane all night.  CHARLESTON, Jan. 2.  Union prisoners were transferred yesterday from Charleston to Columbia, S.C.  Steamer Ella Warley ran the blockade into Charleston.  
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>Boston, January 1, 1862.  The British war-steamer Rinaldo, 16 guns, arrived at Provincetown last night. The commander says he was ordered to lay there, is unbending his sails, and appears to be perfectly at home. The steaming Starlight left Fort Warren at 11 A.M., with MASON and SLIDELL and secretaries, for Provincetown, where they will be transferred to the British war-steamer Rinaldo, now lying there.  After receiving their baggage, etc., the tug proceeded on her way to sea, leaving the fort about 11 o'clock. The whole affair was conducted without any display, in perfect quiet, and in the ordinary manner of conveying passengers. 
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
