<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 30.  Gen. MCCLELLAN has organized an ambulance corps for each division of the army, under command of a Captain, with a First Lieutenant for each division, a Second Lieutenant for each Brigade, and a Sergeant for each regiment, to have control of all ambulances and transport carts.  THE HOSPITALS. While there have been some complaints as to the treatment of soldiers in the hospitals here, and which was at once sought to be remained by the Surgeon-General, the sanitary arrangements are in general excellent, and the attentions bestowed upon the sick and wondered of a character of the greatest possible good. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 29.  Gen. Buell has been ordered to turn over the command of his army to Maj. Gen. Thomas.  Gen. Stahl's advance has reportedly taken Warrenton, Virginia.  Maj. Gen. Wm. Nelson has been killed with a single shot to his heart by Brig. Gen. Jeff. Davis, at the Galt House in Louisville, for an assault offered by the former.  Gen. I. P. Rodman, who was wounded at Antietam, died to-day.  RICHMOND, September 29.  Retaliatory resolutions have been introduced in the C.S. Congress on account of the Emancipation Proclamation. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, September 28.  The English steamer Sunbeam has been captured by the gunboats State of George and Mystic while attempting to run the blockade at Wilmington, N.C.  WASHINGTON, September 28.  POSTAGE STAMPS. The Post-Office Department has received information from various sources that certain persons persistently divert postage stamps from their legitimate purpose by circulating them in packages, together with canceled stamps, as currency. Owing to this use of the stamps, the Department is embarrassed in the supply for mail purposes. The public, therefore, are interested in discountenancing their circulation as currency.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, September 27.  Augusta, Kentucky, 40 miles from Cincinnati on the Ohio River, has been taken by rebel cavalry who destroyed the place.  WASHINGTON, Thursday, Sept. 25. COMPLAINT OF THE VOLUNTEER SURGEONS. Great complaint is made in regard to the conduct of many of the volunteer Surgeons, who recklessly amputate the limbs of the wounded, and leave them destitute of the care needed for their recovery. The object seems to be to secure practice for operating Surgeons. Many operations are performed without judgment, and in a totally unjustifiable manner, frequently hastening the death of the patient. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 26.  THE VICINITY OF THE BATTLE-FIELD. The country for miles around the battle-field of Antietam is one vast hospital, every barn, stable and other building being filled with the wounded. The presence of Surgeon-General HAMMOND on the field of battle undoubtedly effected immense good, saving a large amount of life and preventing much suffering. The different hospitals of this city contain over 19,000 patients.   The weather is beautiful and mild, and under the influence of our genial sun and breeze in the streets and hotel-stoops are more productive.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 25.  Reconnaissance reportedly occurred to-day to Warrenton Junction.  LOUISVILLE, KY., Wednesday, Sept. 24, HALF-PAST 10 O'CLOCK A.M. The city to-day presents quite a martial appearance. The stores are closed, and the military are seizing unenrolled persons to labor in the entrenchments. Refugees from the interior of Kentucky are forming a regiment here. The guerrilla A.R. JOHNSON is acting as Brigadier-General at Hopkinsville, enforcing the Confederate Conscription act, and levying contributions upon Union men. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, September 24.  The governors of the loyal states met in convention at Altoona, Pennsylvania, with seventeen states being represented.  WASHINGTON, September 24.  There is great excitement in Louisville, Kentucky. business is suspended and all are required to labor on the fortifications.  Gen. Buell arrived during the night.  RICHMOND, Sept. 16, 1862. [By telegraph from Dublin, Sept. 16, to Hon. GEO. W. RANDOLPH.] Gen. LORING's command entered the Kanawa Salines on last Saturday morning, and took possession of the salt works, closely pursuing the enemy en route for Charleston. Salt works not much injured. A very large quantity on hand.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, September 23.  The Commissioners of the Pacific Union Railroad Company, incorporated by act of Congress, approved July 1, 1862, assembled at Chicago, deem it proper and necessary to declare the motives which have induced them to accept the trust committed to them by the act,... They do, therefore, resolve that the speedy completion through the territory of the United States, from the Atlantic to the Pacific, of a railway communication, affording adequate means of transit for persons and property, and especially for the mails and military forces of the Government, has become a matter of urgent public necessity.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 22.  To-day, President Lincoln issued an emancipation proclamation, declaring that the slaves in any state in rebellion on January 1, 1863, will thenceforward and forevermore be free.  CHICAGO, September 22.  A battle at Wood Lake, Minnesota, has reportedly occurred to-day with the Indians.  PHILADELPHIA, Sunday, Sept. 21. Gov. CURTIN telegraphs from Hagerstown, notifying all military organizations to wait at home for further orders. Probably all danger is removed, the rebel army being in full retreat down the Shenandoah.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 21.  The armies of Gen. Buell and Gen. Bragg have reportedly left Lebanon, Tennessee, and Carthage, respectively, on their way toward Louisville.  The rebels have now been driven from Munfordsville, Kentucky.  To-day there was reconnaissance beyond Chantilly, Virginia.  A raid of rebel Gen. Stewart's cavalry has occurred in the direction of Williamsport.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 20.  A rebel reconnaissance in force occurred to-day, across the Potomac.  Although our forces were supported by artillery, they were compelled to recross the Potomac after a stubborn resistance.  The enemy crossed at Williamsport but were driven back by the advance of our army and the town was afterwards occupied by us in strong force.  A reconnaissance has also occurred to Ashby's Gap.  Commander George Preble, U.S.N., has been dismissed from the service for allowing the steamer Oreto to escape him at Mobile.  PHILADELPHIA, September 20.  Gov. Curtin has withdrawn the Pennsylvania militia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 19.  A reconnoitering force from our army crossed the Potomac to-day at Shepardstown, after a stout resistance on the part of the rebels.  Four pieces of artillery were captured by our troops.  By daylight the main body of rebels, with their artillery, had crossed the Potomac.  Our cavalry entered Sharpsburgh.  The last of the rebels left Harper's Ferry.  Gen. McClellan reported that Gen. Pleasanton was driving the enemy across the Potomac, and that our victory was complete.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 18.  Late news from yesterday, a strong column of rebel Gen. Braxton Bragg's force reinforced the rebels before Munfordsville and the combined forces completely surrounded our troops.  Our troops were compelled to surrender at 6 a.m.  To-day, the rebels in front of Gen. McClellan abandoned their position in the night, leaving many of their dead and wounded on the field.  An expedition left Pensacola for Sabine Pass and Galveston.  The rebel army from Maryland has reportedly passed hastily through Sharpsburgh.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 17.  The fight of the previous day, at Antietam, was renewed in the morning and raged with the greatest fury through the day.  The carnage on both sides has been terrible.  The rebels have been defeated and our army is left in possession of the field.  Gen. Mansfield was killed and Gens. Hooker and Richardson have been wounded.  Surgeon-General Hammond has telegraphed north for volunteer surgeons for the battle-field of Antietam.   Cumberland Gap, Kentucky, has been evacuated by the Union forces under Gen. George Morgan.  Gen. Morgan exploded the mines and magazines and burned the store-houses at the Gap.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 16.  The battle at Munfordsville, Kentucky, renewed to-day with desperate fighting throughout the day.  Terrific fighting has also continued throughout the day near Sharpsburgh and Antietam Creek, Maryland.  The day closed without any definite result.  WAR DEPARTMENT, ADJUTANT GENERAL's OFFICE, WASHINGTON, Sept. 12, 1862. GENERAL ORDERS No. 129. -- First, The President directs that the first, second and third corps of the Army of Virginia, announced in General Orders No. 103, be hereafter designated the first, eleventh and twelfth. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 15.  Harper's Ferry surrendered by Col. Miles.  The cavalry from Harper's Ferry reached Greencastle, Pennsylvania, having captured an ammunition train belonging to the rebel Gen. Longstreet.  Gen. Pleasanton, of Gen. McClellan's army, started after the enemy, and captured two of their guns.  Gen. Richardson's division came up with the enemy in large force near Sharpsburgh.  Late report from Kentucky--early yesterday, at light, the rebels attacked our forces at Munfordsville, Kentucky, with artillery.  After a hard artillery fight, the rebel infantry attacked our troops and were repulsed five successive times.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 14.  A battle commenced to-day at South Mountain, Maryland.  After a very severe engagement, the corps of Gen. Hooker and Gen. Reno carried Hagerstown Heights by storm.  Gen. Franklin's division engaged the enemy at Crampton's Gap, and, after a hot contest, gained a complete success.  Gen. Reno was killed.  The rebels retreated in the night toward the Potomac, our army pressing them closely.  Harper's Ferry was attacked at 2 a.m., Maryland Heights were abandoned.  Col. D'Utassy sent four companies to the Heights, who brought off four brass twelve-pounders and a wagon-load of ammunition.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 13.  Gen. McClellan has reportedly reached Frederick.  Further reinforcements have been sent to Col. Ford.  The enemy made an attack on the crest of the hill at Maryland Heights.  Our troops retired to the breastworks.  The One Hundred and Twenty Sixth Regiment N.Y.V. fled in confusion at the second attack.  Col. Miles ordered Col. ford to spike his guns and throw the heavy ones down the mountain in case he should be compelled to evacuate Maryland Heights.  Gen. McClellan established his headquarters at Frederick City in the morning.  The pirate Alabama captured and burned the whaler Benj. Tucker.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 12.  Gen. Hooker's forces have now arrived in Frederick, Maryland.  They were received with the greatest enthusiasm by the inhabitants of the city.  Gen. White returned to Harper's Ferry.  Reinforcements have been sent to Col. Ford.  Skirmishing has commenced at Maryland Heights.  A desperate fight has reportedly occurred at Elk River, Western Virginia.  CINCINATTI, September 12.  Reconnaissances in force from Cincinnati have found that the enemy has fallen back.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 11.  Union troops are now occupying New Market, Maryland.  Hagerstown is occupied by the rebel troops who captured a large quantity of flour and have commenced to tear up the railroad track.  Gen. Pleasanton's cavalry have crossed the Monocacy river near the Potomac and found no enemy in force.  Sugar Loaf Mountain, Maryland, is now occupied by our forces.  Rebels made a cavalry raid into Westminster.  Gen. McClellan telegraphed from Rockville, Maryland, to Gen. Halleck to have Col. Miles, who is at Harper's Ferry, to join him at once.  Our forces stationed at Solomon's Gap, near Harper's Ferry, were driven in by the enemy. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, September 10.   Gov. Curtin has issued an order calling on all able-bodied men in Pennsylvania to organize immediately for the defense of the State.  CINCINNATI, September 10.  There is great excitement in this city. 3,000 laborers are ordered to the trenches.  The rebels, 10,000 strong, are believed to be approaching the city.  WASHINGTON, September 10.  A stringent order against straggling has been issued by the War Department to-day.  Cavalry reconnaissance has reportedly occurred near Sugar Loaf Mountain, Maryland.  A large force of rebels is amassed at New-Market, eight miles from Frederick, Maryland. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 9.  Rebel cavalry attacked our force stationed at Williamsburg, Virginia, but our forces have succeeded in holding the place.  Rebels are reportedly evacuating Fredericksburgh.  The pirate ship Alabama has reportedly captured the bark Ocean Rover and the schooner Weather Gauge, which, seeing the Ocean Rover in flames, had come to her assistance.  The Alabama has also captured and burned the bark Alert.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 8.  Restrictions on travel have been rescinded and arrests for disloyalty etc. are forbidden, except by direction of the Judge Advocate at Washington.  Gen. McClellan passed through Rockville to-day with his main army reportedly following him.  A fight occurred to-day at Poolesville, Maryland.  Gen. Lovell Rousseau has reportedly crossed the Cumberland river and is moving north.  RICHMOND, September 8.  Gen. Lee issued his celebrated proclamation to the people of Maryland to-day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 7.  Gen. McClellan has left Washington, under orders to drive the enemy from Maryland, with most of his force preceding him.  His headquarters are now established at Rockville, Maryland.  The Schooner Starlight is reportedly captured by the Alabama, near Flores.  Gen. John Pope is relieved of the command of the Army of Virginia, and assigned to that of the Northwest.  Bowling Green, Kentucky, is reportedly occupied by our advance forces under Gen. James Negley.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 6.  A rebel force under command of Gen. Hill is occupying Frederick City.  Bradley T. Johnson has reportedly been made the rebel Provost-Marshal.  Battle ensued to-day at Washington, North Carolina.  Our troops have captured four guns and many prisoners.  The pirate ship Alabama has captured and destroyed the whaler Ocmulgee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday, Sept. 5. The following items are gathered from newspapers and private sources: It is believed the rebels have crossed in some force this side of Point of Rocks, and subsequently for the most part recrossed into Virginia, as though hesitating to make the experiment of getting a lodgment in Maryland. The rebels have thrown shells across the river at canal boats, etc., which, however, did no damage.  Col. Thos. H. Ford took command of the forces on Maryland Heights.  Forces are stationed at Solomon's Gap and Sandy Hook, near Harper's Ferry.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Thursday Aug. 4.   A man professing to have made his escape from the neighborhood of Leesburgh on Wednesday, by swimming the river, arrived within our lines to-day. He states that JACKSON had entered Leesburgh with his troops, and was pushing toward Harper's Ferry. and LONGSTREET, with a considerable force, was marching in the same direction. The rebels are well supplied with artillery. Most of the Union people about Winchester and Leesburgh had made their escape into Maryland. Others were captured by their secession neighbors, while making the attempt, and thrown into prison. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 3.  Gen. Julius White entered Harper's Ferry to-day with his force from Winchester, Virginia.  Upon receipt of the intelligence that JACKSON was marching toward Leesburgh, rebel flags were displayed by many of the inhabitants, in token of their joy at his coming. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 2.  Gen. McClellan has been assigned to the command of the fortifications of Washington and of the troops for the defence of the Capital.  Considerable fighting has occurred to-day between Fairfax Court-house and Washington, the rebels being held in check by Gen. Hooker and Gen. Fitz John Porter.  An engagement occurred at Plymouth, N.C. in which the rebels were thoroughly routed.  CINCINNATI, September 2.  Business has been entirely suspended in this city to-day and martial law is proclaimed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 1.  General Philip Kearny and General Isaac I. Stevens were to-day killed in a severe engagement near Chantilly, Virginia, two miles from Fairfax Court-House, Virginia.  Fredericksburg is reportedly evacuated by Gen. Burnside's army.  Lexington, Kentucky, is reported evacuated by our troops, who fell back on Covington.  There is great excitement in Louisville in anticipation of an attack.  In Tennessee, a four hour fight ensued at Button's Lane.  The rebels, estimated to be 5,000 strong, were opposed to a Union force of only 800 under Col. Elias Dennis.  At the end of the fight, the rebels left Col. Dennis in possession of the field.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, SUNDAY, Aug. 31. Steamer Raritan, Slover, Trenton, N.J., with mdse. to Wm. Jenkins. Steamer Westchester, Nye, Providence, with mdse. to E. Bynner. Bark Bounding Billow, Mayo, Cape Town, C.G.H., July 17, with wool to Bashford  ES  Mouiton. Bark James Smith, Anderson, New-Orleans 25 ds., with wool to master. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 30.  The Second Battle of Bull Run occurred to-day.  Though the Union position was maintained during the day, General Pope ordered, in the night, a general retreat.  Our army fell back toward Centreville.  Reports received of a severe battle near Richmond, Kentucky.  Our forces were outnumbered and fell back to Lexington.  There has also been a fight at Bolivar, Tennessee, where the rebels were repulsed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 29.  Battle commenced to-day at Groveton, near Bull Run.  The Corps of Gen. Sigel was fully engaged.  The battle of this day ended in a victory for our arms, and at night our army rested near its dead and wounded.  The engagement was furious, and the rebels were everywhere repulsed.  Col. Fletcher Webster of the 12th Massachusetts Regiment was killed.  NEW YORK, August 29.  The Seventh N.Y. regiment has returned to New York. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 28.  Gen. Pope has reportedly found Manassas evacuated by the rebels.  Gen. McDowell's column has reached the rebels near Haymarket.  After a prolonged fight, they have driven the entire force of Gen. Jackson back.  RICHMOND, August 28.  City Point, Virginia, is now entirely demolished by Union gunboats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. PAUL, Wednesday, Aug. 27. The latest news from New-Ulm is to Saturday night. This village is nearly burnt up. An arrival from Crow Wing direct brings intelligence that HOLE-IN-THE-DAY, the great Chippewa chief, issued a proclamation that he would not be responsible for the conduct of the Indians after Tuesday, and warning the whites to leave the country before that time. HOLE-IN-THE-DAY sends a dispatch to Commissioner DOLE and Judge COOPER to come up and make a treaty. The Chippewa Agent, WALKER, against whom complaints have been made by the Chippewas, is reported to have committed suicide in a fit of insanity.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, August 26.  Gen. Jackson's forces have reached Manassas, having marched sixty-two miles in less than two days.  They are reportedly now nearly within cannon-shot of Washington.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 25.  A sharp skirmish reportedly occurred to-day at Waterloo Bridge, Virginia.  Reports from Tennessee indicate rebel forces were repulsed in an attack on Fort Donelson.  RICHMOND, August 25.  Gen. Jackson's forces are reportedly on the move toward Manassas by way of Thoroughfare Gap.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORTRESS MONROE, Sunday, Aug. 24. A severe easterly storm has been raging here all day. All is quiet up the James River and also in the army. The Post-office Department is extending its buildings at Old Point for the much needed accommodation of the clerks employed in this office. Adams' Express are also extending their buildings, as their accommodations for freight have been far too limited.  The cable across the bay was repaired yesterday at noon, and the telegraph is now successfully working between this place and Washington.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 23.  To-day, the Rappahannock river bridge was blown up.  Early in the morning, Union artillery all along the line opened on the enemy, along the Rappahannock.  For several hours, a terrific artillery duel was kept up, resulting eventually in the destruction of the bridge.  FORTRESS MONROE, Saturday, Aug. 23. The steamship Cambria, from New-Orleans, and bound to Philadelphia, has put in here short of coal. Fresh troops are daily arriving at Fortress Monroe, and hundreds are returning to their regiments, who have been away sick. The general health of the army is improving. All was quiet at Williamsburgh yesterday.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 22.  Rebel General J.E.B. Stuart's cavalry attacked a train of sick and wounded early this morning at Catlett's Station, Virginia.  NEW YORK, August 22.  A reception was held in this city to-day for General Corcoran.   PHILADELPHIA, August 22.  The telegraph announces the departure from Philadelphia of the iron-clad frigate New Ironsides. She goes to sea with sealed orders, and is intended, it is generally understood in the navy, for most important service. She bears a resemblance to the Black Prince of the Royal Navy. She is 3,500 tons burden, and carries 500 men, a full sailing frigate's crew, and forty-nine United States marines.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 21.  To-day, two rebel regiments crossed the Rappahannock in face of Gen. Sigel's batteries, which opened on them, killing many and driving the rest back in confusion.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, August 20.  The Sioux Indians to-day attacked Fort Ridgely, Minnesota, and were repulsed.  WASHINGTON, August 20.  The rebels have reportedly driven in our pickets between Culpeper Court-House and the Rappahannock.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>FORTRESS MONROE, Tuesday Aug. 19.  The Richmond Enquirer wants to know where their friends and reporters all are that used to give them reliable information concerning the movements of Gen. McCLELLAN'S army. It adds :  QN Where are they all? We have heard nothing from them of late. Have they all gone over to the Federals? QN  The same paper also contains the message of JEFFERSON DAVIS in which he speaks in the highest terms of his soldiers. He says  QN They have driven Gen. MCCLELLAN from the borders of our capital, and before another Autumn sets in they will have recovered every inch of ground that we have lost. QN  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 18.  Reports received that the rear guard of Gen. McClellan's army has crossed the Chickahominy on its way toward Fort Monroe.  General Pope's army is now reportedly in retreat.  RICHMOND, August 18.  To-day, the Confederate States congress reconvened.  MEMPHIS, Monday, Aug. 11, 1862.  All doubt of the destruction of the Arkansas is at last removed. Gen. BRECKINRIDGE telegraphed her fate to Gen. VAN DORN, and the dispatches are published in the Mississippian.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 17.  Gen. McClellan's advance forces have reached Hampton from Harrison's Landing.  WASHINGTON, Sunday, Aug. 17. We have received the following advises from the headquarters of Gen. SIGEL, Crooked Run, dated 5 P.M. Aug. 16: Eight prisoners were taken yesterday by scouting parties from the First Virginia Cavalry, under command of Major KEEPS. The prisoners confirm previous reports in regard to the precipitate retreat of JACKSON. JACKSON's men are deserting him by Hundreds, and prisoners say deserters are more numerous than forced enlistments. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 16.  Union troops have reportedly evacuated Harrison's Landing, Virginia.  The rebels made a feign of an attempt to cross the Rapidan but were driven back.  Gen. McClellan's advance forces have arrived at Williamsburgh, Virginia.  ST. LOUIS, August 16.  A fight has reportedly occurred in Charlton County, Missouri.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOWLING GREEN, Ky., Friday, Aug. 15, 1862. All sorts of rumors and reports, some of them of the most startling character, have been in circulation, greatly to the excitement of the public mind, during the last twenty-four hours. It was currently reported, and the report has found its way into the newspapers, that an engagement had taken place between some of the National soldiers, stationed at this place, and a part of MORGAN's men, in Allen County, fourteen miles from here. None of MORGAN's men have been in that locality, nor has any engagement been had. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 14.  The President issued a draft order to commence September 1.  Gen. Burnside's Corps d'Armee has reportedly arrived at Fredericksburgh.  RICHMOND, August 14.  Some days ago, says the Macon Telegraph, the citizens of Lee County held a public meeting in reference to negro impressment, at which they appointed Mr. C.M. IRVIN to correspond with the War Department by telegraph, and ascertain it the impressment had been authorized and required by the Secretary of War. If it had, they resolved, like good citizens, to acquiesce in the requisition. if not, they determined not to surrender their negroes. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 13.  A disastrous collision occurred to-day between the steamers Peabody and West Point on the Potomac River.  Approximately 80 convalescing soldiers were lost in the accident.  RICHMOND, the Richmond Dispatch, Aug. 12. The prelude to the battle of Saturday evening occurred on Friday, in Culpepper County, beyond the Rapidan River, in a skirmish between the advance of our army and a large force of the enemy. The latter retreated with some loss in killed and wounded, and twenty-one prisoners fell into our hands, including three commissioned officers, who arrived here by way of Lynchburgh, on Sunday night. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 12.  There has been a reconnaissance in force from Gen. Pope's army in the neighborhood of Slaughter Mountain, near Cedar Mountain, Virginia.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Aug. 12. Accounts from Culpepper, dated yesterday, speaking of Saturday's fight, say that so heavy was the fire to which our comparatively small number of men was exposed, the only wonder is that the entire command was not completely annihilated at the end of half an hour, instead of our bringing off so large a proportion of our force at the expiration of an hour and a half. The prisoners report that their own troops were mowed down by our fire like grass. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, August 11.  Independence, Missouri, has reportedly been captured by the rebels.  WASHINGTON, August 11.  At Culpeper, Virginia, the rebels sent a flag of truce to ask permission to bury their dead from the battle of Cedar Mountain.  The day was spent burying the dead.  A guerilla fight has reportedly occurred near Williamsport, Tennessee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Aug. 6. The steamship Golden Gate, HUDSON, Commander, sailed hence for Panama on the 21st ult., having 95 cabin passengers, 147 in the second cabin and steerage and 95 crew. She had also  SX 1,400,000 in treasure. On the 27th ult., at 4:45 P.M., when fifteen miles north of Manzanilla, while the passengers were dining, an alarm of fire was heard. The steamer was promptly beaded for the shore, three and a half miles distant, the flames meanwhile making fearful headway.  About one hundred, including five children, swam, or were washed ashore, alive. The ship burned to the waters' edge, and soon disappeared. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 9.  A battle commenced to-day at Cedar Mountain, Virginia.  The War Department has issued regulations for enrollment and draft of troops.  ST. LOUIS, August 8.  Guerillas at Stockton, Missouri, have been defeated.  LOUISVILLE, Friday, Aug. 8. Paymaster SPEED has just arrived from Corinth. He reports the safety of all the paymasters stated to have been recently captured near Humboldt. The story arose from the destruction of the trestle work, on the 28th ult., of the Mobile and Ohio Railroad, ten miles north of Jackson, by 150 of BAXTER's rebel guerrillas. HARLTON, the senior paymaster, stopped over night at Humboldt.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 8.  Gen. Pope's forces have reportedly fallen back slightly and are concentrating at Culpeper Court-house, Virginia.  BROOKLYN, August 7.  Considerable damage was done by the severe storm on Tuesday evening, in this city and vicinity. A number of small crafts were wrecked in Gowanus Bay, and vessels were forced from their fastenings along the docks, on the river front, by the violence of the wind, and several small frame buildings in the outskirts of the city, together with fences and outhouses, were more or less injured. So far as known, the lightning did not strike any building within the city limits.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, August 7.  A guerilla fight occurred to-day near Kirksville, Missouri.  The rebels were defeated.   WASHINGTON, August 7.  The English steamer Ladona has been captured.  The rebels crossed the Rapidan River and have advanced toward Culpeper Court-house and Madison Court-house, Virginia.  PHILADELPHIA, August 7.  BEANY, SON  ES  CO., at Chester, Penn., have received a contract from the Government for the construction of an iron gunboat, which is intended more particularly for service in rivers. She will be 236 feet long, 35 feet beam, and 12 feet depth of hold, and will be a side-wheel steamer, with a rudder at each end, similar to the Miami.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 6.  Word has been received that the rebel ram, Arkansas, has been destroyed.  Three thousand prisoners were recently exchanged.  Gen. Hooker has reportedly retired in the night from Malvern Hill.  GEN. CRAWFORD's HEADQUARTERS, NEAR CULPEPPER, Wednesday, Aug. 6, 1862. Nearly the whole army of Virginia is now on the move forward in the direction of the enemy. Gen. MCDOWELL arrived here to-day, and fixed his headquarters at the fine residence of Mr. WALLACK, of the Washington Star. Gen. RICKETT's, HARTSOFF's and DURYEA's commands came with him. Gen. BANKS' army is on the march. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 5.  Today, a battle commenced at Baton Rouge, Louisiana.  Malvern Hill is reportedly occupied by our troops after a fight lasting 1 1E2 hours.  Union gunboats shelled a rebel encampment beyond Malvern Hill.  Gen. Robert McCook was assassinated by the rebels near Salem, Tennessee.   WAR DEPARTMENT, Aug. 5, 1862. Ordered, That the use of the telegraph lines being required for military purposes, all persons actually employed in constructing and operating telegraph lines, at the date of the order calling for three hundred thousand men, be exempt from military duty, so long as they remain in such service. By order of the President. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 4.  The President has ordered a draft for 300,000 men for nine months.  HEADQUARTERS OF THE ARMY OF VIRGINIA, Aug. 3, 1862.  Major-General Halleck: The reconnoitering columns under Gen. CRAWFORD crossed the Rapidan and pushed forward to Orange Court-House, yesterday, and took possession of the town, which was occupied by two regiments of the enemy's cavalry, under Gen. ROBERTSON. Eleven of the enemy were killed and fifty-two taken prisoners. Among the latter are one Major, two Captains and two Lieutenants. Our loss was 2 killed and 3 wounded. The enemy retired in such haste as to leave their wounded in our hands.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 3.  A reconnoitering party from the Army of the Potomac has reportedly been seen within 14 miles of Petersburgh, Virginia.  The steamer Columbia has been captured with a valuable cargo on-board.  Gen. MCCLELLAN recently telegraphed to Washington that he could not get milk for sick soldiers, that the Secessionists would not furnish it, and that Union men charge high prices. Gen. HALLECK telegraphed back:  QN If Secessionists won't furnish milk, seize their cows and milk them yourselves. Have military board to fix the price at which Unionists shall sell, and if they refuse to take that price, seize from them also. QN  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 2.  Reports received that a reconnoitering column from Gen. Pope's army have crossed the Rapidan and have taken Orange Courthouse, Virginia.  Railroad and telegraph lines between Orange Court-house and Gordonsville have been destroyed.   ST. LOUIS, August 2.  There has been a brush with the rebels at Ozark, Missouri.  In a speech delivered at the great war meeting in St. Louis, the Hon. F.P. BLAIR made a stirring speech, urging the people to comply with Gen. SCHOFIELD's order providing for a general enrollment.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, August 1.  A severe fight has occurred at Newark, Missouri.  WASHINGTON, August 1.  A retaliatory order has reportedly been issued by the rebel Government.  Gen. Pope and his officers are declared to not be entitled to the privileges of prisoners of war.  MEMPHIS, Thursday, July 31. Several gentlemen from Brownsville arrived here last evening. They bring some particulars of a rebel raid by Col. FAULKNER on that place on Friday last. Every man that was there buying cotton was taken prisoner, and  SX 120,000 worth of cotton taken from them. Four hundred bales of cotton were burned, 500 National cavalry arrived the same evening.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OLD POINT, Near Fortress Monroe, Thursday, July 31, 1862. We have been in a considerable state of excitement all day -- not so much from what we know here about ourselves, as from what we read in the New-York papers,  QN Scare at Norfolk QN  --  QN Apprehended Attack from the Rebel Jackson QN  --  QN Suffolk in Danger, QN  etc., are very big-sounding heads, that, in all probability, cause more commotion in Gotham than they do at Fortress Monroe. Still, where there is so much smoke, there must be fire. and, although there is very little  QN scare QN  discoverable in these regions, every thing is denoting that we are on the eve of some great event.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 30.  A portion of Commodore Porter's mortar fleet has arrived in Hampton Roads.  The negro story telegraphed from Washington, to the effect that the rebels are evacuating Richmond, is a very good one, but somewhat doubtful. The great bulk of the rebel army is not in the city of Richmond, but somewhat nearer our own lines, and on both sides of the James River -- as we very well know.  The regiments in and about Richmond are really leaving it, the object probably is to move to some point where they are needed -to move north to Gordonsville or south to Suffolk, or in some other direction which Gen. HALLECK, and not we, should know.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 29.  A Memphis correspondent, relates the following incident of the ingenious manner in which a rebel telegraph operator read Gen. HALLECK's dispatches for four days.  Gen. HALLECK's messages to Commodore DAVIS, Gen. CUTTIS, and the commandant of this post, have all passed over it. Little of the line is guarded, out of late the rebels have refrained from cutting the wires. Their unusual amiability is now explained. they found a better use for it! For a week the Memphis operators have detected something wrong in the working of the instruments, and surmised that some outsider was sharing their telegraphic secrets. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, CENTRAL RAILROAD, July 29.  When the train from the West, on the Central Railroad, reached Frederick's Hall, a station 50 miles from this city, it was met by a rumor that the Yankee cavalry had made another raid from Fredericksburgh, and had possession of the track at Anderson turn-out, 10 miles below Beaver Dam, and 30 miles from Richmond. The telegraph wire not being in working order, there was no means of ascertaining the truth of this report. Under the circumstances the conductor, not choosing to risk the passengers and train, took an extra locomotive and ran down to Andersons on a reconnaissance.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 27.  Report received that the British steamer Memphis has ran out of Charleston.  Gen. Pope has left Washington to meet up with his army.  The telegraph is of infinite service in transmitting military orders, but it is subject to some most serious disadvantages. One is, that it offers no means of verifying on the instant the genuineness of its message. If a rebel agent, for example, could get control of an office between Washington and MCCLELLAN's headquarters, he could send any order he might choose in the name of the President to Gen. McCLELLAN, and the latter could not detect the imposition until, perhaps, it might be too late.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Saturday, July 26.  FLOUR steady. WHEAT firm, but closed heavy.  RYE in demand at 65c. WHISKY Imports 17,000.  OATS steady, 35,000 bushels. CORITH, Tennessee, July 26 by way of U.S. Military Telegraph.  To Brig.-Gen. J.T. Quimby, Columbus, Ky.: GENERAL: Examine the baggage of all speculators coming South, and, when they have specie, turn them back. If medicine and other contraband articles, arrest them and confiscate the contraband article. Jews should receive special attention. (Signed) U.S. GRANT. Major-General. 

 </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MEMPHIS, July 25.  The Steamer Cuba has ran the blockade into Mobile.  WASHINGTON, July 25.  The President to-day issued a proclamation warning rebels of the provisions of the Confiscation act.  Mr. G.W. STEVENS, in moving an adjournment of the Court, spoke as follows: MAY IT PLEASE THE COURT: A telegram has just brought us the news that the last of the statesmen, with a single exception, of the early days of the Re public, has ceased to exist. Ex-President VAN BUREN departed this life to-day at his residence in Kinderhook. It is not necessary, and perhaps it would not be fitting for me to speak of the distinguished services of this eminent deceased. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 24.  Gen. Halleck left Washington for Fortress Monroe to-day.  The British steamer Tubal Cain has been captured.  LOUISVILLE, Thursday July 24.  Gen. BOYLE also sent orders to Col. GARVIN, commanding at Henderson, to use rigorous measures to clear the rebels out of the adjoining counties. Gen. GREEN CLAY SMITH telegraphs from Stanford that he is still pursuing MORGAN. Gen. BOYLE replies:  QN Capture him, or drive him out of the State. QN  The dispatch from Cincinnati out night, stating that our cavalry had overtaken MORGAN's band, from Mount Sterling, etc., is without foundation. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 23.  Gen. Pope has reportedly ordered the arrest of all disloyal male citizens in the lines of his army.  A cavalry expedition from Fredericksburgh has reportedly met and defeated two bodies of rebel cavalry. LOUISVILLE, Wednesday, July 23. Yesterday morning trains from Nashville, northward, and Louisville, southward, met at Mitchellsville, and both returned, owing to the report that 1,000 rebel cavalry were near Richland, Tenn. Gov. MORTON, of Indiana, sent 1,000 infantry and artillery to Henderson, which arrived there in the morning. Simultaneously one of our gunboats went up the river with a considerable force to protect Union residents.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 22.  The President issued an order to-day, calling for the seizure of supplies needed by our armies and directing that negroes should be employed as laborers, giving them wages for their labor.  The President also ordered that foreigners should not be required by military commanders to take the oath of allegiance.  The Overland Mail service has been suspended, preliminary to changing the route, which will strike off at Julesburgh, and follow the Cherokee trail through Bridger's Pass to Salt Lake, and thence to the Pacific. This arrangement will save one hundred and fifty miles of travel, and protect the coaches from Indian depredations.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, Monday, July 21, 1862. Cold easterly winds and a lower pressure ushered to the morning of the second day's racing here. As a natural result, the unfavorable weather resulted in not more than fifteen hundred people present. The comparative absence of the fair representatives of the youth and beauty of Boston was a noticeable feature, for there is no doubt that they would have turned out in great numbers if the day had proved propitious. The track was in much better condition than on the previous day, the rain having dried up, and rendered the going comparatively good. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 20.  An expedition from Fredericksburgh has reportedly destroyed several miles of railroad and telegraph lines at Beaver Dam Creek, property of the Virginia Central Railroad.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, July 19. The recently-published orders of Gen. POPE are highly popular with military men as well as civilians, and their execution will remove much complaint on the part of the soldiers. So far as is known at the War Department, there is no foundation for the rumored defeat of Stonewall JACKSON, by Gen. SIGEL. It is not known that any engagement has taken place of late. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 19.  Gen. Butler has reportedly issued an order which emancipates certain negroes.  WASHINGTON, July 14.  In the Senate, on Saturday, proceedings were commenced with an Executive session. When the doors were opened, the resolution declaring the meaning of the act authorizing the President to take possession of all the railroads and telegraph lines, was passed. It was subsequently passed in the House. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, July 18.  Gen. D. E. Twiggs, who retired last year as the oldest Confederate general, died to-day of pneumonia.  CINCINNATI, July 16. We have dispatches from our special correspondent at Lexington, up to 3 o'clock yesterday afternoon. It is positively stated that MORGAN, with a force of 2,500, was at Midway, on the Lexington and Frankfort Railroad, the track of which at that place had been torn up. The train that left Frankfort for Lexington, in the morning, had returned, the conductor learning that powder had been placed under the pier of the bridge at Midway, with the intention of blowing it up as soon as the cars reached the bridge. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 17.  Congress has now adjourned.  The town of Cynthiana, Kentucky, has been taken from the rebels.  BOSTON, July 17. -- Arr. ship Cavalier, Liverpool. bark Sumter, Valparaiso. brig Alice Franklin, Ardrossan. schr. Thriver, Monrovia. also prize schr. Louise, from Mungan Bay, S.C., with 130 bales of cotton, captured by the Albatross. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LOUISVILLE, Ky., Wednesday, July 16. The rebel Col. MORGAN was at Midway yesterday, at noon, and cut the telegraph wires and tore up the railroad. He took away with him everything he could convert to his use. He had four 12-pound howitzers, but it is said only six rounds of ammunition. Last evening he left for Georgetown, and encamped there on GORO's farm. He said he meant to visit Lexington and Frankfort before he got through his job.  The damages to the railroad and telegraph wires at Midway have been repaired, but the bridge burnt by the rebels at Keysers has not yet been reconstructed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 15 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 15.  Yesterday, a battle commenced at Fayetteville, Arkansas.  To-day, Gen. Steven's division from South Carolina has reportedly arrived in Hampton Roads to reinforce Gen. McClellan.  The rebel iron-clad gunboat Arkansas has run past our vessels and has succeeded in reaching the rebel batteries at Vicksburgh.  The Union iron-clad Carondelet put up a gallant fight against the Arkansas before it got through.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 14.  Gen. John Pope has assumed command of the Army of Virginia and has issued an order to his men which concludes  QN I am sure you long for an opportunity to win the distinction you are capable of achieving....Meantime I desire you to dismiss from your minds certain phrases,... I hear constantly of  QN taking strong positions and holding them, QN  of  QN lines of retreat, QN  and of  QN bases of supplies. QN   Success and glory are in the advance, disaster and shame lurk in the rear. Let us act on this understanding, and it is safe to predict that your banners shall be inscribed with many a glorious deed and that your names will be dear to your countrymen forever. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LOUISVILLE, Ky., Sunday, July 13. At New-Hope, Nelson County, at 11 o'clock last night, a party of the Thirty-fifth Ohio Regiment, under Lieut.-Col. MOORE, encountered 450 rebel cavalry, under JACK ALLEN, a half mile south of the railroad. After a brisk fire of musketry for twenty minutes the enemy were routed and fled. There were no National casualties. Blood along the road was found by the skirmishers we sent out, but no enemy. Later accounts say that these guerrillas burned the town of Lebanon, and robbed the Commercial Bank located there. Telegraphic communication is perfected to Nashville, but not over the Lexington branch line. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, July 12.  To-day, Gen. Albert Pike resigned his command in the Confederate army.   WASHINGTON, July 12.  Gen. Curtis has reportedly arrived at Helena, Arkansas.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, July 12. The reading of the journal was dispensed with and the Senate went into Executive Session. After a few moments the doors were opened. Mr. WILSON, of Massachusetts, (Rep.,) called up the resolution declaring the meaning of the act authorizing the President to take possession of railroads and telegraph lines. The bill prevents the construction of any line of railroad under said act. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 11.  To-day, President Lincoln named Gen. Halleck to be General-in-Chief of all United States land forces.  WASHINGTON, Friday, July 11. Mr. STEVENS, of Pennsylvania, (Rep.,) from the Committee on Ways and Means, reported the final Appropriation bill from that source for miscellaneous objects, including an item of half a million of dollars on account of the emancipation of the slaves of the District of Columbia and those to be made free under the Confiscation bill, looking to their colonization and the securing of land outside of the limits of the United States for that purpose.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 10.  Gen. Burnside's forces are reportedly now encamped at Newport's News.  THE LATE BATTLES. -- The best item of good news which the President brings back with him from the Peninsula is one to the effect that the rumors of losses in the late battles were greatly exaggerated. and the telegraph attributes to him a statement that the entire losses on our part, in the several engagements, do not exceed, in killed, wounded and missing, ten or eleven thousand. This is certainly much more like the truth than the preposterous rebel statements of sixty thousand Union loss, thirty thousand of whom were captured</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Wednesday, July 9. The telegraph dispatch from Albany, yesterday, that the Buffalo Common Council had appropriated  SX 80,000 to aid in raising a new volunteer regiment, is untrue. There are legal difficulties in the way of the appropriation. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 8, 1862.  President Lincoln and Gen. Burnside have reportedly arrived at Fortress Monroe.  The president is scheduled to proceed up the James river.  An expedition up the Roanoke River has started from Plymouth, North Carolina.  NEW YORK, MONDAY, July 7.  U.S. steam transport S.R. Spaulding, Howes, Fortress Monroe 36 hours, with 426 sick and wounded soldiers. She towed from Fortress Monroe to this port the Hospital ship St. Mark, with wounded soldiers from the Army of the Potomac. U.S. Hospital ship St. Mark, Colley, Fortress Monroe 36 hours, with 284 wounded and sick soldiers from the Army of the Potomac.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Monday July 7. U.S. steam transport S.R. Spaulding, Howes, Fortress Monroe 36 hours, with 426 sick and wounded soldiers. She towed from Fortress Monroe to this port the Hospital ship St. Mark, with wounded soldiers from the Army of the Potomac. U.S. Hospital ship St. Mark, Colley, Fortress Monroe 36 hours, with 284 wounded and sick soldiers from the Army of the Potomac. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, Saturday July 5, 1862. Oats are quiet and dropping, including Canada, at 41c. TO 44c.. Western, at 42 1E2c. TO 44c.,and State at 44c. TO 45c. HAY -- North River Bale is in request at 55c. TO 70c. 100 lbs. HOPS -- Continue in demand at uniform rates, including last year's crop, at 15c. TO 20c. lb. MOLASSES -- Sales to-day 134 hhds., including Porto Rico at 35c., and Cuba Muscovado, part at 26c. TO 27c. gallon. NAVAL STORES -- Have been very quiet to-day, including Spirits Turpentine, which is quoted at from  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 37 1E2 gallon. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-YORK, July 5, 1862 -- 6 P.M. The reported receipts of the principal kinds of produce, since our last, have been:   COFFEE -- Sales to-day 750 bags St. Domingo, for export, on private terms. and 80 bags Jamaica, at 21c. TO 21 1E2c. lb. Stock on hand this evening, 168,945 bags and 12,975 mats, including 131,377 bags Rio, 18,500 bags Maracaibo, 12,975 mats and 2,508 bags Java, 5,119 bags Costa Rica, 4,585 bugs Cearn, 3,150 bags Laguayra, 2,850 bags St. Domingo, 426 bags Savanilia, and 385 bags Jamaica. COCOA -- Sales, 35 bags Maracaibo, in bond, at 31 1E8c. lb. COTTON -- is quiet, to-day, at former prices. Middlings, 38c. TO 39c lb. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 4.  Gen. McClellan issued a congratulatory address to his army, in which he declared that it should enter Richmond.  The CSS Teaser was victorious today as a lucky shot caught her opponent, the USS Maratanza, in just the right spot and exploded her boiler.  A search of the wreckage of the Teaser reveals a number of interesting items: floating mines ready to be laid in the James River.  QN peculiar fuzes QN  which were sent to Washington for examination. and, most intriguing of all, an observation balloon and the equipment needed to launch it.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 3.  Gen. McClellan's army remains entrenched at Harrison's Landing, protected by artillery and gunboats.  WASHINGTON, Sunday, June 29, 1862.  It appears that the telegraphic communication between the White House and Gen. MCCLELLAN was not broken until near one o'clock on Saturday, and then the wire was cut at Dispatch Station, eleven miles out.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 2.  Gov. Morgan has appealed to the people of New York to volunteer.  WASHINGTON, July 2.  On the James River, Gen. McClellan has moved his forces from Malvern Hill to Harrison's Landing in a driving rain, the site chosen for the gunboat protection it offers.  BOSTON, July 1. -- Arr., ships Tranguebar, London. Charlemagne, Trepan. bark Azor, Faval. ship Autocrat, Liverpool. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 1.  The Battle of Malvern Hill occurred to-day, before Richmond.  Our troops were more successful this day than on those preceding, having been victorious in every action.   Rebel casualties ran high.   The President announced his decision to call for 300,000 more volunteers.  The tax bill was approved.  A brilliant cavalry engagement has reportedly occurred near Boonsville, Mississippi.  The rebels attacked our forces, but were repulsed after seven hours' hard fighting.  </description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
