<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 30 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Saturday, June 29. FLOUR, 5c. lower. WHEAT, declined 1c.. sales 61c. for N. 1. 56c. for No. 2, in store. CORN, closed heavy, at 23c. for Mixed, in store. OATS, firm. Receipts -- 3,000 bbls. Flour, 38,000 bush. Wheat, 56,000 bush. Corn. Shipments -- 95,000 bush. Wheat. FREIGHT, steady, at 7 1E3c. on Wheat to Buffalo. Exchange on New-York, unchanged.  ALBANY, Saturday, June 29. FLOUR -- The receipts are in excess of the demand, and the stock is accumulating. WHEAT -- No sales. OATS -- Sales 13,000 bushels Western at 28c. CORN less active. sales in small parcels, Western Mixed, 45c., at East Albany. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Friday, June 28 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR quiet and unchanged. WHEAT firmer: sales 12,000 bushels No. 1 Milwaukee Club, at 74 c.. 6,610 bushels do, at 75c.. 6,000 bushels No. 2 do., at 70c.. 12,000 bushels No. 2 Chicago Spring at 70c. CORN steady. sales 14,000 bushels at 35c. OATS steady. sales 7,660 bushels at 22c. WHISKY steady. sales 50 bbls., at 14 1E4c. CANAL FREIGHTS steady at 10 1E2c. on Corn. 11 1E4c. on Wheat to New-York. Imports. --8,000 bbls. Flour, 65,000 bushels Wheat, 40,000 bushels Corn. Canal Exports -- 5,000 bbls. Flour, 144,000 bushels Wheat, 72,000 bushels Corn, 11,000 bushels Oats. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Thursday, June 27. FLOUR quiet. WHEAT dull and 2c. lower. Sales at 62c.  TO 63c. for No 1 in store. CORN steady and active. 22c for mixed in store. OATS firm. Receipts: 4,000 bbls. Flour, 38,000 bush. Wheat 136,000 bush. Corn. Shipments: 4 200 bbls Flour 15 000 bush Wheat, 14 000 bush. Corn, FREIGHTS, 7 1E8c TO 8c. on Wheat, for Budain. Exchange on New-York 1E2  TO  cent, discount for Gold.   BUFFALO, Thursday, June 27. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT dull, heavy and lower. sales this A M of 6 000 bush. No. 1 Chicago Spring at 69c.. 6 000 bush. do. at 70c.. 6,000 bush. No. 1 Milwaukee Club at 75c. CORN dull. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, Thursday, June 27.  At 3 o'clock this morning, George P. Kane, Marshal of Police of this city, was arrested at his house by order of Gen. Banks, and conveyed to Fort McHenry, where he is now held a prisoner.  Gen. Banks issued a proclamation following the arrest.  PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, June 27. FLOUR easier. holders are free sellers at the last quotations. Spring Wheat, superfine at  SX 4 50 TO   SX 4 62 1E2. Western,  SX 4 75 TO  SX 5. WHEAT drooping, sales 3 000 bushels Fed at  SX 1 18 TO  SX 1 22. White,  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 40 CORN plenty. sales 2 000 bushels Southern Yellow at 53c. Prime BACON HAMS, 10 1E2c. LARD quiet at 9c. TO 9 1E4c. Solid BUTTER 9c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description> PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, June 25. FLOUR dull and drooping. superfine,  SX 4 25 TO  SX 5. WHEAT dull. Pennsylvania Red,  SX 1 18 TO  SX 1 24. White,  SX 1 30 TO 1 40. CORN firm. held at 52c. TO 53c. PROVISIONS dull. WHISKY firm at 16 1E2c.   BUFFALO, Tuesday, June 25 -- 6 P.M. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT dull and heavy. only one sale was reported -- 7,000 bush. No. 1 Milwaukee Club at 75c. CORN firm and in good demand, at an advance of 1c.. sales 60,000 bush. at 35c. OATS steady. sales 10,000 bush. at 21 1E2c. TO 22c. for Western and Canada. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, June 24. FLOUR dull. WHEAT firm. sales 3,000 bushels Red, at  SX 1 20 TO  SX 1 23. White,  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 40. CORN advanced. sales 4,000 bushels Yellow, at 52c. Provisions quiet. WHISKY dull. at 16 1E2c.  TO 17c.   ALBANY, Tuesday, June 25. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT sarable in small lots only at  SX 1.40 to Woite Canadian and  SX 1 40 TO  SX 1.45 for White Michigan Coas without change at 46c  TO  47c. for Western mixed this side and at East Albany. OATS in large supply at 28c. for Chicago and 30c. for State. sales 20,000 bushels. WHISKY 16c. Received by Central Railroad for New-York, 6,426 bbls. Flour, 100 bbls. Corn Meal, 412 bbls. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Monday, June 24 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR dull. WHEAT dull. no sales. CORN firm. sales 35,000 bushels at 34c. A stock of sound light hot was selling, to the extent of 37,000 bushels, at 27c.  TO 28c. OATS steady. sales 19,000 bushels at 21 1E2c.  TO 22c. WHISKY -- Sales 100 bbls. at 14c. CANAL FREIGHTS lower and dull. at 10c. on Corn, and 11c. on Wheat, to New-York. Imports -- 16,000 bbls. Flour, 126,000 bushels Wheat, 34,000 bushels Corn, 22,000 bushels Oats. Exports -- 1,300 bbls. Flour, 118,000 bushels Wheat, 67,000 bushels Corn, 9,000 bushels Oats, and 1,500 bushels Rye. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Saturday, June 22. FLOUR dull. WHEAT, no sales. CORN in good demand and scarce. sales, 6,000 bush Western Mixed to arrive, at 46c. OATS dull, at 32c  TO 32 1E2c for Chicago. sales 10,000 bush. WHISKY at 16 1E4c Received by Central Railroad from Boston and East, 1,491 bbls. Flour, 80 bbls. Wheat. for New-York, 5,258 bbls. Flour. 1,211 sacks Wheat. 554 bbls. Whisky, 50 bbls. Pork. Shipped per tows to New-York, June 21, 39,800 bush. Corn, 650 bush. Rye, 16,500 bush. Wheat, 21,000 bush. Oats, 7,000 bush. Feed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, June 22. FLOUR quiet. Superfine,  SX 5 TO  SX 5 12 1E2. Extra,  SX 5 25 TO  SX 5 50. Family,  SX 5 75 TO  SX 6. Fancy,  SX 6 25 TO  SX 7. WHEAT dull. sales 3,000 bushels Red, at  SX 1 20 TO  SX 1 25. White,  SX 1 35 CORN quiet at 51c. Cuba SUGAR, 4 3E4c TO 5 1E2c. COFFEE firm. WHISEY firmer -- 16 1E2c.  TO 17c. BUFFALO, Saturday, June 22. FLOUR steady and in moderate demand WHEAT dull. sales 18,000 bushels No. 1 Milwaukee Club, 78c. COEN in fair demand. 6,000 bushels at 33c. WHISKY nominal at 14 1E2c. CANAL FREIGHTS dull. Imports -- 7,000 bbls. Flour, 72 000 bushels Wheat. 2,000 bushels Corn. Exports -- 2,000 bbls. Flour, 94,000 bush.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SPECIAL DISPATCH FROM WASHINGTON. WASHINGTON, Tuesday, June 18.  The Government had the misfortune the other night to drop overboard one of the locomotives it was transporting from this city to Alexandria. It went down in forty feet of water. DUNBAR SCHOONMAKER, a private in Company B, of the Twentieth Regiment, stationed at the Junction, was accidentally killed on Saturday, by the discharge of a gun. The body of the deceased was sent home under an escort. He was a son of the County Clerk of Ulster County. Maj. GATES has been elected Lieutenant-Colonel of the Twentieth Regiment.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SPECIAL DISPATCH FROM WASHINGTON. WASHINGTON, Tuesday, June 18.  The experiment of a balloon telegraph was tried to-day to a limited extent, the balloon being allowed only a few hundred feet elevation. The arrangement for telling out the wire were rudely constructed, and the wire was too small for practical purposes, yet the instruments worked well, and the practicabifity of telegraphing from balloons was fully demonstrated. The operations were witnessed by Prof. HENRY, and several other scientific gentlemen, who apparently took much interest in the affair, and expressed themselves highly pleased with the performance. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SPECIAL DISPATCH FROM WASHINGTON. WASHINGTON, Tuesday, June 18. The rebel soldiers at Manassas Junction complain bitterly of being compelled to dig and delve in the ditches, during the excessive heat, while the negroes who have been pressed into the service are lazy and worthless for the purposes to which they have been for a time assigned. There are hundreds upon the sick list, and the men who have not been accustomed to labor are breaking down constantly. Water is hardly to be had for ordinary purposes, to say nothing of the opportunity to bathe. The hospital there is fast becoming crowded. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Monday, June 18 --1 P.M. FLOUR steady. WHEAT dull. sales this morning of 6,00 bushels extra Wilwaukee Club, at 90c. CORN dull. sales 6,200 bushels at 32c. OATS in good demand. sales 52,000 bushels at 20c.  TO 22 1E2c. Lake Imports -- 8,000 bbls. Flour. 160,000 bushels Wheat. 40,000 bushels Corn. 40,000 bushels Oats. Exports 4,000 bbls. Flour. 313,000 bushels Wheat. 6,000 bushels Corn.. 18,000 bushels Oats. 7,000 bushels Rye. Saturday's Imports -- 16,000 bbls. Flour. 600,000 bushels Wheat. 170,000 bushels Corn. 23,000 bushels Oats. Saturday's Exports -- 1,500 bbls. Flour. 121,000 bushels Wheat. 13,000 bushels Corn. 8,000 bushels Oats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 17.  Reports receive this day of a successful engagement with the Rebels at Booneville, MO.  PHILADELPHIA, Monday, June 17. FLOUR quiet. Superfine,  SX 5 TO  SX 5 50. Extra,  SX 5 75 TO  SX 6. Fancy,  SX 6 25 TO  SX 7. WHEAT dull, with fair receipts. Red,  SX 1 22 TO  SX 1 25. White,  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 40. RYE steady, at 64c. CORN unsettled and lower. sales 8,500 bush. Yellow, 50c. COFFEE -- Sales 500 bags Laguayra, at 13c. PROVISIONS dull. WHISKY steady, at 16 1E2c. TO 17c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, June 16. FLOUR quiet. Superfine,  SX 5 TO  SX 5 50. Extra,  SX 5 75 TO  SX 6. Fancy,  SX 6 25 TO  SX 7 WHEAT dull. with fair receipts. Red.  SX 1 22 TO  SX 1 25. White,  SX 1 90 TO  SX 1 40. RYE steady, at 64c. CORN unsettled and lower. sales 8,500 bush. Yellow, 50c COFFEE -- Sales 500 bags Laguayra, at 13c. PROVISIONS dull. WHISKY steady, at 16 1E2c. TO 17c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Monday, June 15 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR steady. WHEAT and. sales this morning of 6,000 bushels extra Milwaukee Club, at 90c. CORN dull. sales 6,200 bushels at 32c. OATS in good demand. sales 52,000 bushels at 20c. TO 22 1E2c. Lake Imports -- 8,000 bbls. Flour. 100,000 bushels Wheat. 40,000 bushels Corn. 40,000 bushels Oats. Exports 4,000 bbls, Flour. 313,000 bushels Wheat. 6,000 bushels Corn. 18,000 bushels Oats. 7,000 bushels Rye.Saturday's Imports -- 16,000 bbls. Flour. 600,000 bushels Wheat. 170,000 bushels Corn. 23,000 bushels Oats. Saturday's Exports -- 1,500 bbls. Flour. 121,000 bushels Wheat. 13,000 bushels Corn. 8,000 bushels Oats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OSWEGO, Wednesday, June 12. FLOUR steady.  SX 5 for fancy. WHEAT quiet. CORN nominally at 36c., without sales. OATS dull. CANAL FREIGHTS dull -- Flour, 28c.: WHEAT, 8c., and Corn 7c. to New-York, Lake Imports -- 61,000 bushels Wheat, 22,800 bushels Corn, 2,000 bushels Rye. Canal Exports -- 2,000 bbls. Flour, 24,300 bushels Corn, 6,700 bushel's Oats. BUFFALO, Wednesday, June 12 -- 1 P.M. FLOUR -- Unchanged and in moderate demand. WHEAT unchanged. sales 12,000 bushels No. 1 Chicago Spring, at 82c.. 30,000 bushels Milwaukee Club, at 82c. TO 84c. CORN dull, and no sales. OATS, demand fair. sales 27,000 bushels at 28 1E2c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 13.  Harper's Ferry is reportedly being evacuated to-day by the rebels.  CHICAGO, Wednesday, June 12. FLOUR more active and a shade lower. WHEAT slightly declined. sales at 72c. for No. 1 in store. CORN 1c. lower. sales at 21c. Receipts -- 5,500 bbls. Flour, 51,000 bushels Wheat, 102,000 bushels Corn, 26,000 bushels Oats. ALBANY, Wednesday, June 12. FLOUR more active and prices have a downward tendency. WHEAT, in lots,  SX 1 45 for White Canada and  SX 1 48 for White Michigan. CORN 42c. Whisky 16c.. sales 203 bbls. Shipped by truths to New-York, June 11 -- 99,000 bushels Corn, 250,900 bushels Wheat, 16,000 bushels feed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHICAGO, Wednesday, June 12. FLOUR more active and a shade lower. WHEAT slightly declined. sales at 72c. for No. 1 in store. CORN 1c. lower. sales at 21c. Receipts -- 5,500 bbls. Flour, 51,000 bushels Wheat, 102,000 bushels Corn, 26,000 bushels Oats.  NEW ORLEANS, Wednesday, June 12. COTTON -- Some little inquiry for manufacturing, but no sales. FLOUR,  SX 8 50 TO  SX 9. PORK,  SX 25 TO  SX 26. PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, June 12. FLOUR dull and unsettled. WHEAT declined. sales 5,000 bushels. red  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 34, white  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 14 CORN quiet. sales 7,000 bushels, at 51c. TO 54c. COFFEE -- Rio 11c. TO 12c. WHISKY dull, at 16 1E2c. TO 17c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 11.  A skirmish has occurred at Romney, Western Virginia.  BUFFALO, Tuesday, June 11 -- 6 P.M. FLOUR steady and in moderate home demand. WHEAT -- Market steady, with a fair demand. sales 6,000 bushels No. 1 Chicago Spring, at 82c. 25,000 bushels fair to good Milwaukee Club, at 82c. TO 84c. CORN -- Demand moderate, and market leas firm. sales 26.000 bushels, at 32 1E2c. TO 34c. Other grains quiet and no sales. WHISKY lower. sales 1,300 bbls., at 14c. CANAL FREIGHTS -- 10c. on Corn and 11c. on Wheat to New York. Lake Imports -- 10,000 bbls. Flour, 182,000 bushels Wheat, 81,000 bushels Corn, and 35,000 bushels Oats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON, June 10.  The Union army was to-day routed at Big Bethel, Virginia.  BUFFALO, June 10 -- 6 P.M. FLOUR -- demand moderate and market steady. WHEAT firmer and in fair demand. sales, 24,000 bush. Milwaukee Club, at 82c.. 26,000 bush, ordinary to fair do., at 80c. TO 82c.. 1,000 bush. No. 1 Chicago Spring, at 82 1E2c. TO 83c.. 6,500 bush. No. 2 do., at 80 1E2c. CORN steady. sales, 18,000 bush, out of condition, at 30c.. 37,000 bush., at 32 1E2c. TO 34c.. 7,000 bush prime, at 35c. No sales of other grains. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Sunday June 9.   QN Occasional QN  writes to the Philadelphia Press:  QN The dispatches seized in the telegraph offices are all being collected and brought on here. Mr. SANFORD, of Philadelphia, President of the American Telegraph company, has been appointed to superintend the examination, and will forthwith appoint a necessary force to carry through the examination. QN   LIVERPOOL, Tuesday evening, June 4. In the Cotton market to day the sales reached 15,000 bates, including 7,500 to speculators and exporters, the market closing firm and active. BREADSTUFFS -- Flour very dull. Wheat dull, with a declining tendency. Corn dull. Mixed, 30s. 6d. TO 31s.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, June 6. FLOUR inactive. WHEAT dull. Red,  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 38. White,  SX 1 43 TO 1 50. CORN buoyant. sale 3,000 bushels at 51c. TO 54c. COFFEE -- Rio, 10 5E8c. TO 11 1E2c. PROVISIONS very dull. WHISKY dull at 16 1E2c TO 17c. OSWEGO, Thursday, June 6. FLOUR declined 25c.. sales at  SX 5 for fancy brands. Market for grain decidedly flat no sales CANAL FREIGHTS dull. Flour, 28c.. Wheat 8c. and Corn 7c. to New-Fork. Lake Imports -- 900 bbls. Flour. 15,200 bush.   ST. JOHNS, N.F., Friday night, June 7. Arrangements have been made by which it is confidently expected the mob will do no more violence to the telegraph wires. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Thursday, June 6. FLOUR is very dull. Canadian White WHEAT, in car lots,  SX 1 46. OATS, 30c. for Canada and 31 1E4c. for State. CORN, 46c. at East Albany. sales 6,500 bushels. WHISKY 16c. A lot of 1,700 bushels TIMOTHY SEED sold at  SX 2 12 bushel. Received by Central Railroad, 6th: For Boston and the East -- 1,834 bbls. Flour, 108 lbs. Wool, 1,156 bbls. Pork. for New-York -- 6,188 bbls. Flour. 447 sacks Wheat, 412 bbls. Whisky, 60 bbls. Pork, 700 boxes Cheese, 229 cases Tobacco. Shipped by trains to New-York, June 5 -- 47, 70 bushels Corn, 56,600 bushels Wheat, 21,000. bushel Oats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Wednesday, June 5. FLOUR quiet and steady. WHEAT lower, with fair milling inquiry. sales 37,000 bushels inferior to choice Milwaukee Club, at 90c. TO 95 1E2c. CORN dull and no sales. WHISKY nominal. CANAL FREIGHTS dull and uncharged. Imports -- 9,000 bbls. Flour, 32,000 bushels Wheat. Exports -- 1,200 bbls. Flour, 28,000 bushels Wheat, 23,000 bushels Oats, and 7,000 bushels Rye. PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, June 5. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT firm. sales 4,000 bush. Red at  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 36. White,  SX 1 48. COFFEE -- Rio, 11c. TO 12c. WHISKY dull at 16 1E2c. TO 17c.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, June 4. FLOUR quiet. WHEAT steady and unchanged. CORN dull. sales at 55c. WHISKY dull at 16 1E2c. TO 17c.   BUFFALO, Tuesday June 4 -- 1 P.M. FDOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT dull. sales 2,000 bushels, at 90c. for No. 2 Spring. 96c. for No. 1 co.. and 97c. for Sheboygan Spring. CORN dull. sales 5,000 bushels out of condition, at 32c. CANAL FREIGHTS lower and dull. 11 1E2c. on Corn. 12 1E2c. on Wheat to New-York, Imports--10,000 bbls. Four, 50,000 bushels Wheat, 30,000 bushels Corn. Canal Exports, 300 bbls. Flour, 101,000 bushels Wheat.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Monday, June 3. FLOUR quiet and steady. WHEAT flat and no sales. CORN dull, with a declining tendency. sales 17,000 bushels Prime Yellow, at 34c. CANAL FREIGHTS steady -- 12c. TO 13c. on Corn and Wheat, to New-York. Imports -- 14,000 bbls. Flour, 140,000 bushels Wheat, 21,000 bushels Corn. Canal Exports -- 2,000 bbls. Flour, 48,000 bushels Wheat, 29,000 bushels Corn, and 21,000 bushels Oats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, June 3.  Gen. Beauregard to-day arrived at Manassas Junction to take command of the Confederate army.  NEW YORK, June 3.  A Border State Convention is reportedly being held at Frankfort, Kentucky.  BOSTON, June 3 -- Arr. steamship Delta, Halifax. brigs St. Peter, Pictou. Charles Helath, Savannah. The schr. Sarah Goodsell, of New Haven, Goodsell, hence for Nassau, N.P., was sunk May 20, about 40 miles N.E. from Eluthera. She had experienced a very heavy gale on the 11th ult., while crossing the Gulf, causing her to leak badly, which increased to such an extent that it was impossible to keep her free. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, June 2, 1861.  News received to-day of a Union victory at Phillippa, Western Virginia.  Capt. W.H. CHESTER, of the Sickles Brigade, informs us that each telegraph station has a small instrument, ball and key, and the central station to supplied with a ten-numbered annunciator, such as is seen in hotels. The signals will be by representing conceited questions and replies, too simple to be misunderstood. Whenever there is a separation of one compound, the advancing column may be accompanied by a telegraph line, and constant communication keying, even when on the march.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, June 1, 1861.  Capt. W.H. CHESTER, of the Sickles Brigade, informs us that the telegraphic corps connected with that command is well organized, and will be put into practical operation soon, at Camp Scott. He commands a company composed exclusively of telegraph operators, line-repairers, battery-keepers, and mechanics, in different branches. The instruments consist of ten lines of insulated wire, weighing not over 40 pounds to the mile, diverging from the General's tent, and connecting at ten picket stations one and two miles distant.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 31 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, May 31.  Reports received to-day of a cavalry skirmish at Fairfax Court-House.  PHILADELPHIA, Friday, May 31. Spring wheat FLOUR  SX 5 25 TO 5 37 1E2. WHEAT active. Red  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 38, White  SX 1 40 TO  SX 1 55. CORN dull. sales 2,000 bushels, at 56c. LARD 10c. WHISKY dull, and unchanged. CINCINNATI, Friday, May 31. FLOUR firmer -- fair demand at  SX 4 45 for superfine. WHISKY dull at 12c. More inquiry for PROVISIONS, but not much doing. Exchange steady at 3E8 TO  1E2. Gold dull at 1E2. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 30 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ALBANY, Thursday, May 30. FLOUR moderately active, demand for more extra grades. Corn meal  SX 1 TO  SX 1 12 100 lbs. WHEAT dull. RYE 65c.. sales 2,000 bushels. CORN better, 46c. for Western Mixed, afloat. sales 20,000 bushels. Shipments of Corn by tows to-night large. OATS 31c. for Canada East. 32c. for Chicago, and 33c. for State. sales, 2,000 bushels. BARLEY -- 56c. for State four rowed Winter and Spring. 68c. for Canada West. sales 6,000 bushels. Received by Central Railroad for Boston and the East, 1,529 bbls. Flour, 124 bbls. Beef, 180 bbls. Pork, and 72 bbls. Provisions. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 29 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Wednesday May 29.  U.S. steam transport Alabama Schenck, Hampton Roads 28 hours, with prize bark Winifred in two. 29th Inst., at 10:15 A.M., off Bamegat passed U.S. steam transport Coatzacualcos with troops bound south.   U.S. transport Empire City, Brown, Fortress Monroe 28th inst., at 4 A.M., where she landed the Seventh Regiment, N.Y.S.V. U.S. steam transport Jersey Blue, Chadsey, Washington, D.C. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 28 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 28.  To-day, Generals Banks and Fremont were both appointed to the rank of Major-General.  PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, May 28. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT firm. sales 3,000 bushels Red,  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 40. White,  SX 1 45 TO  SX 1 60. CORN firm. sales 80,000 bushels, at 58c. TO 60c. WHISKY dull, at 16 1E2c. TO 17c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 27 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 27.  General Butler is now occupying Newport's News.  NEW YORK, Monday May 27.  Ship Liverpool Kearney, London and Isle of Wight April 26, with mdse. and 170 passengers to Grinnell, Minturn  ES  Co. In lat 46, lon. 47 59, passed large quantities of field and several large icebergs. Ship Marian, (Ham.,) Grongmann, Havana 14 ds., with sugar to Funch, Meincke,  ES  Wendt. Ship J.R. Ryerson. Strong, Liverpool 32 ds., with coal to J  ES  N. Smith  ES  Co. Brig Mary (of Baltimore, Wilson, Rio Janeiro April 7, with coffee to master, 81d in co. with barks Justina, and Wheatland, of Baltimore. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 26 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 26.  QUEENSTOWN, Thursday, May 16. From the London Daily News City Article this morning. No surprise will be felt should a rise in the Bank rate of Discount take place to-day. The applications at the Bank yesterday were not, however, on as active a scale as is usually the case when there is an advance in the rate on the following day. In the open market, not much business was done below 5 1E4 cent., and many of the dealers were content to turn away business to the Bank. From the London Times of this morning, the exportation of gold to America on Saturday and yesterday amounted to a total of  SX 548,000. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 25 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, May 25. FLOUR firm, at  SX 5 50 TO  SX 5 62 1E2 for Superfine, WHEAT steady, at  SX 1 95 for White, and  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 39, for Red. CORN steady. sales of Yellow at 60c. LARD steady, at 10. WHISKY dull, at 16c. TO 17c. CHICAGO, Saturday, May 25. The currency question is in statu quo. business of all kinds very quiet. FLOUR -- No, transactions. WHEAT declined 6c. TO 8c.. sales at 75c. TO 76c. for No. I for gold. CORN dull, and 5c. lower. sales at 23c. Receipts -- 20,000 bbls. Flour, 44,000 bushels Wheat, 99,000 bushels Corn, Shipments -- 1,100 bbls. Flour, 52,000 bushels Wheat, 32,000 bushels Corn.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 24 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 24.  The Union army has now reportedly advanced into Virginia.  Col. E.E. Ellsworth was killed in Alexandria to-day, the first casualty of the war.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 23 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LONDON, Thursday, May 16. It is positively asserted that Mr. GLADSTONE will announce in the House of Commons to-night, that the mail contract with the Galway steamship line has terminated. It is staied authoritatively that negotiations for the withdrawal of the French forces from Rome are approaching a conclusion. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 22 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Wednesday, May 22.  Movement of the seat of the rebel government has reportedly been completed to Richmond.  Steamship Marion, Coles, Washington City, with freight and passengers to Spofford, Tileston  ES  Co. 21st inst., at 8 1E2 A.M., passed U.S. gunboat Pocahontas and transport Coatzeonalcos, both bound up. 22d. 8 A.M., passed ship Calliope, of Bath, 18 miles S. of Fire Island Lightship, standing N. Steamer Mars, Nichols, Philadelphia, with mdse. to J.  ES  N. Briggs.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 21 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 21.  Telegrams are reportedly being seized in Washington by the Federal Government.  TRENTON, N.J., Tuesday, May 21. U.S. Marshal DEACON and Deputies, by order of the United States Government, took possession, at 3 o'clock this afternoon, of all the telegraphic dispatches in the offices at Newark, Princeton and Trenton, in this State. They number back several years. All have been placed in possession of U.S. District-Attorney KENLEY, at Newark.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINNATI, Saturday, May 18. FLOUR unchanged, at  SX 4 50 for superfine. WHISKY 12 1E2c. PROVISIONS dull. LARD 8 3E4c. Kentucky currency 4 TO 5 cent. discount. Eastern exchange 1 cent. premium. NEW-ORLEANS, Saturday, May 18. COTTON -- Sales to-day, 800 bales at 11 1E4c. TO 11 1E2c. for Middling. FLOUR advancing. Superfine  SX 7, MESS PORK  SX 20, WHISKY 22c, CORN 60 TO 70c. MINIATURE ALMANAC -- THIS DAY. Sun rises.... 4 39 Sun sets..... 7 14 Moon sets... 1 53 HIGH WATER -- THIS DAY. Sandy Hook. 3 36 Gov. Island.. 4 25 Hell Gate... 5 47.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 19 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>OSWEGO, Saturday, May 18. FLOUR dull and unchanged. WHEAT held above the views of buyers, and no sales. CORN dull and drooping. CANAL FREIGHTS steady. Flour, 32c.. Wheat, 9c.. Corn, 8c. to New-York. Lake Imports -- 490 bbls. Flour, 14,000 bushels Wheat, 8,800 bushels Corn, 3,300 bushels Oats, 2,800 bushels Peas. Canal Exports -- 1,300 bbls. Flour, 54,300 bushels Wheat, 16,000 bushels Corn. CHICAGO, Saturday, May 18. FLOUR firm. WHEAT firm, at  SX 1 30 for No. 1, payable in common currency, and 89c. TO 90c. in preferred. CORN quiet, and firm at 45c. in common currency. OATS firm. Receipts: 4,000 bbls. Flour, 45,000 bush. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 18 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Friday, May 17. FLOUR quiet and unchanged. WHEAT dull and heavy. Sales 6,000 bushels No. 2 Chicago Spring, at 91c. TO 92 c.. 3,000 bushels Milwaukee Club, at 98c. CORN heavy and lower. Sales 9,000 bushels, at 37c. TO 37 1E2c. CANAL FREIGHTS firm. 13c. on Corn, 14c. on Wheat to New-York. Imports -- 5,000 bbls. Flour, 112,000 bushels Wheat, 65,000 bushels Corn, 3,000 bushels Oats. Exports -- 300 bbls. Flour, 122,000 bush-Wheat, 74,000 bushels Corn. PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, May 18. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT steady: Red,  SX 1 35 TO  SX 1 38. White,  SX 1 40 TO  SX 1 50. CORN quiet: sales of 4,000 bushels, at 63c. WHISKY dull.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 17 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 17.  Reports of a Union triumph received to-day from Kentucky.  RICHMOND, May 17.  Confederate States Congress to-day authorized the issue of fifty million dollars in bonds, to be payable in twenty years.  LONDON, Saturday afternoon. Consols close at 91 3E4 TO 91 7E8 for both money and account. American Securities are flat. the Persia's advices were received too late to have any effect on the market. The latest quotations are -- Illinois Central shares 40 TO 39 discount. Erie 19 TO 20. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Thursday April 16.  From LIVERPOOL, Saturday -- 3 P.M. There is great excitement here to-day, caused by the advices from America, received by the steamship Persia, and all markets are unsettled and excited. COTTON -- The sales of Cotton to-day reach 20,000 bales, including 10,000 to speculators and exporters, and there is a partial advance of 1E8d. Many operators have withdrawn their stocks from the market. BREADSTUFFS are steady. The Provision Market is steady. PRODUCE MAREET -- Splits Turpentine are firm, and all qualifies have advanced. 40s. is pail to arrive, and 42s. 6d. TO 456. asked on spot, but not paid. Resia, buoyant, and advanced.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 15 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 15.  In London a word was invented, on Friday, on 'Change, for this event, which has had great success also at Paris. It was called a very civil war. A week ago the Government at Washington was ridiculed in Europe for its seeming weakness and inactivity, and the subject of conquest and annexation in the Western Hemisphere was talked about, as if the United States had suddenly been wiped out of existence. Spain was to annex St. Domingo, while France was to annex a part or all of Hayti and the Republic of Ecuador. They asked, indeed, What will England say? but never once what will the United States say?</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 14 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BUFFALO, Tuesday, May 14. FLOUR dull and heavy. sales, 400 bbls., at  SX 4 75 for Extra State.  SX 5 TO  SX 5 25 for Extra Indiana and Ohio. WHEAT and CORN are extremely dull, and nominally lower. WHISKY dull. held at 15c. CANAL FREIGHTS, 11c. TO 11 1E2c. on Corn, 12c. TO 12 1E2c. on Wheat, to New-York. Lake Imports -- For 48-hours, 24,000 bbls. Flour, 289,000 bushels Wheat, 223,000 bushels Corn. Canal Exports -- 133,000 bushels Wheat and 328,000 bushels Corn. PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, May 14. FLOUR quiet. WHEAT wanted. White, at  SX 1 40  TO  SX 1 60. Red,  SX 1 33 TO  SX 1 35. CORN declined 2c., at 62c. TO 63c. WHISKY nominal, at 17c. TO 17 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 13 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, May 13.  Reports received that interrupted communications have resumed with Washington by way of Baltimore.  Baltimore is now occupied by Federal troops.   An Anti-Secession Convention occurred to-day in Western Virgina.  NEW ORLEANS, May 13 -- Arr. Charles Farwell and Ariel, from Havre. American Union, from Liverpool. Robert Harding, Calcutta. bark Bollar, Havana. The report of the bark Old Dominion having been seat back to the City by the U.S. Revenue cutter Corvia, for not having a clearance, was an error. she sailed on Saturday. Alameda -- ship. of Boston, bound S., was seen, April 15, lat. 35, lon. 18 40. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 12 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, May 12. FLOUR unchanged. WHEAT steady. Red  SX 1 33 TO  SX 1 35. White  SX 1 40 TO  SX 1 50. CORN inactive, at 65c. WHISKY 17c. TO 17 1E2c. NOTICE -- MISSOURI BONDS STOLE! --  SX 1,000 6 per cent Bond, State of Missouri, No 2068. Stolen from S. DRAPER, No. 36 Pine-st. All persons are warned from negotiating the same, as payment has been stopped. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 11 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, May 11.  In order to facilitate communication with the institutions, a contract has been entered into with Marshal LEPPERTS, for  SX 1.180, for a telegraph from No. 1 Bond-street to Bellevue Hospital, thence to Sixty-first-street, crossing Harlem River be a submarine cable, and terminate at such point on Blackwell's Island as the Commissioners shall require. Instruments are to be furnished at No. I Bond-street and Bellevue Hospital, and operators instructed. A break in the Croton water-pipe over the river had been repaired at a cost of  SX 139. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 10 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Friday, May 10. COTTON -- Sales today 3000 bales, at 11c. for Middling. Sales of week, 8,350. Receipts, 8,000 bales, against 89,000 bales same time last year. decreased receipts, 343,250 bales. decreased at all ports, 893,000 bales. exports, 57,000 bales. total, 1,644,000 bales. stock, 57,000. COFFEE -- Woek's sales, 1,400 bags, at 12 1E2c. TO 13 1E2c.. stock, 5,600 bags, against 22,500 same time last year. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, May 9. -- Arr. steamer Cambridge, Philadelphia. barks Vernon, Messina. Avela, Palermo. brig Zuleika, Bathurst.  NEW-ORLEANS, Tuesday, April 9. COTTON -- Sales of 1,600 bales at 12 1E2c. TO 13c. for Middling. Sales for three days, 5,000 bales. receipts do., 6,500 bales, against 14,250 bales, being a decrease of 322,500. decrease at all Southern ports, 779,000 bales. Sterling Exchange, 6 1E2 TO 7. Exchange on New-York, 1E8 TO 1E2 premium. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 3E8d. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 08 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, May 8 -- Arr. steamers Ben De Ford, from Baltimore. Cambridge, from Philadelphia. The ship Middlesex, reported abandoned at sea, had a cargo of 1,400 tons of coal and about 160 crates of crockery. She was built at Essex, Conn., in 1851. was 1,424 tons, rated A1 1E2, and owned by Tapscott  ES  Co.. valued at  SX 55,000, and insured in New-York for  SX 10,000. Capt. Ulmen, of bark Ida Kimball, which arrived at Rockland March 28, reports that, March 20, when two days out from Bermuda, passed Br. schr. Spray, with both masts and bowsprit gone, and abandoned. Had hoop poles on deck. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 07 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, May 7 -- The steamship Baltimore, for Havana, came in collision on Saturday night, in Chesapeake Bay, with schr. J.H. Host, from New York. The schooner sunk, and the steamship returned to this port leaky. (By telegraph to Ellwood Walter, Esq., Secretary Board of Underwriters.)   CINCINATTI, May 7.  TOBACCO -- The demand has been very moderate, mainly from the home trade. Sales have been reported of 26 hhds. Kentucky at 4 1E2 TO 11c., 27 hhds. Virginia at 5 1E2c.. 72 cases Seed Leaf at 4 1E2c. TO 7c.. 12 cases Florida with 93 bales Havana, and 140 bales Sagua on private terms. WHISKY -- Sales 400 bbls, mainly at 18 1E4c. gallon. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, May 6. FLOUR dull. Howard-street, Ohio, and City Mills are held at  SX 5 50. no sales. WHEAT declined 5c.. Red.  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 37. White,  SX 1 45 TO  SX 1 65. CORN steady. Yellow, 58c. TO 61c. PROVISIONS quiet and unchanged. COFFEE firm, at 12 3E4c. TO 13 3E4c. WHISKY firmer, at 17 3E4c. TO 18c. CINCINNATI, May 6. FLOUR quiet and quotations are nominal. WHISKY dull at 13 3E4c. PORK -- Mess,  SX 17. Bacon in moderate demand, at 7c. for Shoulders. 19 1E2c. TO 10 1E2c. for Sides. LARD is steady at 9 1E2c. TO 10c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 05 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, May 5. Ship Cultivation, Russell, Liverpool, with mdse. and passengers to Williams  ES  Gulon. Bark Reinder, Bartlett, Punta Arenas 117 ds., and Hampton Roads 7 ds., to Wm. A. Sale  ES  Co. April 5, 140 miles S. of the Houx, was boarded by boat C. Berg. No. 16. Bark Vestalinden, (Nor.,) Olsen, Newcastle 65 ds., with coal to Roosevelt  ES  Sons. Brig Gotfredo, (Ital.,) Auremma Palermo 80 ds., with mdse. to order. Has experienced terrible weather, almost continual gales from W.. has stove bulwarks and stauncheons lost sails, spars and four bolts. was obliged to throw overboard part of cargo. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CINCINATTI, May 4.  GRAIN -- The market opened heavily for Wheat, influenced by the increased receipts. but, with a reaction in freights favorable to shippers, and in view of the encouraging tenor of the private advices from England, the export demand improved, and toward the close prices of really desirable lots were quoted steady, the principal holders refusing to make any important concessions to buyers The reported sales reached 71,500 bushels, including white Canada, part at  SX 1 50. Canada Club at about  SX 1 30. White Western at  SX 1 42 TO  SX 1 60, chiefly at  SX 1 45 TO  SX 1 50 red Western in store and afloat at  SX 1 36 TO  SX 1 38. Amber Wisconsin at  SX 1 35.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 03 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 3, 1861.  President Lincoln to-day issued a proclamation calling for more troops to serve for three years.  Both the Regular army and the navy are to be increased.  BOSTON, May 3 -- Arr. steamer Kensington, Philadelphia. ships Gen. Nowell, Liverpool. Wm. Lord, Jr., do.. barks Edwin, Arica, and S.B. Hale, Cardenas. brigs Gen. Marshal and Gipsey, do.. Wingold, Cienfuegos. Lanzarotte, Pernambuco. Shibboleth, Port-au-Prince. Prince Oscar Frederic, Gottenburg. schrs. N. Nickerson, Cape Haytien. Messenger, Mobile. BOSTON, May 3 -- Arr. ship Arizona, fm. Liverpool. barks Rechabite, Ardrossan. Fleurion de Helleview, Rochelle.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 02 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Thursday, May 2.  The Sixty-ninth (Col. CORCORAN's) is guarding the whole road from Annapolis to Washington. They were ordered to march for Washington to-day, but the order was countermanded. The Regiment was behaving excellently well. Father MALONE has great influence over the men, and was after any delinquents with a sharp stick. No troop-ship arrived at Washington, to-day, but the steamer Boston came in with stores. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 01 May 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, May 1.  The Seventh paraded this afternoon in full dress, making a grand appearance. It is quartered in the Representative Hall. The Seventy-first is quartered in the building erected for the Inauguration Ball. The Rhode Island men are in the Patent Office. The Fifth Massachusetts are in the Treasury Department. A serious accident occurred to Lieut. MOSES G. HERRICK, of Beverly, Mass., attached to Company E, Eighth Regiment. His command stacked arms in the old Rep. Hall, one stack fell, and one of the muskets was discharged. The ball struck Lieut. H. in the ancle, completely shattering the joint, and rendering amputation necessary. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday, April 30. Senator HUNTER, W.C. RIVES, W.D. PRESTON, Judge CAMDEN and BROCKENBROUGH have been appointed by the Virginia Convention as delegates to the Southern Congress. The report of the release of Gen. HARNEY by the Gov. of Virginia, is verified. This, however, is a matter of indifference in Administration circles. He has arrived in Washington. The Virginia Convention has passed an ordinance establishing the Navy of Virginia and authorizing the banks to issue one and two dollar notes. The Navy Department is to put sea-going vessels on their guard. The light-houses at Cape Henry and Charles show no lights. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Tuesday, April 30. Notwithstanding the large number of troops new in Washington, and although many of them are permitted to have full range of the streets during the day, nothing whatever approaching to even a slight disturbance of the peace, has occurred in any locality. They all seem to be united in a common object: namely, the protection of the Government and the Capital, irrespective of the political views by which, at their homes, they may be divided. Ladies of the city have tendered their services as hospital nurses should such services be necessary, while some of them are preparing lint, in the possible contingency that it may be needed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Friday, April 28. FLOUR advanced. superfine at  SX 5 25 TO  SX 5 50 WHEAT advancing. red,  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 35. white,  SX 1 10  TO  SX 1 50. CORN advanced. sales 4,000 bush. 62 1E2c. WHISKY steady at 18c. TO 18 1E2.   WASHINGTON, Sunday Night, April 28, 1861. The telegraph wire continues in operation between here and New-York, but the system of espionage and censorship established by the Secessionists at Baltimore, and emulated by the War Department here, render it practically of little value to the Press. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 27.  Reportedly, twenty-one thousand National troops are now in the City.  With the large number now here, and those constantly arriving, our citizens feel perfectly secure from outside or disunion attack, and therefore they are comparatively free from disquieting excitement. As might be expected, we hear of but little, if any, private or public expression of secession sentiments. those among us of such views now practising the philosophy of silence. Contrary to many assertions which have found their way into the newspapers, none are restricted or interfered with in legitimate pursuits, and the civil administration, as heretofore, is unimpaired. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, April 26, from LIVERPOOL, April 19 -- A.M. All the markets open quiet, but steady. LONDON, April 19. The Budget was opened in the House of Commons last night and debated. The opposition denounced it generally, but proposed no amendment. The Paris Bourse closed buoyant last evening at 68f., 50c. Consols this morning are at 91 7E8 TO 92. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, April 25.  To-day, Virginia seceded, joining the Confederate States.  NEW YORK, from LONDON, April 25.  GUARANTERS UPON THE SLAVE-TRADE REQUIRED In the House of Commons, on the 11th inst., Mr. W. FORSTER gave notice that when Mr. GREGORY's motion in favor of the recognition of the new American Confederation come up he should move the following:  QN That this House does not desire to express any opinion upon the subject, and the Government will not recognize such Confederation without taking security for the suppression of the Slave-trade. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Wednesday, April 24.  Ship Chicago, Chase, Liverpool, via Mobile 14 ds., in ballast to Nesmith  ES  Sons. Bark John Avilles, (of Bangor,) Lee, St. John, P.R., April 9, with molasses to L.W.  ES  P. Armstrong, of New- Haven, April 21, in the Gulf Stream, passed brig War Eagle, before reported, and took from her 100 bags coffee, a hoop skirt etc. Bark Golden Rule, Whiteberry, Aspinwall 15 ds., with coffeee etc., to J.F. Joy. Bark R.A. Allen, Patten, Cardenas 8 ds., with sugar etc. to Benner  ES  Deake. Brig Maria, Morgan, Para March 31, with rubber, etc., to R.L. Corning. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, April 23. -- Arr. ships Gen. Williams, from Antwerp, Birmingham, from Boston. As the schr. S.F. Solliday, of Philadelphia, was coming through Hell Gate yesterday afternoon, she struck on the Gridiron. She will probably get off at high water. Has received no damage. At Humacoa, April 6, brig E.A. Reed, Crane, for New-London in 6 ds. At St. John, P.R., April 9, schrs. Anna Hinks, from Boston just arr. C.R. Vickery, do.. Rescue wtg orders. Peerless, for Arecibo, wind bound. brigs Robert Kirkland, do.. Francis Jane, for Baltimore.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, Monday, April 22. FLOUR dull at  SX 5 31 TO  SX 5 50 for superfine. WHEAT steady. red,  SX 1 31. white,  SX 1 40 TO  SX 1 50. CORN firm. sales 5,000 bushels at 62c. WHISKY firm at 18c. TO 18 1E2c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>PHILADELPHIA, April 20.  Philadelphia is full of regiments, but they have been furnished neither clothes nor arms. Red tape rules. The wines between Philadelphia and Baltimore are down, as well as the bridges, and all communication is cut off. Maryland has learnt the first letter in the alphabet of secession, and by the assistance of JEFF DAVIS and the devil, will soon be able to spell out  QN Destruction. QN  C.H.W.   The Union men in Delaware are in a bad fix. Though the population is largely for the Union, all State arms are in the possession of the Secessionists, transferred by the Governor, who has not responded to the requisition of the President, and will not. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, April 20.  There has been an immense Union demonstration in the city to-day.  The Gosport Navy-yard was attacked.  Three ships, three frigates, two sloops, and a brig bearing over 400 guns were burned.  PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, April 20. The Government has taken possession of the Baltimore Road. No trains are leaving here for Wilmington PHILADELPHIA, Saturday, April 20. The excitement and enthusiasm here is intense. A telegram has been received stating that Secretary CAMERON threatens to bombard Baltimore, unless the bridges in Maryland are restored. It is rumored that Washington is to be attacked tomorrow. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, April 19.  The Massachusetts 6th Regiment, while passing through Baltimore enroute to Washington, were attached by a mob.  Several members of the Regiment were killed.  NEW YORK, April 19.  The Seventh New York Regiment departed to-day for Washington.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, April 18.  The Sixth Massachusetts Regiment arrived to-day, enroute to Washington.  Concern is growing for the safety of the capitol.  WASHINGTON, April 17.  Col. CHARLES LEE JONES to-day resigned his commission as Adjutant-General of the District of Columbia Militia. There is no ground for the report that JEFFERSON DAVIS is in Richmond. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 17.  Report received that Virginia Governor Letcher issued a proclamation today that is hostile toward the national government.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, April 17. GOV. SPRAGUE has been telegraphed to come hither with Rhode Island's quota of troops without delay. Additional volunteer companies were mustered in to-day by the War Department, and others are forming to offer their services to Government. There is no intelligence here to warrant the belief that Harper's Ferry has been seized, as was currently reported to-day, together with other mere reports of an exciting character. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, April 16.  The Confederate Government today called for 32,000 more troops.  Fort Pickens has been reinforced by Col. Brown's command.  BALTIMORE, Tuesday, April 16. FLOUR dull and heavy. Howard-street, Ohio and City Mills,  SX 5.37 1E2. WHEAT dull. Red,  SX 1.30 TO  SX 1. 35. White,  SX 1.40 TO  SX 1.65. CORN Steady. Mixed at 57c.  TO 58c.. Yellow, 60c. TO 61c.. White, 63c. TO 65c. PORK buoyant, and advanced 50c.. sales at  SX 18 for Mess. and  SX 13 for Rump. COFFEE firm at 13c. TO 14c. WHISKY dull at 17 1E2c. PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, April 16. FLOUR dull,  SX 5 31 1E4 TO  SX 5 50. WHEAT firm. sales 5,000 bushels -- red  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 32, white  SX 1 38 TO  SX 1 50. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 15.  President Lincoln has to-day issued his proclamation for 75,000 volunteers.  There is tremendous excitement across the north in regard to the situation.  CINCINNATI, Monday, April 15. Business is almost suspended. FLOUR unchanged. WHISKY unsettled. PROVISIONS nominally unchanged. Market for uncurrent money greatly unsettled. Sight Exchange on New-York, 1 cent.. gold, 5 cent. premium. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>SAG-HARBOR, April 14 -- Arrived 15th, ship Jefferson, Huntting, 160 sperm., 700 whale, 5,000 lbs. bone, 1,950 bbls. whale, 280 sperm, 17,000 lbs. bone, all told. At Maracaibo, March 22, bark Ilva, Durie, for New-York, in 5 ds. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON, April 13.  Federal troops stationed in Fort Sumter have surrendered to Confederate States authorities.  NORFOLK, April 13. -- Arr. schr. Sea Drift. 18 ds. fm. Porto Rico, with molasses. Lost deck-load, both masts, sails and rigpicg during a gale. Arr. in Hampton Roans, ship Paragon, from Havre. SAVANNAH, April 13. -- Arr. brig Blackfish, and schr. Red Eagle, for New-York. NEW ORLEANS, April 13 -- Arr ships Robert Cushman, Cumberland. Houghton and Oberon, from Liverpool. Fleetwood and Zenobia, from Havre. Harriet -- brig, of and for Boston, 10 ds out, April 10, 25 miles S.E. of Highlands. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>CHARLESTON, April 12.  On this day, Charleston batteries commenced firing on Fort Sumter.  BOSTON, April 12 -- Capt. Parrish, of the steamship Yorktown, which arrived last evening, (11th,) from Richmond, Va., reports at 2 1E2 P.M., of the 11th passed steamer Uncle Ben, 10 miles south of Barnegat, bound South. The steamship Roanoke, of the New-York and Virginia Steamship Company's Line, has been laid up for the present. The Bremen barks Washington, bark Pyrmont, Levanter, (Br.,) brig Ianthe, schr. Electric Light, are at anchor in Quarantine, outward bound. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 11.  C.S. General Beauregard has reportedly demanded the unconditional surrender of Fort Sumter.  NORFOLK, April 11. -- Schr. Sea Drift, of Mobile, has just been towed in, totally dismasted. (By telegraph.)   BOSTON, April 11 -- Arr. ship President Smidt, Antwerp. bark Young Turk, Messina.   NEW-YORK....THURSDAY, April 11. Steamships Northern Light, Tinklepaugh, Aspinwall, D.R. Allen. Cahawba, Smith Havan., Livingston, Crocheren  ES  Co., Montgomery, Morley, Savannah, H. B. Cromwell  ES  Co. Steamers Sarah, Jones, Philadelphia, Loper  ES  Kirkpatrick.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, April 10 -- Arr. ship Zenobia, Havre. April 11 -- Arr. ship Cavalier, Liverpool. Steamships Northern Light, for Aspinwall. Cahawba, for Havana and New-Orleans. Ships Anna Kimball, for Melbourne. Magnet, and Phantom, San Francisco. Also, steamship Montgomery, for Savannah. All the vessels that have been detained in the River, and in the S.W. Spit, by adverse winds, went to sea to day. At Remedios, March 29, bark Zidon, Foster, for Boston in 15 ds.. Brigs Orison, Aduros, for New-York or Portland in a few ds.. Hidalgo, Whittemore, for New-York in 15 ds. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, April 9.  President Jeff. Davis has made a requistion for troops to-day.  BOSTON, April 9. -- Arr. steamer Cambridge, Philadelphia. barks Vernon, Messina. Avela, Palermo. brig Zuleika, Bathurst.  NEW-ORLEANS, Tuesday, April 9. COTTON -- Sales of 1,600 bales at 12 1E2c. TO 13c. for Middling. Sales for three days, 5,000 bales. receipts do., 6,500 bales, against 14,250 bales, being a decrease of 322,500. decrease at all Southern ports, 779,000 bales. Sterling Exchange, 6 1E2 TO 7. Exchange on New-York, 1E8 TO 1E2 premium. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool, 3E8d. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BALTIMORE, April 8 -- The steamship Baltimore, for Havana, came in collision on Saturday night, in Chesapeake Bay, with schr. J.H. Host, from New York. The schooner sunk, and the steamship returned to this port leaky. (By telegraph to Ellwood Walter, Esq., Secretary Board of Underwriters.)   NEW YORK, Monday April 8.  Brig Sultan, Sutton, Wilmington. N.C., 9 ds., with naval stores to C.B. Dibble  ES  Co. Has had some very heavy weather. split sails,  ES . Brig Martha Jane, (Br.,) Corbett, Horton, N.S., 7 ds., with potatoes to P.I. Nevins  ES  Son. Brig Giovanni Stefano, (Aus.,) Capponi, Liverpool 56 ds., with coal to order. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sunday, April 7. The telegraph wires south of Petersburgh, Virginia, are reported to be down -- therefore, we are unable to receive any further advices, other than those in this morning's paper, from the South. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW-ORLEANS, Saturday, April 6. COTTON -- Sales to-day 12,000 bales at 12 1E2c. TO 13c. for Middling. CORN buoyant at 35c.56c. FREIGHTS -- Cotton to Liverpool 3E8d. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>BOSTON, April 5 -- Arr. ship North American, Liverpool. Barks Ann Augusta, Glasgow. Catharina, Paramaibo.  BALTIMORE, Friday, April 5. FLOUR firm. City Mills  SX 5 37 1E2. Howard-street,  SX 5 50. Ohio,  SX 6. WHEAT steady. Red,  SX 1 30 TO  SX 1 39. White,  SX 1 50 TO  SX 1 58. CORN -- Yellow, 60c. TO 61c.. White, 60c. TO 63c. PORK firm. Mess,  SX 17. Prime,  SX 14. LARD, 10C. COFFEE firm, at 12 3E4c. TO 16 1E4c. WHISKY dull at 17 1E2c. TO 18c. CINCINNATI, Friday, April 5. FLOUR very dull. Superfine,  SX 4 35 TO  SX 4 40. WHISKY firm at 13 1E2c. MESS PORK in good demand. sales of 2,000 bbls. at  SX 16 75 TO  SX 16 87 1E2. BACON held at 9 1E2 TO 10 1E2c. LARD, 9c. lb. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Thursday April 4.  SHORTEST CHINA PASSAGE OF THE SEASON. -- The celebrated clipper ship Snow Squall. Capt. Lloyd, anchored at the Bar on Wednesday evening, having again out-distanced all her competitors in the China fleet. She left Amoy Jan. 7, and passed Java Head Jan. 23, counting 85 days from Amoy, and 70 from Java Head. Telegraph -- bark, bound E., was signalized, March 27, lat. 43 10 lon. 52 40. Zephyr -- bark, bound E., was signalized, March 25, lat. 45 59, lon. 42 05. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 3.  Reports are received that great preparations are commencing in most northern navy yards.  BOSTON, April 3. -- Arr. bark St. Mary's, from Buenos Ayres. NEW ORLEANS April 3 -- Arr. ships Mamaroneck, from Liverpool. Niagara, from Boston. barks Guiding Star, do.. Iola, and Wylie, Bordeaux. 


</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, Tuesday April 2.  LAUNCH. -- The steamer Westchester will be launched from the yard of Messrs. Van Dusen Brothers, foot of Sixteenth-street, East River, this afternoon, at 2 o'clock. She is 112 feet keel, 125 feet on deck, 21 feet beam, 49 feet over the guards, 8 feet 3 inches depth of hold, being 233 tons. She is built for the light draft of 2 feet 9 inches, though very strong, with arches in the hold, securely fastened, to answer the purpose of a hog frame. The cabin accommodations will be very superior in every respect and will be heated by steam. The engine is by the Neptune Iron Works, at Eighth-street, East River, 30-inch cylinder, with 6 feet stroke.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, April 1.  ST. THOMAS, via HALIFAX, March 30 -- The clipper ship Contest, from New-York to San Francisco, arrived yesterday, leaking 18 inches per hour. 200 tons cargo thrown overboard. she is discharging.  By telegraph to Ellwood Walter, Esq., Sec. Board of Underwriters. ST. THOMAS, Feb 30 -- The brigantine Wm. A. Dresser, of Bangor, from New-Haven, bound to Ponce, with cargo of shooks and hoops, arrived this morning, with loss of foretopmast and topgaliantmasts and sails, in a gale on the 4th. vessel not injured in the hull. </description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
