<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 31.  An expedition to Mount Elba and Longview, Arkansas, returned to Pine Bluff, having destroyed a large amount of rebel property.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, March 30. CONCERNING CENSUS STATISTICS. Mr. WILEY, of West Virginia, (Union,) from the Committee on Finance, reported adversely on the resolution directing the Superintendent of the Census to prepare certain tables showing the population, products and manufactures of certain sections by comparison and in detail.  The resolution was ordered to lie on the table. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 30.  An engagement occurred to-day in Arkansas with one thousand two hundred rebels who were routed and pursued ten miles.  SPRINGFIELD, ILL., Wednesday, March 30. Col. OAKES, Assistant Provost Marshal General, started for Charleston last night and telegraphed to-day for the Forty-first Regiment, which left this afternoon. Gen. HEINTZLEMAN has also been requested to send 5,000 troops from Indianapolis. This indicates that the troubles in that section are of a serious character. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 29.  A rebel force crossed the Cumberland River at Eddyville, Kentucky.  NEW YORK, March 29.  The American Telegraph Company have opened an office at the St. James Hotel, in this City.   CAIRO, Tuesday, March 29. FORREST, with a force estimated at 7,000, was reported within eight miles of Columbus, Ky., last night. They cut the telegraph lines between that place and Cairo yesterday. About forty more prisoners, captured at Union City, arrived here last night. They report that only 250 prisoners were captured with Col. HAWKINS, and parties of them were escaping every day.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 28.  The advance forces of General Banks' army have left Alexandria, Louisiana.  A Copperhead riot has transpired to-day in Charleston, Illinois.  A battle on Cane River, Louisiana, thirty five miles above Alexandria, began and ended to-day.  Rebel forces were defeated.  NEW YORK, March 27.  The Metropolitan Police authorities have been very busy, within the last few days, in perfecting their arrangements relative to the approaching fair.  A new line of police telegraph has been strung from Headquarters, at No. 300 Mulberry-street, to Palace Garden, on Fourteenth-street, at which latter point are to be established the headquarters of the policemen.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 27.  From FORT MONROE, Thursday, March 24. The schooner John Gilpin, from New-York, arrived to-day. The Captain reports they experienced very heavy weather. March 22, shipped very heavy sea, washing overboard BENJAMIN REINPART, of Rockaway. The Chesapeake and Roanoke Canal was damaged to a slight extent by the storm. No further damages are reported. The telegraph line is not yet working. FORTRESS MONROE, Friday, March 25. The dispatch steamer Fort Jackson arrived this morning from the blockading fleet off Wilmington, and reports a great number of wrecks all along the coast from Hatteras to Cape Henry.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 26.  By dawn this morning, rebel forces attacking Paducah, Kentucky, were gone and a silence hangs over the defenses.  President Lincoln has issued a proclamation defining the Amnesty Proclamation.  Gen. Franklin's forces have reached Alexandria, Louisiana.    Grant has reportedly returned to Culpepper Court-House, Virginia, where he maintains headquarters for the Army of the Potomac.  General McPherson has taken command of the Army of the Tennessee and is reporting to General Sherman.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 25.  Rebels to-day attacked Paducah, Kentucky.  The city has been partially fired.  Illinois Republican Congressman and abolitionist, The Honorable Owen Lovejoy, died to-day.  CAIRO, Thursday, March 24. A rebel force, estimated at 7,000 men, with artillery, under Gen. FORREST, advanced northward as far as Obion River last night. At 3 o'clock this morning their advance drove in our pickets south of Union City. The latter in the morning cut off communication with Columbus, Ky., by destroying the railroad, cutting the telegraph wires, and burning the bridges. Our forces at Columbus have gone to meet them. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 24.  The Union garrison has surrendered at Union City, East Tennessee, after repulsing the rebels, two thousand strong, three times.  MEMPHIS, Tuesday, March 22. FORREST is reported at Bolivar, Tenn., with 7,000 men, stopping men moving North. GRIEBSON'S cavalry is looking out after the rebels. A party of workingmen, with a guard of twenty men of the First Alabama Cavalry, were surprised and made prisoners by a party of guerrillas in Arkansas, opposite Memphis. The men were engaged in taking up the rails on the Memphis and Little Rock Railroad. There was no fight.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 23.  General Steele's army has left Little Rock, Arkansas.  The order reorganizing the Army of the Potomac has been issued.  The command of the Fifth Corps of the Army of the Potomac has shifted from Major General George Sykes to Major General G. K. Warren, who last July saved the Union left flank at the Battle of Gettysburg.  PROCEEDINGS IN CONGRESS.  Mr. GRIMES, of Iowa. (Union,) offered the resolution of the Legislature of Iowa, in favor of the construction of a military and wagon road from some point on the west side of the Missouri River, near the mouth of the Niobrara River, in Nebraska Territory, to Gallatin in Idaho Territory. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 22.  General Thayer, with an army of 5,500 men, have left Fort Smith, Arkansas, to cooperate with General Steele's army.   FORTRESS MONROE, Sunday, March 20. Five guerrillas were arrested on the Eastern Shore, Virginia, yesterday, and brought here, charged with cutting the telegraph cable near Cherrystone recently. Postmaster-General BLAIR arrived here this morning, and visited the Rip Raps and Navy-yard at Norfolk to-day. No vessels came into the Road to-day for refuge. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 21.  To-day there was an engagement near Teachoes, Louisiana.  The rebels have been defeated at Natchitoches, on the Red River, in Louisiana.  ST. LOUIS, Thursday, March 17. Gen. POPE, from his headquarters at Milwaukee, says indications point to the concentration of the most powerful bands of Sioux Indians early in Spring in Missouri above the mouth of Grand River. A large force of cavalry, under Gen. SULLY, will march against these Indians as soon as there is grass enough on the prairies for the horses to subsist on. Until this expedition moves it will be unsafe for steamers to navigate the Missouri above Fort Pierre. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 20.  A rebel attack on Jenkins' Island and Spanish Wells, Hilton Head, South Carolina, has been frustrated.  From the Richmond Dispatch, March 14. Additional particulars of the fight at Suffolk last Wednesday show that it was a perfect rout of the enemy. Gen. RANSOM advanced on the town about 10 o'clock in the morning and chased in the negro pickets. A regiment of negro cavalry was stationed in the town, which dismounted after the first fire and scattered in all directions. Many were killed in the streets. Several took refuge in a house in the eastern part of the place, and refusing to surrender, the house was fired. One got out during the burning and was killed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 19.  A body of rebels attempted to land near Port Royal Ferry, South Carolina, to-day.  SAN FRANCISCO, Tuesday, March 15. There is rather more activity in business. Isthmus butter and sugars are very firm. Foreign and domestic spirits are unsettled. There have been extensive operations in alcohol, ales, Goods are going to Oregon en route to Boyrs and the neighboring mines as rapidly as transportation facilities will permit. Telegraphic advices from Portland, Oregon, represent all steamers leaving for the Cascades as crowded with passengers and freight. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 18.   General Sherman officially assumed command of the armies of the west to-day.  DEPARTMENT OF VIRGINIA AND NORTH CAROLINA, CAPTAIN OF THE PORT's OFFICE, FORTRESS MONROE, Va., March 1, 1864.  All steamers are prohibited from throwing overboard ashes while anchored in the channel leading to Hampton.  Vessels anchoring so as to obstruct navigation to and from these wharves, will remove at once on notice from this office.  To prevent accident and damage to the submarine telegraph cable, no vessel will be allowed to anchor between the two red buoys on the upper end of Hampton bar.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 17.  A rebel raid has occurred during the night on Magnolia, Florida.  General Grant, presently in Nashville, has formally assumed command of all the armies of the United States and informed everyone that  QN Headquarters will be in the field, and, until further orders, will be with the Army of the Potomac. QN   Some weeks ago Commissioner OULD notified Gen. BUTLER that at a certain date he would declare certain paroled prisoners exchanged, and that he (BUTLER) might do the same, to which Gen. BUTLER acceded, and issued an order as suggested by OULD, which was at once countermanded by our Government.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 16.  Rebel guerillas have attacked a train from Nashville, near Estelle Springs, Tennessee.  In Tennessee, rebels shelled from a camp, near Bennett's Ferry, on the Cumberland River.  The rebel attack on our forces at Skull Creek, near Hilton Head, South Carolina, have been frustrated.   ST. JOHN's, Newfoundland, Monday, March 14. The Newfoundland Telegraph Line ceased to work on the morning of Feb. 26, during a heavy storm, and has not been in working order since, until to-day. The storm continued several days and was accompanied by a terrific fall of sleet, breaking down the lines for miles and miles.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 15.  An official order has been issued, promulgating the President's call for two hundred thousand more troops and ordering a draft for any deficiency, on the 15th of April.  NEW YORK, March 15.  New York Governor Seymour has signed the Police Bill and the Commissioners have been sworn in.  ST. LOUIS, Saturday, March 12. Advices from Natches, on the 2d instant, say that reliable information puts the rebel force in West Louisiana at 5,000 to 6,000 men, under Gens. DICK, TAYLOR and POLIGNIKE, and Col. HARRISON. The rebels are fortifying Fort Deruslee on the Black River, and Fort Trinity on the Ouachita River.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 14.   Fort DeRussey, on the Red River in Louisiana, has been attacked and captured by Union forces under General Smith.  The Philadelphia Telegraph of yesterday says  QN that a letter has been received from a friend of the late brave Col. DAHLGREN, who served with that unfortunate officer during the recent raid about Richmond, which states emphatically that the so-called 'order' alleged to have been found upon the body of DAHILGREN, was a fabrication and forgery.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 13.  A portion of our fleet has arrived before Alexandria, Louisiana, and demanded its surrender, which was complied with.  A Cairo dispatch states that Gen. SHERMAN's army has returned to Vicksburg, and an officer who arrived at Cairo on the 7th, from Vicksburg, confirms the arrival of Gen. SHERMAN's forces at Jackson, with a small army of negroes, and a large number of mules, cattle, hogs, etc., the spoils of the march. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 12.  General Grant has reportedly departed Washington on a train to Nashville where he is expected to meet with General Sherman.  Major General Halleck, at his own request, has been relieved as General-in-Chief and named Chief of Staff to General Grant.  General Grant has been assigned command of all the armies.  General Sherman has been named as General Grant's replacement in the west, with General McPherson moving into General Sherman's vacated billet.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 11.  A fight occurred to-day with guerillas on the Atchafalaya River, Louisiana.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, March 8. The petition of ELI THAYER and others, presented on Monday, was incorrectly stated to be in favor of  QN the passage of a law confiscating the lands of the rebels, and distributing them among freedmen. QN  The petition, in reality, asks Congress  QN to confiscate utterly, and without reserve, the lands of rebels. and to give of the same, one hundred and sixty acres to each private in the naval service, and to each man in the rank and file of the Union army, and of the rebel army who will take the subscribed oath of allegiance to the United States. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 10.  General Grant arrived to-day at the headquarters of the Army of the Potomac.  Palatka, Florida, is now occupied by our troops.  An expedition left Vicksburgh, Mississippi, for Fort De Russey, Louisiana.  The Emancipation Report has been adopted by the Virginia Constitutional Convention in Alexandria.  SAN FRANCISCO, Monday, March 7. Dates have been received from Hong Kong up to Jan. 13. Chinese papers contain nothing concerning the Alabama in addition to the news telegraphed here from New-York. All the American shipping in Chinese waters was unemployed. Sandwich Island dates are to Feb. 13. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 9.  President Lincoln made formal presentation to-day of the Lieutenant-General's commission to General Grant.  A skirmish has taken place near Suffolk, Virginia, in which colored troops were engaged.  An expedition from Yorktown, Virginia, to the vicinity of Kings and Queens Court-house met and dispersed a body of rebels.  BALTIMORE, Tuesday, March 8. Reports are in circulation, and have probably been telegraphed from here, of the invasion of Maryland by rebel raiders. It may be confidently stated that the only foundation for these rumors is the fact that a small rebel force has been seen in London County. Va. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 8.  There has been a special election in New York, resulting in allowing soldiers to vote.  New Hampshire has held an election.  General Grant is now visiting Washington.  He is expected to join the President at the White House this evening for the President's weekly reception.  From Baltimore we learn of a raid in the Chesapeake Bay, on Saturday morning last, by which two vessels were captured -- one a tug, the Iolas, in the employ of the Government as a dispatch boat, and the other a side-wheel steamer, the Titan, loaded with Commissary stores. The affair occurred in Cherrystone Inlet, and the telegraph station and sub-marine cable were also destroyed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 7.  IN CONGRESS.  MILITARY ROAD AND TELEGRAPH IN OREGON. Mr. NESMITH, (Dem.,) of Oregon, introduced a bill to grant lands to aid in the construction of a military road and telegraph line from Portland City to Dalles, in Oregon.  The telegraph, this morning, presents a number of dispatches from Cairo respecting Gen. SHERMAN'S expedition, all of which are stale and very stupid. Rebel reports, already published, of his occupation of Meridian, are later, and certainly more lucid. It begins to be believed that Gen. SHERMAN is on his way back to Vicksburgh, if he has not already reached there.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 6.  The President has received a dispatch from Gen. BUTLER, stating that Gen. KILPATRICK arrived yesterday within our lines with a loss of something less than one hundred and fifty men, having had skirmishes on the way. Among the missing are Cols. DAHLGREN, COOK and LITCHFIELD. DAHLGREN and COOK are supposed to be prisoners. Gen. KILPATRICK destroyed a large portion of the Virginia Central Railroad, and several mills along the James River, and other valuable property. He penetrated to the suburbs or outer fortifications of Richmond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 5.  Secretary of the Treasury Chase, in a letter to Hon. Jas. C. Hull of Ohio, has withdrawn his name as a Presidential candidate.   Rebel naval commander John Taylor Wood, C.S.N., has led a daring raid against the Federals at Cherry Point, Virginia.  With some 15 men in open barges, he crossed the Chesapeake Bay at night and took the Union telegraph station.  Shortly thereafter, two small U.S. Army steamers, the Aeolus and Titan, stopped at the station, unaware that it was in Confederate hands, and were also quickly taken.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 4.  General Custer made a reconnaissance to Ely's Ford on the Rapidan River.  General Sherman's army reached Vicksburgh, returning from their raid through Mississippi.   WASHINGTON, Wednesday, March 2. A special dispatch from Culpepper to-day, says:  QN Gen. CUSTER, with 1,500 picked men, in light marching order, left Culpepper Court-house about 2 o'clock on Sunday afternoon. The Sixth and Third Corps marched from their Winter quarters earlier in the day. the former halted at Madison Court-house, and threw out a strong cordon of pickets, while the latter bivouacked in the neighborhood of James City.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 3.  To-day, General Kilpatrick arrived within the lines of Butler's army.  WASHINGTON, Monday, Feb. 29. THE DESTRUCTION OF THE HOUSATONIC. The Navy Department has received the following from Lieut. T.J. HIGGINSON, lately commanding the steamer Housatonic:  QN About 8:45 P.M. of the 17th inst., the officer of the deck discovered something in the water about 100 yards from the vessel.  It had the appearance of a plank moving on the water, and came directly toward the ship. The time when it was first seen till it was close alongside was about two minutes. The torpedo struck the Housatonic forward of the mizzen mast.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 2.  Generals Kilpatrick's and  Butler's forces have united in the vicinity of Richmond.  Provost Marshal General Fry has ordered the draft to take place on the 10th instant in all sub-districts which had not filled their quotas on the 1st instant.   WASHINGTON, Monday, Feb. 29. HOMESTEADS FOR SOLDIERS AND SAILORS. Mr. JULIAN, of Indiana, (Union,) introduced a bill to secure to persons in the military and naval service homesteads in confiscated and forfeited estates within insurrectionary districts. Referred to the Committee on Public Lands. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, March 1.  Major General Ulysses S. Grant was nominated to-day by President Lincoln for promotion to the rank of Lieutenant General.  Early this morning, General Kilpatrick's expedition reached the outer fortifications of Richmond.  They carried the outer line of works but were repulsed from the next line of works.  Gens. Kilpatrick's and Butler's forces met in the night.  General Sherman and his staff have arrived in New Orleans.  General Custer's cavalry expedition has reportedly returned to Culpeper, Virginia.  An election is in progress to-day in Louisiana.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 29.  At eight o'clock a.m., General Kilpatrick's forces took up their line of march along the road to Spotsylvania Court-House, Virginia, en route for the junction of the Virginia Central Railroad and the Richmond and Fredericksburgh Railroad.  Colonel Dahlgren's command attacked with a great destruction of bridges, railroad track, etc.  General Kilpatrick reached and destroyed a portion of the Richmond and Fredericksburgh Railroad.  His forces have reportedly left Fredericksburg for Richmond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 28.  General Kilpatrick's forces have reportedly made demonstrations in front of the rebel works at Mine Run in Orange County, Virginia.  General Custer started on a reconnaissance toward Gordonsville, in cooperation with General Kilpatrick.  General Sherman has arrived at Vicksburgh, Mississippi, on his return from his great raid through Mississippi.  TUNNEL HILL, Ga., Friday, Feb. 26. Early yesterday morning, Gens. BAIRD and CRUFTS crossed Tunnel Hill Ridge with their commands, and marching through the gap in Rocky Face range, drove the rebels from the Cleveland road into Rocky Face valley.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 27.  General movement continues of General Kilpatrick's forces on the expedition toward Richmond.  They left camp near Culpepper Court-House and encamped eight miles south of the Rapidan River.  MEMPHIS, Tenn., Friday, Feb. 26. Arrivals from Vicksburgh confirm the previous reports that Gen. SHERMAN had occupied Selma, Ala. The reports from Gen. SMITH'S cavalry expedition are not so good. Stragglers who arrived here to-day state that the rebel Generals FORREST, ADAMS, LEE and RODDY, concentrated their forces against those of Gen. SMITH, and forced him back with considerable loss. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 26.  General Smith's expedition has reportedly arrived in the vicinity of Memphis, Tennessee.   NEW YORK, February 26.  A.G. BROWN, Confederate Senator from Mississippi, has written a letter to the Enquirer of the 13th, in reply to a communication that appeared, charging the Federal Government with maltreating the rebel prisoners on Johnson's Island. Mr. BROWN says he has a friend there who corresponds with him regularly, and says his imprisonment was as mild as he could expect, and that he was in want of nothing but liberty. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 25.  General Kilpatrick's forces have commenced moving on an expedition to Richmond.  A skirmish occurred early to-day at Bean Station, Tennessee.  Our army is in front of Dalton, Georgia.  Tunnel Hill has been carried by our forces after considerable fighting.  A rebel raid occurred to-day on Maysville, Kentucky.   PORTLAND, MAINE, February 25. Two more bodies have been recovered from the wreck of the Bohemian, and nine mail-bags have been found. The wreckers have arrived from New-York, and operations will commence at once. The wind is southwest. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 24.  To-day an engagement is continuing at Tunnel Hill, Georgia.  The Senate has passed a bill authorizing the appointment of a Lieutenant-General.   The Richmond papers publish the Military Bill which is now the law of the Confederacy. Section 1 -- Provides that all white men, residents of the Confederate States, between the ages of 17 and 50, shall be in the military service of the Confederate States during the war. Section 2 -- Provides that all between the ages of 18 and 45 now in service shall be retained during the present war in the same organizations in which they were serving at the passage of this act, unless they are regularly discharged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 23.  Fort Powell, in Mobile Bay, has been bombarded by our mortars.  A desperate rebel charge was made on the rear-guard of General Smith's cavalry forces.  A skirmish has occurred near Tunnel Hill, Georgia, this morning.  In the early afternoon, a contest for its possession commenced.  NEW YORK, February 23.  JOHN C. HORNE was arrested yesterday on a complaint made by Mr. B.F. BUTLER, of the banking house of Messrs. PHELPS, MAITLAND  ES  CO., Nos. 45 and 47 Exchange-place. The charge is one of forgery. Mr. HORNE, it seems, claims to be a merchant in Havana. He is charged with having forged endorsements on bills.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 22.  General Palmer's forces are now occupying Ringgold, Georgia.  The expedition  up the Savannah River has withdrawn.  The steamer Bohemian has been lost off Cape Elizabeth.  The Great Sanitary Fair is opening to-day in Brooklyn, New York.  A call of the Republican National Committee has been made, appointing June 17 as the day for the convention to meet in Baltimore.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 21.  A force of troops have left Hilton Head and are proceeding up the Savannah River.  There is heavy fighting in Pontotoc, Mississippi.  AID TO THE PACIFIC RAILROAD. Mr. SHERMAN, of Ohio, (Union,) introduced a bill to amend an act to aid in the construction of a railroad and telegraph line from the Missouri River to the Pacific Ocean, and to secure to the Government the use of the same for postal, military and other purposes, approved July 1, 1862. Referred to Committee on Pacific Railroad. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 20.  A skirmish with Mosby's cavalry at Piedmont Station, Virginia, occurred to-day.  A battle occurred to-day at Olustee, Florida.  Our troops under General Seymour met 15,000 rebels, 55 miles beyond Jacksonville.  The battle was desperately fought during three hours and at sunset our forces retired, overpowered, to Sanderson.  Sherman's troops have reportedly left Meridian and the rebels are moving back in, rebuilding the railroads etc.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 19.  General Seymour's forces have advanced to Barber's Station, a distance of 12 miles.  Gloucester, Mass., Thursday, Feb. 18. A fire broke out in Sawyer's Block at 3 o'clock this morning, and it is estimated that seventy-five buildings were destroyed. It has swept Front-street entirely on both sides, and is still raging furiously. Some eight or ten buildings have been blown up to stop it. The engines cannot be worked, it is so cold, and the men are used up. Among the buildings destroyed is the telegraph office. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 18.  General Seymour has reportedly left Jacksonville, Florida, and established a depot of supplies at Baldwin, Florida.  General Smith's Union expedition has reached Okolona, Mississippi, 75 miles south of Corinth, Mississippi.   ARRIVAL OF DESERTERS. Forty-one lusty rebels, in uniform, marched up Pennsylvania-avenue unguarded. They told that they had been conscripted six weeks ago, were Union men, and had not been in action yet. and had escaped through LEE's picket lines to seek the protection of our Government. They did not say anything about enlisting however. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Feb. 17 -- 11 1E2 P.M. ADMIRAL DAHLGREN'S INACTIVITY. The Committee on the Conduct of the War will soon examine into the causes of the inactivity of the iron-clad fleet off Charleston. Persons and papers will be called for, and a thorough investigation made into the causes of the delay on the part of the navy to cooperate with the army in its assaults on the rebel stronghold.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 16.  The Governor of Alabama has issued a proclamation to the citizens of Mobile, informing them that the city was about to be attacked, and exhorting noncombatants to leave.  Gen. Sherman's troops are continuing their binge of destruction in Meridian, Mississippi.  SEVERE COLD. The coldest weather ever known in Washington crushed the town yesterday and to-day. The nervous measure of the cold was trebled by a furious north wind. Drivers were taken from the horse cars this morning disabled. Soldiers were rescued last night from freezing in the suburbs. The mercury then stood  six above. A gale in full blast. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 15.  Sherman's troops numbering 10,000 have set destruction upon Meridian, Mississippi.  They have proceeded to take apart railroads, warehouses, shops, supply depots, arsenals, offices, cantonments, hotels, and nearly everything else in a five day binge of destruction.  Resistance from rebel General Polk's small force has been negligible.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 14.   Meridian, Mississippi, has been evacuated by the rebels.  A guerilla attack has occurred at Tecumseh Landing, Mississippi.  THE RISE AND FALL OF THE WHISKY BAROMETER. The ebb and flow of whisky makes the holders of that fluid the wretchedest of men. They were happy yesterday when the House, by a bare majority of four, voted to concur with the Senate in its amendment downward of the Tax Bill. They are in mourning to-night over the rumor that the Conference Committee is going to stretch its action and recommend a swinging tax upward on all stocks on hand. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 13.  The entire line of the Memphis and Charleston railroad has been evacuated by our forces.  A telegram from Cumberland Gap says that on the 12th inst. the rebel Gen. LONGSTREET had his headquarters at Morristown, and his army was encamped, under marching orders, at Strawberry Plains. Deserters, who are very numerous, come into our lines reporting that LONGSTREET's confidence in his men is so slight that on that account he is deterred from attacking Knoxville.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 12.  The enrollment bill was to-day passed in the House of Representatives.  BALTIMORE, Friday, Feb. 12. An express passenger train which left Camdenstreet depot on Thursday night for Wheeling and intermediate points, was captured by a company of Confederates when near Kearneysville Depot, about eight miles west of Harper's Ferry. It appears a switch had been turned, and the usual signal, the waving of a lighted lamp, made by the raiders, as the train approached. The signal caused the engineer to stop the engine. The train was then surrounded by the raiders, and a number of armed men entered the cars.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 11.  General W. L. Smith's cavalry expedition has reportedly started in the direction of Collierville, Tennessee.  NEW ORLEANS, February 11.  The friends of Mr. HAHN, the regular Free State candidate for Governor, held a grand mass meeting on the evening of the 10th, which was largely attended, Capt. STEPHEN HOYT, of Massachusetts, had been appointed Acting Mayor of New-Orleans by Gen. SHEPLEY, Military Governor. The registry of voters was proceeding rapidly. About 4,500 had been registered.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 10.  From  NASHVILLE, Tenn., Feb. 8. Major-Gen. Halleck, General-in-Chief: Gen. FOSTER telegraphs from Knoxville, under date of yesterday, that an expedition sent against THOMAS and his band of Indians and whites at Quallatown has returned completely successful. They surprised the town, killed and wounded 215, took 50 prisoners, and dispersed the remainder of the gang in the mountains. Our loss was 2 killed and 6 wounded. U.S. GRANT, Major-General. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 9.  The rebel Mosby has appeared with 300 men on the old Bull Run battlefield.  The rebels claim to have repulsed the late advance across the Rapidan River of a force from the Army of the Potomac. Gen. LEE officially telegraphs the results of ROSSER's late raid, which was chiefly made for the capture of supplies, in which he claims it was very successful. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 8.  A band of rebel guerillas have crossed from Missouri into Kansas, near Aubrey.  The Florida expedition reached Jacksonville, Florida.  The effect of Gen. BUTLER'S demonstration against Richmond is described by two refugees, who arrived at Fortress Monroe from that City yesterday, as having been perfectly fearful. Utter consternation and panic seized upon the people of Richmond, which had been almost denuded of troops to reinforce LEE.  COUN, Newfoundland, Monday, Feb. 8. The telegraph line is still obstructed. We are looking hourly for it to be repaired. The weather is now fine. There is a strong northwest wind.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 7.  The portion of the Army of the Potomac which had been sent out on a reconnaissance has returned to its old quarters.  The rebels have been driven across the Rapidan River.  There is great excitement in Richmond in expectation of the approach of General Butler's force.  An expedition sent from Knoxville, Tennessee, has returned, having surprised a body of rebels.  Killed and wounded are 215, taken prisoner are 50, and the remainder of the band are dispersed.  COUN, Newfoundland, Saturday, Feb. 6.  There was a severe sleet storm on Tuesday night and Wednesday, and the line east broke on Wednesday morning. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 6.  The expedition sent out by Gen. Butler with object of liberating our troops held as prisoners at Richmond, made a demonstration at Bottom's Bridge and drove in the rebel pickets.  There is great excitement in Richmond.  A portion of the Army of the Potomac is engaged.  Sherman's force has reportedly left Jackson for Meridian, Mississippi, about 100 miles away.  The Nashville Union of the 2d inst. announces that a portion of Gen. GRANT'S army has crossed the Tennessee River at Larkinsville, Alabama, which is a station on the Mobile and Charleston Railroad, about thirty-five miles west of Stevenson. It is several miles north of the Tennessee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 5.  A formidable expedition has left Port Royal, South Carolina, under command of General Seymour, for Jacksonville, Florida.  General Sherman has entered Jackson, Mississippi. the rebels have offered little resistance.  An engagement has occurred between General Sherman's forces and the rebels at Bear Creek, near Clinton, Mississippi.  A dispatch from Gen. BUTLER says that on the 2d inst, the enemy seized the railroad between Newbern and Morehead City, and captured the gunboat Underwriter, which they destroyed. A dispatch one day later announces, however, that the rebels did not hold their ground, but retired to Kinston.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 4.  Col. Mulligan has to-day driven the rebels from Moorefield, West Virginia, after six hours of hard fighting.  The expedition to White Oak River has reportedly came on a body of rebel cavalry about five miles from Young's  Cross Roads, capturing the entire party.  Skirmishing of Gen. Sherman's forces is occurring near Champion Hill.  Rebels have burned the telegraph office at Red House. The telegraph line is now working over the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 3.  General Sherman's expedition has reportedly left Vicksburg, Mississippi.  The rebels threatening Newbern, North Carolina, have retired to Kingston, and Newbern has been relieved from danger of attack.  An expedition has left Newport for White Oak River on a reconnaissance.  WHEELING, Wednesday, Feb. 3. Gen. KELLY telegraphs this afternoon to Gov. BOREMAN that the rebels have been driven back from the line of the railroad at all points, and are now in full retreat, vigorously pursued by our troops. The damage to the North Branch and Patterson Creek bridges is but trifling. The railroad will be in working order in two days.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 2.  A portion of our forces have encountered a large force of rebels in Mechanicsburgh Gap, near Romney, West Virginia.  We succeeded in forcing the rebels to retreat.  A guard posted at Patterson's Creek bridge, on the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, was attacked by rebel cavalry.  The rebels fired the bridge, which was not consumed.  The rebels were driven back from the railroad at all points.  A vessel which had run into Charleston Harbor as destroyed by shot from our vessels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, February 1.  The President ordered that a draft for 500,000 men, to serve for three years or during the war, be made on the 10th day of March, for military service of the United States, crediting and deducting therefrom so many as may have been enlisted or drafted into the service prior to the first day of March, and not heretofore credited.  Rebels are reportedly advancing in Western Virginia.  Burlington is occupied by them.  Fighting in the New Creek, Virginia, valley has commenced.  An engagement at Smithfield, Virginia, is continuing.  Our outposts at Bachelor's Creek have been driven in by a strong force of rebels threatening Newbern, North Carolina.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 31.  An expedition went up the James River to Smithfield, Virginia, to destroy provisions etc. of the rebels.  An engagement occurred to-day at Smithfield.  A final repulse of the rebels endeavoring to retake Cumberland Gap occurred to-day.  NASHVILLE, Tenn., Tuesday, Jan. 26. Gen. ROSSEAU lately received information that a brigade of rebel cavalry under Gen. FORREST, with a battery of artillery, were about to cross the Tennessee River at Florence, Alabama, for the purpose of a raid through Middle Tennessee. Gen. ROSSEAU has made preparations to receive them.  He has strengthened the posts and sent out scouting parties.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 30.  A supply train has been captured by the rebels near Petersburgh, West Virginia.  The garrison of Petersburgh evacuated the place in the night.  The engagement with the rebels endeavoring to retake Cumberland Gap is continuing.  FIVE MILES NORTH OF TUNNEL HILI, G.A., FRIDAY, Jan. 29, 1864. Gen. PALMER, with Gen. DAVIS's division, moved here yesterday on a reconnaissance. The Twenty-eighth Kentucky and Fourth Michigan drove in the rebels' advance pickets and captured a company of rebel cavalry. The rebels retreated from Tunnel Hill during the night. They lost 32 killed and wounded. Our loss was two wounded.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 29.  Three brigades of a cavalry corps, about 1,600 strong, skirmished with the rebels under Gen. Jones on the Virginia road, 13 miles from Cumberland Gap.  The skirmishing lasted three hours.  Our forces held their position until dark, though they were attacked by a superior force, when they withdrew to their camps, three miles in the rear.  CAIRO, Wednesday, Jan. 27. The Steamer Belle of Memphis, with 292 bales of cotton, and Memphis dates of the 25th, has arrived. She also brought 450 reenlisted men of the Kansas cavalry, with about the same number of furloughed men from various other regiments, all en route home.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 28.  The resolution in the Senate, to expel Senator Garrett Davis of Kentucky, has been withdrawn.  Gen. Palmer made a reconnaissance to Tunnel Hill, George.  The rebels retreated in the night.    It appears from a letter found on the body of Capt. WILLIAM R. SMITH, who was killed in the recent fight with COLE's cavalry on Loudon Heights, that MOSEBY had an  QN electrician QN  attached to his command, for the purpose, no doubt, of tapping the telegraph lines of the Army of the Potomac. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 27. The rebel army at Dalton, Georgia, is reported to be 30,000 strong, and so reduced in supplies that they are killing their best mules for supplies of meat. Gen. GRANT arrived at Chattanooga yesterday morning. A dispatch from Cincinnati to the Philadelphia Bulletin confirms the report that Gen. ROSEGRANS has been assigned to the Department of Missouri, and adds that Gen. SCHOFIELD has been ordered to report to Gen. GRANT, and will be assigned to a command in East Tennessee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 26.  Senator Bayard, of Delaware, announced his determination to resign his office, and delivered his valedictory.  Athens, Alabama, has been taken by the rebels.  Gen. Palmer sent an expedition into Jones and Ouslow Counties, North Carolina, which succeeded in destroying large quantities of stores.  The news from Chattanooga is encouraging. Trains are now running regularly between that place and Nashville. The arrival of supplies is large, and full rations are again issued to the troops. A large number of recruits are constantly arriving, sufficient to balance the number of Veterans going home. The desertions from the rebel army are very numerous.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, January 25.  Mr. J.B. RICHARDS, one of the operators in the employ of the People's Telegraph Company. No. 21 Wall-street, died very suddenly on Friday.   HAVANA, Saturday, Jan. 16, 1864. From St. Domingo we are told that the Spanish forces under the command of Gen. HUNGRIA, civil and military Governor of the District of Samana, made a successful attack on the enemy's camp on the 31st ult., which, after a hard resistance, they took, together with what was contained in it, consisting of one cannon, an 8-pounder, ammunition, arms, horses, clothing, two oxen, and a large supply of fresh meat. The attack was made in two opposite directions.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 24.  Gen. Butler has issued an order forbidding the passage through our lines of white women and children from the South.  HALIFAX, Wednesday, Jan. 20. A severe gale, with rain, hail and snow, visited this province yesterday and last night, prostrating telegraph wires, and doing other damage. In the Admiralty Court to-day nothing was done, and it adjourned until next Wednesday. The Chesapeake is unloading her cargo at the Government warehouse for safe keeping. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 23.  Two Mississippi regiments have attempted to fight their way out of the rebel lines, for the purpose of taking the oath of allegiance to the United States.  OSWEGO, N.Y., Tuesday, Jan. 19. A violent storm of hail and rain prevails here this afternoon, accompanied by most severe lightning. The wind is northeast and a snow-storm appears to be setting in. BUFFALO, Tuesday, Jan. 19 -- P.M. The snow-storm continues with a high wind. No trains leave for the East or West before to-morrow. Telegraphic communication is interrupted.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, January 22.   The steamship Morning Star, from New-Orleans Jan.12, arrived at this port last evening. On the day of her departure a very important proclamation was issued by Gen. BANKS, calling for an election of officers for a State Government, to be held on the 22d of February, under the provisions of the Amnesty Proclamation.  CINCINNATI. Tuesday, Jan. 19. There are eight inches of snow on the ground here. The weather is clear this afternoon, and the mercury stands at 27 above zero. The railroad trains are all behind time to-day, being snow-bound. The Ohio River is open to Maysville, Ky.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 21.  In Tennessee there is a growing movement to denounce slavery and rejoin the Union.  A pro-Northern faction has met at Nashville and proposed a resolution for the abolition of slavery.  Confederate hospital buildings have burned in an extensive conflagration at Camp Winder, near Richmond.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Jan. 19. The diplomatic correspondence which has been submitted to Congress, is in printed form, and very voluminous. It commences as far back as November, 1862, and relates to many interesting subjects.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, January 20.  It has been stated that the American Telegraph Company have had all their cables across the North River destroyed. Such is not the case. They have seven cables, five of which were carried away. The other two have worked regularly. The wires connecting with the five disabled cables are yet operating from Jersey City, but it is expected a portion of the broken cables will be repaired to-day. There will be no delay to business hereafter in consequence of the accident.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, January 19.  An unsuccessful attempt was made to burn President Davis' home to-day.  CHICAGO, Ill., Thursday, Jan. 7, 1864. The telegraph has doubtless informed you of the general outlines of the  QN Great Storm QN  which passed over so large a section of the country last week. It was emphatically a great storm -- It has been as cold, the wind has blown as furiously, and as much snow has fallen in a given time -- but all three have not before come in combination. A week has passed, and there has been scarcely any improvement in the temperature. Even in our best houses -- with grate, or furnace, or stove in full blast -- it has at times been next to impossible to keep warm.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 18.   Pro-Union areas of western North Carolina, northwestern Georgia, and eastern Tennessee are reportedly becoming more vocal in their protest about the South's conscription laws.  Evasion is becoming more frequent and open meetings are being held to protest the draft.  THE REBEL FORCES IN TEXAS. Authentic information received by the Government reduces considerably the numbers of the rebel forces in Texas and other portions of the Southwest. The whole of MAGRUDER's force in Texas does not exceed 15,000, and the troops in Louisiana, under command of TAYLOR and other guerrilla chiefs, are put down at less than half that number. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 17.  Gen. HANCOCK goes North to-morrow on business of the War Department. Gen. WARREN will, in his absence, command the Second corps.  Gen. MEADE is in constant communication with his army by telegraph, and commands it over the wires.  Great activity prevails at the Naval Depot at Cairo, and it is said that an expedition to go up Red River is being fitted out. Workmen are engaged  in preparing the boats required for this purpose, and in about two weeks it is expected that all will be ready. What the object of the expedition is has not transpired. the Red River should be sufficiently high to admit the passage of these vessels up very far.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, January 16.  The Richmond Enquirer reports that  QN there were 26 ships off Wilmington that...guard all the avenues of approach with the most sleepless vigilance. QN  The consequences are that the chances of running the blockade have been greatly lessened, and it is apprehended by some that the day is not far distant when it will be an impossibility for a vessel to get into that port without incurring a hazard almost equivalent to positive loss.  Having secured nearly every seaport on our coast, the Yankees are enabled to keep a large force off Wilmington.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 15.  GENERALS WHO WILL NOT BE CONFIRMED. Senators are determined to correct many of the errors of military appointment inevitable in the hurry and ignorance that ruled the opening of the war. At least five Major-Generals and over twenty Brigadiers will be restored to civil life by the consent of the Senate. and if officers of higher rank than those named obstruct the prosecution of the war by being obstacles to promotions profitable and necessary to the country, they too will be removed. The purpose of the Senate in these regards seems fixed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 14.  Our pickets at Three Mile Station, Virginia, have been attacked by rebel cavalry.  Union troops returned to Point Lookout following a raid in Virginia.  Rebels under Gen. Vance have reportedly made a raid toward Tenisville, Tennessee, and captured a train of 23 wagons.  They were promptly pursued by Col. Palmer, who recaptured the wagons and took an ambulance loaded with medicines, 150 saddle-horses, and 100 stand of arms.  Gen. Vance, together with his Adjutant-General and Inspector-General, was captured.  The rebel steamer Mayflower has been captured in Sarasota Pass, Florida.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, January 13.  An Interesting trial of skill through the medium of the electric telegraph was initiated last evening between an association of chess amateurs holding their meetings at No. 189 Bowery, New-York, and known as the  QN Paulsen Chess Club, QN  and the Chess Club of Philadelphia. On the present occasion the Philadelphians are represented by three of their ablest players, Messrs. WHITEMAN, KEICHELN and THOMAS, and the New-Yorkers by Messrs. BENZINGEE, JOHNSTON and CHEMIER. The preliminaries having been agreed upon and New-York having won the  QN toss QN  for first move, their Committee assembled at the office of the People's Telegraph.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 12.  An expedition has reportedly left Point Lookout on a raid through Westmoreland, Northumberland, and Richmond Counties, Virginia.  The force is successful this instant in destroying a large amount of property.  News from Paris, December 25, 1863.  A new Atlantic Telegraph Company is being formed here for laying down a telegraph commencing at Cape Ministered, touching at Lisbon, and crossing the Atlantic to the South American coast at the point where the Atlantic is narrowest. The telegraph will then run up the American coast to the West India Islands and thence to the United States.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 11.   In the Senate, John B. Henderson of Missouri has proposed a joint resolution to abolish slavery throughout the country by amendment to the Constitution.  LEAVENWORTH, KANSAS, Dec. 26, 1863.  A terrible Northwester has prevailed and brought with it snow in quantities unparalleled in this region.  The average depth of the snow from the mountains east to Western Illinois would not be less than eighteen inches in this latitude. The drifts have been enormous. All communication, East or West, has been interrupted for over a week.  The Hannibal and St. Joseph Road was blockaded for several days, one or two trains been closed in drifts for that period.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 10.  A heavy fight occurred to-day near Strawberry Plains, East Tennessee.  The rebels were repulsed with heavy loss.  A battalion of Maryland cavalry have been attacked by rebel guerilla Mosby in Loudon County, Virginia.  NEW YORK, January 10.  Last week an order was received from the Navy Department at Washington, by Admiral PAULDING, directing the discharge from Brooklyn Navy Yard of ROBERT M. STEELE, master carpenter, ISAAC R. STEELE, his brother, clerk, and WM. ROBERTSON and JOHN KERLIN, quartermen. These discharges were made upon the report of a committee of investigation appointed on the 22d of December to investigate certain allegations of fraud and corruption against these parties. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 9.  Word is received from Richmond that President Davis has warned his commanders in Mobile, Alabama, that an attack by Admiral Farragut could be expected soon.  BUFFALO, Saturday, Jan. 9. A high wind is blowing here, accompanied by a heavy snow-storm. The thermometer stands at seven degrees above zero. The weather is nearly as bad as it was last Saturday. The telegraphic lines are all working. There is no detention on the railroads. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 8. Our garrison at Petersburg, West Virginia, is now surrounded by rebels.  The Anglo-rebel steamer Dare is successfully chased and destroyed.  HALIFAX, Friday, Jan. 8. The steamship Africa, Capt. SHANNON, from Liverpool at 10 o'clock on the morning of the 26th, via Queenstown on the afternoon of the 27th of December, arrived at this port at 7 1E2 o'clock this evening, bringing three days later intelligence from Europe. The Africa reports that she has had heavy weather and head winds during the entire passage. She sailed for Boston at 7 3E4 o'clock this morning, where she will be due to-morrow (Saturday) evening.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 7.  Judge Caleb B. Smith, late Secretary of the Interior, died to-day.  A rebel force of about three thousand cavalry, supposed to be commanded by IMBODEN, was marching in the direction of New-Creek, West Virginia, and there was great activity among Union troops along the road. On Sunday afternoon a force of guerrillas fell upon a Government train between New-Creek and Petersburgh, and captured a large number of horses and wagons. One of the teamsters, a negro, seeing the guard overpowered, cut his mules loose from the wagon, mounted the saddle mule, and made his way safely to New-Creek, followed by the balance of the animals.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 6.  A skirmish has occurred in Newtown, West Virginia.  ENLISTMENTS IN THE INVALID CORPS. Further enlistments in the Second battalion of the invalid corps are prohibited -- a sufficient number of men being received by transfer from regiments in active service. Recruits are wanted for the first battalion.  A DESERTER SENTENCED TO BE SHOT. Before a General Court-Martial in Philadelphia, a private in the Eighty-first Pennsylvania Volunteers, was tried and found guilty of desertion and conduct prejudicial to good order and military discipline, having deserted and reenlisted as a substitute, and was sentenced to be shot unto death by musketry. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 5.  REBEL PRISONERS AND THE AMNESTY PROCLAMATION. The President's Amnesty Proclamation will soon be presented to the rebel prisoners now in our hands. We now hold over forty thousand of all grades. Of this number, 30 per cent., it is estimated, will avail themselves of this opportunity to escape from confinement and the thralldom of JEFF. DAVIS.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, January 4.  C. Godfrey Gunther was to-day inaugurated mayor of this city.  The cavalry reconnaissance sent on January first to Front Royal, Virginia, has reportedly returned to the Army of the Potomac.   WASHINGTON, January 4.  The position of rebel army.  One division of EWELL'S corps occupies the heights of Fredericksburgh, where it has gone into winter quarters. A few field pieces are mounted on the fortifications fronting the river.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, January 3.  Archbishop Hughes died to-day.  At Jonesville, Virginia, three hundred of our troops were attacked by an overwhelming force of rebels.  After a desperate resistance, our forces surrendered, losing thirty killed, thirty wounded, one gun, and two small howitzers.  The American ship Living Age, from Akyab for London, has been captured by the rebel pirate Tuscaloosa, and released on giving bonds for  SX 160,000. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK,  January 2. To-day, more machinery used in the making of Confederate bonds and treasury notes was seized in this city.  The police commissioners of New York, who were removed from office by Governor Seymour on December 31, replied to the governor's communication, declining to relinquish their offices until they have been accorded a trial on the charges preferred against them.  WASHINGTON, January 2.   Two rebel captains, HAMILTON and Mix, and eleven privates, were captured by the Eighth Iowa cavalry, in Hickman County, Tenn., and Were taken to Nashville on Wednesday. A rebel lieutenant was killed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, January 1, 1864.  Machinery used to make Confederate bonds and treasury notes were found in this city.  The machinery included a geometrical lathe, dies, and plates.  The contractor was arrested.  Six million dollars of Confederate bonds and one million dollars in treasury notes were confiscated.  State officers of New York were sworn in to-day at Albany.  WASHINGTON, January 1, 1864.  An emancipation jubilee of the colored inhabitants of Norfolk, Virginia, and vicinity, on the anniversary of the issuing of the President's proclamation of freedom, is underway.  A cavalry reconnaissance has reportedly departed to the vicinity of Front Royal, Virginia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, December 31.  The Richmond Examiner to-day reported  QN to-day closes the gloomiest year of our struggle. QN   A dispatch from Cumberland announces that a considerable rebel force, under Gen. EARLY, of LEE'S army, is in the Shenandoah Valley, between New-Market and Mount Jackson, evidently moving upon Winchester. Deserters arriving report many rebel troops anxious to accept the terms of the President's Proclamation.  WASHINGTON, Thursday, Dec. 31. POSTPONEMENT OF THE DRAFT. Orders have been issued by the War Department postponing the draft until the 15th of January. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>MEMPHIS, Wednesday, Dec. 30. After suffering defeat at Summerville and Middlebury, the particulars of which have not been received, the rebel Gen. FORREST divided his forces into four columns, which were reported to be 4,000 strong and crossed Wolf River, near Lafayette yesterday afternoon. They destroyed several small culverts, trestles, and the telegraph on the Memphis and Charleston Railroad, between Colliersville and Moscow, and have gone South, with Gen. GRIERSON's cavalry and MORGAN's brigade of infantry in hot pursuit, and it is hoped will bring them to a stand at Coldwater.  The telegraph is now working, and the railroad will be repaired this inst.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 29.  An expedition to cooperate with Gen. Averill's forces has reportedly returned to Harper's Ferry.  On Thursday evening, the atmosphere being unusually dry and clear, some interesting experiments were made upon the line of the American Telegraph Company.  The lines from Portland, Boston and New-York were connected with Philadelphia, Louisville and Chattanooga, and the operators at both ends were in instant communication with each other, exchanging friendly greetings, congratulations upon recent Union triumphs, etc.  It was proposed to make a connection with Salt Lake, in distant Utah, which could likely have been accomplished.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 28. MEMPHIS, Tenn., Dec. 17, 1863. GENERAL ORDERS, No. 173. -- Colored troops properly disciplined and commanded, can and will fight well, and the general commanding the corps deems it to be due to the officers and men of the Second Regiment West Tennessee Infantry of African Descent, thus publicly to return his personal thanks for their gallant and successful defense of the important position to which they had been assigned, and for the manner in which they have vindicated the wisdom of the Government in elevating the rank and file of these regiments to the position of freedman and soldiers. By order of Maj.-Gen. S.A. HURLBUT.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 27.  Obsequies were cited to-day for the late Gen. Corcoran.  A Southern paper gives the following big statistics about JOHN MORGAN:  QN JOHN MORGAN has fought sixty-three battles, and has been successful in fifty-seven. taken 50,000 prisoners. killed and wounded 20,000, and destroyed  SX 50,000,000 worth of property. taken 50,000 stand of small arms, 50 pieces of artillery and 20,000 horses, and traveled 12,000 miles. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 26.  The C.S.S. Alabama has reportedly captured and burned the ships Sonora and Highlander, both in ballast and at anchor in the entrance of the Straits of Malacca.  LYNCHBURGH, Sunday, Dec. 20. A special correspondent of the Virginian says that on Wednesday morning the enemy's advance guard charged up Main-street, with pistols drawn, ready to open fire upon the citizens who crowded the street. They broke open the Post-office, cut the telegraph wires, and then proceeded to the depot, which was crowded with ladies and gentlemen awaiting the train. They broke open trunks, destroyed their contents, and set fire to the building.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 25.  The shelling of Charleston is continuing to-day.  Ten or twelve buildings have been destroyed by fire.  EDRAY, POCAHONTAS COUNTY, West Va.,  Dec. 22, 1863. Gen. W. W. Averill reports to Major-Gen. Halleck, General-in-Chief: I have the honor to report that I cut the Virginia and Tennessee Railroad at Salem on the 16th inst., and have arrived safely at this point with my command. Three depots were destroyed and 100 wagons. The telegraph wire was cut, coiled and burned for half a mile. The water station, turn-table and three cars were burned, and the track torn up and rails heated and destroyed as much as possible in six hours. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 24.  There was vigorous bombardment of the city of Charleston, South Carolina, in the night.  CLEVELAND, Friday, Dec. 18, 1863. The Convention of Assessors in session in this city for three days past, adjourned this afternoon, and the members are hurrying off to their respective States and districts this evening, to be followed by the others to-morrow morning. It has been eminently a working Convention. Never, perhaps, has a Convention considered, discussed and disposed of so much business, of so much public importance, in so short a time. They ate no idle bread while here.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, December 23. The  QN New-England Society in the City of New-York, QN  celebrated the Fifty-eighth Anniversary of their existence, and the Two Hundred and Forty-third Anniversary of the Landing of the Pilgrims in Plymouth, in their usual manner, last evening, by a dinner at the Astor House. About three hundred and twenty persons, including members of the Society and invited guests, sat down at the tables.  The President of the Society, Mr. HENRY HURLBUT, presided on the occasion, and on this right sat Rev. Henry Ward Beecher, Hon. John P. Hale, United States Senator from New-Hampshire, Rev. Dr. Weston, Gen. Sickles, Judge Roosevelt, and Gen. Dix.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 22.  Gen. Michael Corcoran died to-day.  Rebel Capt. Semmes of the C.S.S. Alabama has reportedly moved his base of operations from the East Indies back to the Cape of Good Hope, Africa.   By telegraph from Fortress Monroe, we have a dispatch published in the Richmond papers of the 19th. from Charleston, to the effect that the Ironsides and three monitors, while attempting to pass the obstructions, became entangled, and that the Ironsides will probably have to be abandoned. Two of the monitors were also said to have been badly disabled. This is the result of an attempt probably made by our vessels to pass the obstructions. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 21.   DISPATCHES TO THE ASSOCIATED PRESS. WASHINGTON, Saturday, Dec. 19. The Evening Star has the following:  QN The authorities here have dispatches from Gen. GRANT, at Chattanooga, dated last night at 9 o'clock. They do not indicate any recent change in the state of affairs there. Gen. GRANT is in constant and direct telegraphic communication with Gen. FOSTER, at Knoxville, and had there been fighting between LONGSTREET's forces and ours pursuing him -- as the press dispatches from Cincinnati state -- Gen. GRANT would, doubtless, have sent dispatches here.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 20.  LIVERPOOL, Thursday, Dec. 3. COTTON -- The sales for the last two days were up 3,500 bales, including 1,000 to speculators and exporters. The market has declined to 1d. TO 2d. since the sailing of the Canada, BREADSTUFFS quiet and steady. PROVISIONS dull and tending downward. The Bank of England advanced its rate of discount yesterday to seven, and again to-day to eight per cent. This caused much depression in the funds, the quotations for which are not yet received from London. A furious gale interferes with telegraphing. Considerable damage is reported.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 19.  The steamer Chesapeake has been delivered over to British authorities at Halifax.  The prisoners, on landing, were rescued by the citizens.  The authorities here have dispatches from Gen. GRANT, at Chattanooga, dated last night at 9 o'clock. They do not indicate any recent change in the state of affairs there. Gen. GRANT is in constant and direct telegraphic communication with Gen. FOSTER, at Knoxville, and had there been fighting between LONGSTREET's forces and ours pursuing him -- as the press dispatches from Cincinnati state -- Gen. GRANT would, doubtless, have sent dispatches here.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 18.  Secretary of State Seward and British envoy Lord Lyons have to-day discussed the capture of the steamer Chesapeake.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, Dec. 15. Though Gen. BUTLER and a member of the Sanitary Commission now at Fortress Monroe, have telegraphed to the Government here that the rebel authorities have stopped the distribution of supplies sent from the loyal States to the Union prisoners in their hands, we are notified that up to this time no information had reached Washington indicating that anything like an official rebel notice has been communicated to either Maj.-Gen. BUTLER or Brig.-Gen. MEREDITH.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 17.   Yesterday, John Buford, who commanded the cavalry that made the initial contact at Gettysburg, was promoted to Major General.  Last night, he died of typhoid.  The steamer Chesapeake, captured by rebel passengers on December 6, has been retaken by the Elia and Annie in Sambro Harbor, near Halifax.  Rebel Gen. Stuart's cavalry has raided the Orange and Alexandria Railroad.   The customary annual visit of the Justices of the Supreme Court of the United States to the President, was postponed on account of his illness. But, upon a formal notice that he would be happy to see them to-day, they proceeded in a body to the Executive Mansion.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 16.  The Virginia and Tennessee Railroad has been cut at Salem by Gen. Averill's cavalry expedition.  Three depots were destroyed, containing 2,000 barrels of flour, 10,000 bushels of wheat, 100,000 bushels of shelled corn, 50,000 bushels of oats, 2,000 barrels of meat, and many other articles.  RICHMOND, December 16.  Rebel Gen. Joseph Eggleston Johnston will replace Lt. Gen. William Hardee as commander of the Army of Tennessee.  Johnston has been located at Brandon, Mississippi, and will leave his command to Lt. Gen. Leonidas Polk.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 15.  Rebel Gen. Longstreet's forces have driven back the Federals, under the command of Brig. Gen. James M. Shackelford, in a sharp fight.  Federal forces held for a while but have now withdrawn further.   Telegrams were received here last evening from Knoxville up to yesterday morning. Gen. FOSTER had assumed the command of the troops lately under Gen. BURNSIDE, and the latter had departed from that City for Cincinnati. All was then quiet in the vicinity of Knoxville. It was stated there, on the authority of scouts and messengers that much of Gen. LONGSTREET's artillery and trains had fallen into the hands of our pursuing force.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 14.  A portion of rebel Gen. Longstreet's army has made a descent from Rogersville and engaged the advance of our forces near Bean's Station.  Gen. Longstreet divided his army and made, with one portion, an attack on Bean's Station, and with the other an attack on Kelly's Ford.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 13.  BRISTOL, Thursday, Dec. 10. LONGSTREET's forces are in line of battle at Rutledge. His rear is skirmishing with the enemy, whose pursuit has not been vigorous since our forces left Morristown. Our cavalry were skirmishing all day Monday with the advance of WILCOX's forces on Clinch River. Capt. EVERETT's raiding party returned to Abingdon, attacked the enemy at Mt. Sterling, Kentucky, and routed them after a stubborn resistance. The court-house and jail were burned. Capt. EVERETT captured a number of horses and  SX 100,000 in greenbacks.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 12.  Gen. Butler gave notice that the rebel authorities are now refusing to receive more supplies for the Union prisoners in Richmond.  Up to now, rations have been sent to feed the 13,000 Union prisoners held there.   Rebel Gen. John Morgan has escaped across the Tennessee River at Gillespie's Landing, 60 miles from Chattanooga.  PORTLAND, Friday, Dec. 11. Collector WASHBURNE has just received the following from Halifax:  QN The Chesapeake is at St. Mary's destitute of coal. Gunboats will take her if there to-morrow. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 11.  Over 220 shells were fired at Fort Sumter to-day and it is on fire.  One shell exploded a powder magazine, killing 11 and wounding 41 of the defenders.    CAIRO, Saturday, Dec. 5. Memphis papers of the 3d instant are received. The Memphis Bulletin says:  QN Cotton is less active than any day previous to October. The sales to-day were 172 bales. Forty to fifty rebels made a raid on Saulsbury, on the 2d instant. They tore up the railroad track for some distance, burning the ties, twisting the rails and cutting the telegraph wires. HATCH's cavalry started in pursuit of them, and we took forty prisoners. The railroad was repaired in twenty-four hours.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 10.  Shells were reportedly thrown into Charleston, South Carolina, during the night.  The Abingdon Virginian learns from good authority that a small body of Yankees came up to Jonesville on Friday, the 6th, from the Gap, and committed all sorts of depredations. They burnt the Academy and Masonic Hall, set fire to a church, and stole all the horses, cattle, grain and negroes they could find.  QN When it is remembered, QN  remarks the Petersburgh Express,  QN that there are abundant, supplies in Lee -- enough to Winter a division of our army -- it is almost criminal to permit these degradations -- especially when a battalion of men could prevent it. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 9.  President's Lincoln amnesty message was to-day transmitted to Congress.  The captain and crew of the steamer Chesapeake landed at St. John.  GREAT SALT LAKE CITY, Thursday, Nov. 12, 1863. The prices of provisions show no symptoms of relaxation. Continuous arrivals from the Bannock Mines, for the purpose of purchasing in those branches of business, conduce to a stiffening of the figures asked by sellers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 8.  The House of Representatives unanimously passed a vote of thanks to Gen. U.S. Grant and his army, and ordered that a medal be struck in his honor, in the name off the people of the United States.  President Lincoln issued a proclamation of amnesty to-day, to those in the South who will take an oath of allegiance.  Gen. Averill's expedition has moved to cut the Virginia and Tennessee Railroad.  CUMBERLAND GAP, Friday, Dec. 4. Gen. FOSTER has driven the enemy from Clinch River, and is in pursuit of him. The check our forces, however, received yesterday will doubtless secure the retreat of Gen. LONGSTREET.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 7.  Gen. Foster is reporting that rebel Gen. Longstreet is in full retreat.   EXECUTIVE MANSION, WASHINGTON, D.C. Dec. 7, 1863. Reliable information being received that the insurgent force is retreating from East Tennessee under circumstances rendering it probable that the Union forces cannot hereafter be dislodged from that important position. and esteeming this to be of high national consequence, I recommend that all loyal people do, on receipt of this information, assemble at their places of worship and render special homage and gratitude to Almighty God for this great advancement of the National cause. A. LINCOLN.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 6.  The advance guard of Gen. Sherman's force, sent to the relief of Gen. Burnside, arrived at Knoxville to-day.  The steamer Chesapeake was last night taken possession of, by sixteen rebel passengers near Cape Cod.   The Confederates took over the ship, killing the second engineer, and took her to the Bay of Fundy in Nova Scotia.  The intent was to refuel the ship and go to Wilmington.  The capture of that ship has great alarm in northern ports.  The monitor Weehawken is foundering at her anchors inside Charleston harbor.  Union troops garrisoning Natchez, Mississippi, were attacked by rebels to-day. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 5.  The steamer Isaac Newton was destroyed to-day.  Rebels are threatening our forces near the Rapidan River.  Gen. Butler has issued an important order relative to the colored troops.   NASHVILLE, Tenn., Friday, Nov. 27, 1863. Yesterday was duly observed here as a National Thanksgiving, according to the President's appointment. A more brilliantly beautiful day has never greeted this honored and honoring anniversary. Not a cloud was seen in the sky, nor did a dry leaf rustle by the slightest breeze during all the day. Several of the churches held religious services, and respectably numerous audiences gathered to render fitting praise.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 4.  To-day there was a rebel cavalry attack on our forage wagons near Harrison, twelve miles from Chattanooga.  OMAHA, N.T., Thursday, Dec. 3, 1863. The great event of breaking ground on the Union Pacific Railway came off yesterday near this city. The population turned out en masse. The Territory was represented by its Governor. the Cities of Omaha and Council Bluffs by the Mayors and Councils. Speeches were made by several gentlemen present, and the grand work inaugurated with the utmost zeal and enthusiasm.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 3.  Rebel Gen. Longstreet has begun moving his troops away from the city of Knoxville.  LOUISVILLE, Thursday, Dec. 3. A midnight special to the Journal says:  QN Gen. WILCOX telegraphed Gen. BURNSIDE, Knoxville, on Nov. 30, that at 11 o'clock on the evening of the 20th, the rebels attacked our force, and succeeded in driving our skirmishing line to the right on the Kingston road and forced it back to Fort Saunders. We afterward regained the position after sharp skirmishing all night. On Sunday morning, at 7 o'clock, the rebels moved three brigades against Fort Saunders, of a portion thereof. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 2.  Rebel cavalry have been repulsed at Clinch River, Tennessee.  Rebel Gen. Bragg has reportedly turned command of the Army of Tennessee over to Lt. Gen. William Hardee.  CINCINNATI, Tuesday, Dec. 1. The Commercial's Cumberland Gap correspondent telegraphs to-night that all available force has been sent from there to intercept LONGSTREET's retreat into Virginia. He says a courier from Knoxville brings intelligence of the enemy's attempt to cross the river on Sunday, bringing on a general engagement, and resulting in the defeat of the enemy and the capture of Gen. WHEELER's division of 5,000 rebels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, December 1.  The Army of the Potomac reportedly commenced falling back yesterday and at night crossed the Rapidan in safety.  CHATTANOOGA, Tuesday, Dec. 1. A dispatch from Gen. BURNSIDE, dated Nov. 25, says:  QN The enemy, on the 25th, moved up three brigades, and attacked his brigade in a strong position on the south of the river, three miles from Knoxville. A hard fight ensued. The enemy was repulsed with a loss of 150 killed. QN   The position was strengthened, and though the enemy moved down a large force with the intention of renewing the attack, BURNSIDE believed it could be held.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 30.  The rebels to-day blew up the magazines of Fort Esperanza, Matagorda Bay, Texas.  At 1 o'clock Friday morning, General Grant telegraphed that his forces are in vigorous pursuit toward Red Clay, which is a station on the Western and Atlantic Railroad, almost due east of Chattanooga. BRAGG took this course evidently in the hope of forming a junction with LONGSTREET, but the splendid cavalry raid of Col. LANG, entirely defeats his object. Col. LANG tore up the railroad for 15 miles above and below Cleveland, and destroyed much valuable property there, including a large foundry. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 29.  The rebels in front of Knoxville were repulsed to-day with heavy loss.  CINCINNATI, Friday, Nov. 27. The steamer Telegraph, No. 3, bound from Cairo to Memphis, sunk at Osceola on Monday. She had 4,000 sacks of Government grain on board and a number of passengers. Three negroes were drowned. Two of the crew were scalded. There were no casualties among the passengers. The vessel lies with seven feet of water in her lower decks. She will doubtless be raised. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 28. The rebels made an attack in force upon a large portion of our line, at Knoxville, Tennessee, the attack being a feint to cover the real point of attack.  Gen. GRANT has achieved the greatest success of the war. He telegraphs officially that our captures amount to fifty-two pieces of artillery, three thousand prisoners, five thousand stand of arms and ten standards. Yesterday, the rebel army was in full flight for Dalton, Ga., burning the bridges to prevent pursuit, and destroying their depots, stores and every thing that could impede their retreat.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 27.  Gen. Grant reported that the route of the rebels was most complete, and that Bragg's loss would fully reach 60 pieces of artillery.  Gen. Hooker's, Palmer's, and Sherman's commands reported ten miles beyond Chickamauga Creek, in pursuit of the rebels.  A fight has occurred near Germanna Ford, on the south side of the Rapidan.  The rebels have fallen back to a stronger position.  Gen. Hooker's corps engaged near Ringgold, Georgia and a battle commenced there.  Rebel Gen. John Morgan and six of his officers escaped from the Ohio Penitentiary during the night.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 26.  This is Thanksgiving Day.  The Army of the Potomac is advancing and crossing the Rapidan.  A severe cavalry battle occurred near the Rapidan, in which the rebels were driven back.  Our forces have left their camps near Missionary Ridge and marched toward Chickamauga, which they reached at 10 a.m., finding that the rebels had left the place, after destroying a large quantity of stores, etc.  Hookers column engaged in skirmishing.   We have taken from 5,000 to 10,000 prisoners, and it was expected that Gen. HOOKER intercept the flying rebels at Rossville. Gen. GRANT telegraphs that our loss is not heavy, and that his success is complete.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Nov. 25. Dispatches giving details of recent operations before Chattanooga were received to-night from Gen. GRANT. He is in happy spirits and confident of success. Atlanta he declares to be a prize already within his grasp. DISPATCHES TO THE ASSOCIATED PRESS. CHATTANOOGA, Wednesday, Nov. 25. We are completely victorious. The enemy is totally routed and driven from every position. Our loss is very small and the enemy's is heavy in prisoners. Finding Gen. HOOKER so successful in his movements against Lookout Mountain, the enemy evacuated that position during the night. Gen. HOOKER took possession early this morning. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 24. Gen. Sherman crossed the Tennessee River before daylight, at the mouth of the South Chickamauga, and carried the northern extremity of Missionary Ridge.  A battle at Lookout Mountain occurred to-day.   Advices received from the Army of the Potomac last-night say the heavy storm of Saturday, while doing no damage to the railroad, had the effect of swelling the principal streams to an almost impassable height. and  the low grounds and hollows, owing to the particularly soft and spongy character of the soil, are full of sloughs and cradle-holes, dangerous to wagon transportation. Deserters come into our lines almost hourly. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 23.   A battle commenced at Chattanooga to-day.  Our forces advanced directly in front of the fortifications, drove in the enemy's pickets, and carried his first line of rifle-pits.  Gen. Hooker carried the northern slope of Lookout Mountain.  From the Liverpool Post, Nov. 7. Telegraphic advices were received in town yesterday announcing the capture of the American ships John Watt and Bold Hunter by the Confederate cruiser Georgia, now at Cherbourg. The Georgia had, we believe, shortly before arriving at Cherbourg, boarded upward of 90 vessels: so the above are only a tithe of what may be expected soon to follow.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 22.   From the San Francisco Bulletin, Oct. 22. It is generally known that a new telegraph line from this city to the East is in progress of construction.   There will be from thirty to forty poles to the mile -- twenty-five being the usual number. It is proposed to make this line throughout one of the most substantial lines ever built.  The instruments to be used -- twenty of which are now here -- are known as the Morse Relay. Their peculiarity consists in their being worked by the main circuit alone -- an ingenious mechanism contrived by the manufacturer, J.J. CLARKE, of Philadelphia, doing away with the trouble and expense of local batteries.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 21.  From GETTYSBURGH, Penn., Thursday Evening, Nov. 19, 1863.  The only train that has been permitted to leave here, to-day, was the special train bearing the President and his party, which left at 6 o'clock this evening. Even the mail train, which should have left at 8 o'clock this morning, was detained for fear it would come in collision with some of the numerous trains that have been following each other in rapid succession from Hanover Junction, bringing visitors to the Dedication. How they are all to sleep here to-night it is difficult to imagine. All the hotels as well as the private houses were filled to overflowing last night. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 20.  News from ST. LOUIS, Wednesday, Nov. 18. The telegraph has been extended to Fort Smith. Gen. MCNEIL has issued an order that all molestations of the telegraph shall be regarded as the work of bushwhackers, and for every cutting of the wires a guerrilla prisoner shall be hung. Our forces occupy Waldron, about 30 miles south of Fort Smith. Our scouting parties have captured a rebel Major, two Captains, and quite a number of prisoners, together with a portion of COOPER's train, laden with commissary stores and ammunition. At last accounts COOPER was flying rapidly toward Red River. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 19.  The Gettysburgh battle-field was consecrated to-day as a national cemetery for the Union soldiers who fell in the July battles at that place.  Addresses were made by President Lincoln and Edward Everett.  An attack occurred on a rebel camp at New Iberia, Louisiana.  The discovery of a rebel plot hatched in Canada to liberate the prisoners on Johnson's Island, and burn Buffalo, and ravage the commerce of Lake Erie is classified here with the finding of mares' nests. The telegraph at Sandusky, Cincinnati, Buffalo and Washington has dwarfed the just proportions of this horror.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 18.  The schooner Jas. L. Gerety, from Matamoras, has been seized by rebel passengers.  A cavalry fight has occurred near Strasburgh, Virginia.  Aranzas, Texas, has been captured by Gen. Banks' troops.  BEAVER MEADOWS, (Penn.,) Wednesday, Nov. 11. The military authorities of the Eleventh District of Pennsylvania are making short work with the Carbon Thugs. The call of the mine owners for assistance was promptly answered on Sunday, by the arrival at Beaver Meadows of two companies of the Invalid corps, under the command of, Capt. D.L. BECKWITH, as senior Captain and ranking officer.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, November 17.   There was enthusiastic reception of Henry Ward Beecher at his church in Brooklyn on his return from Europe.  WASHINGTON, November 17.  One of our camps near Chattanooga was shelled by a rebel battery.  Our troops, falling back before Gen. Longstreet's army, reached Knoxville, Tennessee.  There is continuing attack of the rebels on our forces.  A siege on Knoxville has commenced by Longstreet's army.  A shell was thrown into Charleston, South Carolina, from Fort Gregg.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 16.  Maj. MYERS, Chief of the Signal corps. which got organized in the very crisis of the fever of our military experiment and expenditure, was relieved yesterday and ordered to Memphis then to report back here to the Adjutant-General. The property of the corps has been turned over to Capt. NICODEMUS, except the field telegraphic force and materials and trains, which have been assigned to duty under Col. ANSON STAGER, of the Military Telegraph. The expenditure of the Signal corps is said to be five thousand dollars a day -- and this is the reason given for sending this new exile to our cotton-growing Siberia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 15.  There has been reconnaissance of our forces along the Rapidan at Raccoon Ford.  An advance in force of Gen. Longstreet has occurred on Gen. Burnside's force. our forces are retreating to Knoxville, Tennessee.  Corpus Christi, Texas, has been captured by Gen. Banks' troops.   From the Richmond Enquirer, Nov. 3. The Atlantic telegraph cable is certainly to be tried again. It appears that the indefatigable Mr. CYRUS FIELD has just come over from England to New-York, bringing a specimen of the new cable manufactured by Messrs. GLASS, ELLIOTS  ES  CO., and Yankees are largely taking stock. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 14.  Rebel Gen. Longstreet crossed the Tennessee River in his march against Knoxville, Tennessee.  SAN FRANCISCO, Tuesday, Nov. 10. A fire at Nevada City yesterday destroyed nearly all the buildings on Broad-street, five brick buildings on Main-street, the Episcopal, Methodist, Congregational and Catholic Churches, the theatre, Court-house, express and telegraph offices, the gas works, the United States Hotel and many stores in the neighborhood. The County records were saved. The loss is estimated at  SX 200,000. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 13.  It is reported to-day on authority of the surgeons in the Army of the Potomac, that our losses on Saturday were about 400, as stated in the Press telegram last night. 260 of these who are wounded, arrived here this morning, and were placed in the hospital. The premises of the Old Capitol Prison are densely crowded to-day, 1,730 rebel prisoners that were taken in Saturday's engagements having reached here up to 2 o'clock this morning.  The Star of this city says:  QN We hear that Gen. GRANT has telegraphed hither that two of the most advanced positions of Gen. BURNSIDE have been assailed and captured by the rebels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, November 12.  The laborers, car-drivers, and conductors went on strike to-day in New York City.  The cars have been stopped on some of the city's railroads.  A body of rebel cavalry crossed the Tennessee River and destroyed two railroad bridges near Lynnville, Tennessee. MEMPHIS, Sunday, Nov. 8. The rebel General RICHARDSON struck the Memphis and Charleston Railroad six miles east of Salisbury yesterday morning, destroyed the railroad bridge at Middletown, burned two small bridges, tore up several miles of track, and cut the telegraph badly. The latter was repaired this morning. The former will be in running order to-morrow.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 11.   To-day there was formal presentation to Gen. Meade of the battle flags captured in the battle on the evening of the 7th.  Lord Lyons officially informed the Government at Washington that he had received information from the Governor-General of Canada of a plot to invade the United States from Canada, destroy the City of Buffalo, and liberate the rebel prisoners on Johnson's Island in Lake Erie.  Gen. Butler has assumed command of the Departments of Eastern Virginia and North Carolina, headquarters at Fortress Monroe.  Gen. Foster took leave of his command to-day at Fortress Monroe.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 10.  Rebel report from ATLANTA, Wednesday, Nov. 4. The Yankees maintain possession of Raccoon Valley, having been heavily reinforced. From Richmond papers of Friday received at Fortress Monroe, we obtain the following: The Yankees shell our forces incessantly. The floods in Tennessee have demolished all the Yankee pontoons. The Yankee advance has reached Florence.  The enemy are raiding the country near Huntsville, committing great depredations. Their raids are more disastrous than any of their preceding ones in Madison and Huntsville Counties. BRAGG has it in his power to muzzle the telegraph, but he cannot muzzle the mails.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 9.  Reconnaissance has occurred to Culpepper, Virginia.  Gen. Meade has issued a congratulatory order to his troops on their successful passage of the Rappahannock.  PHILADELPHIA, Friday, Nov. 6. There are reports of a terrible riot in the coal regions around Mauch Chunk.  Four men, it is reported, were killed last evening.  Gov. CURTIN, it is stated, has been telegraphed to for troops to quell the disturbance. THOMAS HULL, of the firm of HULL, SMITH  ES  CORLIES, has received a dispatch from Summit, Penn., that GEORGE K. SMITH, of that firm, has been shot dead by the rioters. Mr. ULRICH, storekeeper, was also fired at by the rioters.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 8.  A cavalry fight has occurred at Hazel Run, Virginia.  Gen. Meade reported that on advancing from Kelly's Ford, in the morning, it was discovered that the rebels had evacuated their position on the Rappahannock.  Our army was put in motion and the pursuit of the rebels continued by the infantry to Brandy Station, and by the cavalry beyond.  Our captures in the fight at Rappahannock were four guns, eight battle flags, and over 1,900 prisoners.  The rebel steamer Cornubia has been captured at Wilmington, North Carolina.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 7.  To-day there was a battle on the banks of the Rappahannock, near Rappahannock station. our army was very successful, capturing rebel redoubts and taking 2,000 prisoners.  The reconnaissance of the Chowan River, North Carolina, is reportedly continuing.  Received from Richmond and published this morning is an official list of the Union officers now confined in the Confederate States military prison at Richmond, with the places and date of their capture. This important document has recently been furnished to our Government by the Confederate authorities. Its publication will not only furnish much information, but will relieve the anxieties of many persons.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 6.  An engagement occurred to-day in West Virginia.  Reconnaissance has occurred on the Chowan River, North Carolina, to near the mouth of the Blackwater.  Damages to the Orange and Alexandria Railroad, effected by the rebels recently, are being repaired.  Eleven miles of the road was reconstructed in seven days.  Among the items of work performed were 653 linear feet of bridges, varying from 20 to 65 feet in height. 27,700 ties were prepared and laid sufficient to make a string of timber 45 miles long. The destruction of the road by the rebels was most thorough. Telegraph poles were cut down and the telegraph wire destroyed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, November 5.  There is a ball in New York city to-day to honor the Russians.  WASHINGTON, November 5.  A skirmish has occurred at Metley's Ford, Tennessee.  The steamer Margaret and Jesse has been captured by the Fulton.  Gen. Averill has attacked and defeated the enemy near Lewisburgh, capturing three pieces of artillery, 100 prisoners, and a large number of small arms, wagons, and a large quantity of camp equipage.  The enemy's loss in killed and wounded is estimated at 300.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 4.  Brownsville, Texas, has been captured by Gen. Banks' army.  ATLANTA, Friday, Oct. 30. No new reports from above by telegraph. The following has been received by mail: MISSIONARY RIDGE, Thursday, Oct. 29. The enemy have crossed a division at Brown's Ferry, three miles below Chattanooga, and are in possession of Raccoon Mountain, which they are apparently fortifying. A rapid shelling of our camps on the west side of Lookout Mountain was kept up by the enemy to-day, our batteries replying. No casualties reported. Heavy skirmishing anticipated on the left.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 3.  Elections have occurred in New-York, New-Jersey, Massachusetts, Minnesota, Missouri, and Wisconsin.  The Union ticket has been successful in all states but one.  A reconnaissance operation has occurred to Falmouth, Virginia.  Rebels have been repulsed at Colliersville, Tennessee.  A battle occurred to-day at Bayou Coteau in the Teche country, Louisiana.  NEWARK, N.J., Monday, Nov. 2. A collision occurred on the Camden and Amboy Railroad, between Trenton and Tacony, on Sunday afternoon. GEORGE S. SPELLMAN, a telegraph operator, had both his legs broken. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 2.  Brazos Island, Texas, is now occupied by Federal forces and Boca Chica has been captured by Gen. Banks' army.  The Convention of the National Telegraphic Union will be held this evening. The Delegates to the Convention will meet at 8 o'clock, at the Everett House, in the City of New-York, for the purpose of completing the organization of the  QN Union, QN  adopting a Constitution and Bye-Laws, and electing a President and other officers for the ensuing year, and transacting such other business as may come before the Convention. The proprietors of the Everett House have most kindly tendered the use of a room for holding the sessions of the Convention. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, November 1.  A plot to liberate rebel prisoners in Ohio was discovered.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Oct 28. JOHN H. O'NEILL, United States Military Telegraph Operator, of Pittsburgh, Penn., a gentleman deservedly esteemed, died this evening in Alexandria, Va., of typhoid fever, aged 23 years.   ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, Tuesday, Oct. 27, 1863. No battle occurred yesterday, as was confidently anticipated by many persons whose opportunities for knowing all the secrets of the service are considered good. The enemy, however, still show a bold front north of the Rappahannock, and no one can foresee what an hour may bring forth.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>UTICA, NEW YORK, Friday, Oct. 30, 1863. The Special train from Albany, bearing the Russians route for Niagara Falls, reached here early yesterday morning. The train consisted of four passenger cars, a lunch car and baggage car, and is under the charge of conductor B.B. YATES, who puts the Russians through at the rate of 45 miles an hour, running time. He reached Niagara Falls at 5 P.M. All the towns have greeted the Russians with waving handkerchiefs.   Before leaving Niagara Falls, this morning, the officers of the Russian fleet went down in a body from the Cataract House to the stairs leading to the ferry at the foot of the American Falls, for a photographic image.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Friday, Oct. 30. Nothing additional to what has already been telegraphed has been received at the headquarters of the army up to noon to-day concerning HOOKER's victory. The fight took place at Brown's Ferry, on the Tennessee River, near Chattanooga, and the result is considered of the highest importance, as it removes the rebel obstructions to steamboat navigation to that point, and secures other advantages in opening up the way for army supplies.  At 9 o'clock yesterday morning, Maj.-Gen. THOMAS telegraphed to the War Department as follows: Gen. HOOKER was attacked at 12 o'clock, midnight, and a severe fight ensued which continued for two hours.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>CHATTANOOGA, Wednesday, Oct. 28, Via NASHVILLE, Thursday, Oct. 29. Lookout Mountain was yesterday taken by our forces, the enemy falling back without resistance. Our troops occupy the south bank of the river from Bridgeport to Chattanooga, and the river and railroad are unobstructed. L.L. CROUNSE. NASHVILLE, Thursday, Oct. 29. Lookout Mountain was taken on the 28th by our troops, under Gen. HOOKER, with the Eleventh corps and a portion of the Twelfth, and PALMER's division of the Fourth corps. There was no serious opposition.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 28.    There has been a furious bombardment of Fort Sumter to-day.  Confederate President Jefferson DAVIS, as he was returning from his visit to BRAGG's army, made a speech at Selma, Ala., on the 18th inst., and we find a telegraphic abstract of it in our Southern files. In the course of it he touched upon the foreign relations of the Confederacy, and remarked:  QN Self-reliance and energy is now our only duty. we should not look to Europe for aid, for such is not to be expected now. QN  So JEFF. DAVIS has at last given up what has been one of his fondest hopes ever since the rebellion broke out -- hope of aid from abroad. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 27.  Shells were thrown into Charleston, South Carolina, by Gen. Gillmore.  NASHVILLE, Sunday, Oct. 25. There is no news of importance from Chattanooga. HOOKER's force has crossed the Tennessee River and fighting was reported yesterday. The telegraph was cut this morning, but is now working. The river is rising, and is five feet on the shoals. There have been no arrivals by the river. Gen. ROSECRANS left for Cincinnati at noon. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 26.  Skirmishing occurred to-day along the lines of the Army of the Potomac.  The bombardment of Fort Sumter is renewed.  Gen. Hooker has moved from Bridgeport, Tennessee.   The military telegraph between Chattanooga and Nashville has been closed to the Press. A dispatch to the Cincinnati Gazette, dated Chattanooga, Oct. 24, says that Gen. GRANT arrived there on the 23d inst. Deserters report BRECKINRIDGE and HINDMAN's forces to have withdrawn from our front and moving in large bodies to our left. The object of the movement was not clear. Rumors say that Rome and Atlanta have been attacked in the rear. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 25.  WASHINGTON, Friday, Oct. 23. Major Gen. MEADE, after a brief visit to Washington, returned to his headquarters to-day. Cavalry reconnoissances are continuing on our part as far as the Rappahannock. The Orange and Alexandria Railroad has already been repaired one mile beyond Bristoe Station. Forces are engaged day and night in repairing the damages of the enemy. Reports from the army say the discipline and morale of the army were never better than at the present time, and both officers and men have the greatest confidence in the ability of Gen. MEADE.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 24.  NASHVILLE, Tenn., Tuesday, Oct. 20. Quartermaster-General MEIGS and Staff arrived here this evening. He reports that Gen. GRANT assumes the command of the Department of the Cumberland, Tennessee and Ohio, to be called the Military Division of Mississippi. Gen. THOMAS, it is reported, is to command the Army of the Cumberland. Gen. HOOKER is at Stevenson, Ala. E.M. STANTON, the Secretary of War, has arrived here on a special train. He is the guest of Judge CATRON.  A railroad accident occurred at Murfreesboro, killing and wounding several. The telegraph is working to Chattanooga. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 23.  Dr. Wright was executed to-day at Norfolk, Virginia.  Dr. Wright had shot a Federal officer dead after the doctor made a comment unbecoming of negro soldiers and the officer attempted to slap Dr. Wright on the cheek with his sword.  The Signal corps has earned additional honors during the late campaign. it first discovered the movements of the enemy from the Rapidan to Madison Court-house, and thence, via Sperryville, to Warrenton, thus enabling Gen. MEADE to take such measures as resulted in defeating LEE's plans. The corps attached to the Army of the Potomac is under the direction of Capt. NORTON.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 22.  A cavalry skirmish occurred to-day near Fayetteville, Virginia.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, Oct. 21. Accounts from the Army of the Potomac, up to 1 o'clock yesterday afternoon, furnish us with the following highly important intelligence: Gen. KILPATRICK's cavalry division, yesterday, pushed back Gen. STUART's rebel cavalry beyond Gainesville toward Warrenton. There was considerable fighting, but no considerable loss on our side. Gen. LEE, it is positively stated, was at Warrenton on Monday, and had formed his line of battle and posted his artillery.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 21.  A battle reportedly occurred to-day near Tuscumbia, Alabama.  There has been a fight near Philadelphia, Tennessee, and a cavalry skirmish near Sulphur Springs, Virginia.  HEADQUARTERS OF THE ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, Saturday Evening, Oct. 17, 1863. The recent movements of the two great armies now confronting each other in Virginia are not without interest, particularly by reason of the science and skill displayed by the Commanding Generals, and the indomitable energy manifested by the men composing both armies. Within five days, these two formidable bodies have traversed a distance of between seventy and eighty mile.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 20.  Gov. Seymour issued a proclamation in response to that of the president calling for troops.  Gen. George H. Thomas assumed command of the Army of the Cumberland.  ST. LOUIS, Tuesday, Oct. 20. Little Rock advices to the 14th, state that the rebel army is scattered in every direction, and an extraordinary revival of Union sentiment has taken place among the people. Over one thousand men joined the Federal army at Little Rock, and the people were coming in daily and taking the oath of allegiance. The official report of the capture of the Confederate steamers on the Red River will not differ materially from the accounts already telegraphed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 19.  Gen. Rosecrans relinquished his command of the Army of the Cumberland to-day.   BUFFALO, Oct. 19. -- The schr. S.E. Hudson, with wheat from Milwaukee for this port, collided yesterday morning with the propeller Eclipse 42 miles above Buffalo, sinking the schooner and drowning one man. The vessel and cargo a total loss. The propeller not damaged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 18.  Gen Grant has assumed command of the Departments of the Ohio, Cumberland, and Tennessee.  Charlestown, Virginia, has been attacked by the rebels.  Secretary of War Stanton has arrived in Louisville, Kentucky.  CAIRO, Sunday, Oct. 18. The Memphis Bulletin, of the 16th, has information from a Union refugee, just escaped from the bloodhounds of the rebel conscriptors in Mississippi, that JOE. JOHNSTON's force, with the exception of one division, had been sent to reinforce BRAGG, and that there were not over 10,000 rebel troops in Mississippi. Gen. LORING was at Canton on the 8th, with 5,000 infantry. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 17.  A spirited engagement occurred at Manassas Junction this morning.  The president has called for 300,000 volunteers to be raised before the 5th of January, stating that a draft would then take place for any deficiency in the quotas of the States existing at that time.  NEW-ORLEANS, Friday, Oct. 9, 1863. Upon the heels of the conscription order, comes out Brig.-Gen. SHEPLEY's notification to the taxpayers, by which, on a certain day, an alphabetical list of all the delinquent tax-payers in New-Orleans is to be published, and after a certain time all property of the delinquents is to be seized and sold. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 16.  Gen. Grant has been ordered to the command of the Departments of the Ohio, the Cumberland, and the Tennessee.  There has been a rebel raid into Brownsville, Missouri. ST. LOUIS, MO., Monday, Oct. 12. SHELBY's and COFFEY's raiders left the Pacific Railroad Saturday, moved north and reached Booneville yesterday morning. They burned no railroad property at Tipton, as previously reported, but plundered the town of a large amount of money. The citizens of Warfield, Greenfield, and other towns though which the rebels passed, suffered in a like manner. The Federal troops from several directions are closing in on them.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 15.  ST. LOUIS, Saturday, Oct. 10. Telegraphic communication was interrupted about thirty miles west of Jefferson City last night, by rebel raiders having struck the Pacific Railroad at that point. They are marching eastward, and accounts of this morning place them five miles east of Tipton. The fortifications of Sedalia have been strengthened with baled hay, and every preparation has been made for the defense of that post. It is not known yet whether the rebels have done any damage to the Pacific Railroad. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 14.  A battle has occurred at Broad River or Bristoe Station, Virginia.   ST. LOUIS, Saturday, Oct. 10. The Democrat's (Leavenworth) special gives the particulars of the attack on Gen. BLUNT and his escort below Fort Scott. He was attacked by 300 rebels in Federal uniform, near the encampment of Lieut. POND. His escort broke, and out of 100 men, seventy-eight were killed -- all shot through the head, evidently after they were captured. Maj. CURTIS, son of Gen. CURTIS, was thrown from his horse, and was found with a bullet-hole through his head.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 13.  Mr. Vallandigham has been defeated as the Copperhead candidate for the Governor of Ohio.  Pennsylvania Governor Curtin has been reelected.  LOUISVILLE, Friday, Oct. 9. Gen. CROOK, commanding a brigade of cavalry twelve miles beyond Franklin, yesterday afternoon, came up with a portion of WHARTON'S rebel cavalry. Sharp fighting ensued. the result of which was 125 rebels killed and wounded, 300 taken prisoners, and four pieces of cannon captured. The rebels are in full retreat, and our forces are pursuing. No casualties to the Federals are reported. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 12.  The rebels have been driven from Brandy Station, Virginia.  NEW YORK, October 12.  A series of robberies have been committed on the Hudson River Railroad. One of the victims is a Mr. LANDON, who testifies that on Wednesday night last, he left this City on an Express train of the Hudson River Railroad, bound for Montreal.  While approaching Yonkers, two ruffians entered the car, dragged LANDON therefrom and threw him into Spuyten Duyvil Creek. The injuries he received, together with the cold bath, rendered him insensible for a time. When he recovered he  found that his pocket-book, containing over  SX 800 in money, was missing.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 11.   The Army of the Potomac has reportedly withdrawn to the north side of the Rappahannock River.  There has been an attack on the Memphis and Charleston Railroad, near Germantown.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, Oct. 10. The Republican Extra says Government has received dispatches dated Chattanooga, Oct. 9, and from officers on duty at ROSECRANS' headquarters. also official dispatches from Nashville, all containing reports most encouraging for the National cause. The forces under Gen. MITCHELL overtook the rebel cavalry on the 6th inst. below Shelbyville, and a battle immediately ensued, resulting in a complete rout of the enemy.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 10.  A sharp fight occurred to-day with the rebel Stuart's cavalry at Robertson's River.  There has been a skirmish between the rebels and Gen. Burnside's forces at Blue Springs, Tennessee.  Gen. ROSECRANS' headquarters, October 6.  QN Not a man was injured by the rebel batteries yesterday. Our men are not annoyed by the long range firing in the least, and go about their work the same as ever. The negro boys continued to play marbles while the bombardment was going on, which is some evidence that a very extensive alarm did not exist.   RICHMOND, October 10.  President Jefferson Davis reviewed the rebel army before Chattanooga to-day.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 9.  Gen. BANKS remains in New-Orleans. As a line of telegraph is laid down as the Union army advances, the Commanding General of the Department will have rapid communication with the army in the field. To enable civilians of Ohio employed in divisions of the army to come home to vote, the Governor has ordered State agents at all points to issue half-fare tickets. It is estimated that fully 3,000 voters will thus be added to the poll. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 8.  The rebel rams in the Mersey have reportedly been placed under the supervision of English officials.   NASHVILLE, Wednesday, Oct. 7. Up to a late hour this evening information from Chattanooga at Murfreesboro did not tell of a general engagement. The two armies still remain in front of each other, fortifying. Irregular firing was of constant occurrence. There were some movements being made on the part the enemy that seemed odd and mysterious, but not positively threatening.  Neither railroad nor telegraph communication is open to Stevenson, Ala., from Nashville. but the news brought is not depressing.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 7.  MAILS FOR THE BLOCKADING FLEET. -- The United States transport Massachusetts will sail in a few days from the Philadelphia Navy-yard for the South Atlantic Blockading Squadron. Letters, papers and parcels, properly directed to the officers and crew, will be cheerfully forwarded if sent to the Philadelphia Navy-Yard before the departure of the vessel. There are some 30 vessels attached to the fleet now, the officers and crews of which anxiously expect news and newspapers from their friends at the North. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 6.  The frigate Ironsides was attacked yesterday by a rebel vessel and torpedo in Charleston Harbor, in the night.  An engagement has reportedly occurred at Blue Springs, Tennessee.  CHARLESTON, Thursday, Oct. 1. The firing during to-day has been heavier than for several weeks past. The enemy has been steadily pounding at the ruins of Sumter from his old batteries on Morris Island, beyond Wagner. His fire was chiefly at Sumter, but he also shelled Fort Johnson. Our batteries and Fort Moultrie replied with a brisk and steady fire. All quiet to-night.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Monday October 5.  The railroad bridge south of Murfreesboro, Tennessee, has reportedly been destroyed by rebels.   Rebel batteries have opened on Gen. Rosecrans' forces at Chattanooga.  A letter from Dalton,. Ga., Sept. 26, published in the Richmond Dispatch on Saturday, says:  QN The over-sanguine multitude will be somewhat disappointed to know that the chances of Gen. BRAGG taking Gen. ROSECRANS' army is no easy job. Although his losses have been heavy, he yet has a very formidable army. QN  The two armies were still confronting each other at last accounts at Chattanooga. ROSECRANS, it is said, has established three lines in front of the town.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 4.   The frigate Ironsides was attacked yesterday by a rebel vessel and torpedo in Charleston Harbor, in the night.  NASHVILLE, Tenn., Sunday, Oct. 4. An explosion occurred near Bridgeport. A train of twenty army wagons laded with ammunition had camped near the city for the night. Two negroes quarrelled, one of whom accidentally threw a flame among the ammunition, causing it to explode and communicate to the other ammunition. Immediately after wagon after wagon caught fire, the teamsters and their attendants leaping for their lives.  Nine or ten are killed and double that wounded. The fire finally reached the magazine, exploding it.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 3.  The president to-day issued a proclamation appointing November 26 as Thanksgiving Day.  McMinnville, Tennessee, has been attacked by rebels.  ST. JOHNS, N.F., Thursday, Oct. 1. The heavy rains of last week occasioned a terrible freshet in the rivers on this island, which has done so much damage to the telegraph wires that they could not be worked for eight days.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, October 2.  There has reportedly been a success cavalry engagement at Anderson's Cross-roads, Kentucky.  The crews of the gunboats Reliance and Satellite, captured on the Rappahannock, the boat's crew from the Wabash, taken in Charleston Harbor, and the boat's crew of the Niphon, captured at New Inlet, N.C., have arrived here as paroled prisoners. They number in all about sixty. Accompanying them is a deserter from the Richmond City Battalion, named CHARLES HUTCHINS, formerly of Brooklyn, N.Y. He says that there are from 10,000 to 11,000 rebel troops in the neighborhood of Richmond.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, October 1.  To-day there was a reception for the officers of the Russian fleet by the military and civil authorities of New York.   LOUISVILLE, Saturday, Sept. 26. Gen. BURNSIDE was at Knoxville yesterday. Military authorities here say that BURNSIDE did not know of the impending battle between ROSECRANS and BRAGG, and could not have reinforced ROSECRANS if he had. The battle had been long concluded before the news reached BURNSIDE.  The rebel telegraph line from the Gap to Morristown is not in order, but there is telegraphic communication between Knoxville and Morristown.</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
