<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 30.  Rebel report of operations on the Charleston and Savannah Telegraph wires.  The pursuit of Yankee spies went to the Combahee Swamp.  The operator, a redheaded Yankee, was found while stuck up to his middle in the mud, unable to extricate himself. The remaining two negroes with the telegraphic instrument, made their escape in a flatboat. The Yankee operator said that he had established his connection with our telegraphic line only a few hours before, and had only obtained a few unimportant messages.  As the party were well provided with submarine wire, they intended to establish telegraphic communication between our line and Yankee headquarters.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 29.  An engagement has reportedly occurred at Morganzia, Louisiana.  OPERATIONS ON THE CHARLESTON AND SAVANNAH TELEGRAPH WIRES From the Savannah newspaper, Sept. 14.   A railroad overseer at Green Pond discovered a wire leading from the Charleston and Savannah railroad to the woods.  A party of Yankees was found with an instrument arranged so as to enable them to take off the dispatches. The Yankees comprised three whites and three negroes bearing instruments, submarine wire, and other implements.  Three of the party were captured, a Chaplain, a First Lieutenant and a negro, all of the 54th Mass. negro regiment. The pursuit went to the Combahee Swamp.  The operator, a redheaded Yankee, was found while stuck up to his middle in the mud, and unable to extricate himself. The remaining two negroes with the telegraphic instrument, made their escape in a flatboat but at last accounts our men with their dogs were in pursuit, with a good prospect of overtaking them. The Yankee operator said that he had established his connection with our telegraphic line only a few hours before, and had only obtained a few unimportant messages.  As the party were well provided with submarine wire, it was probably their intention to establish telegraphic communication between our line and the Yankee headquarters. THE CAPTURED TELEGRAPHERS. From the Savannah Republican, Sept. 16. The Yankee telegraph operator, and those taken prisoners with him, were taken before Gen. WALKER yesterday and examined. The prisoner states that a telegraph line is in operation along the coast, between Tybee and Morris Island.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 28.  The Army of the Columbia was reviewed to-day by Gen. Cortez.  U.S. SANITARY COMMISSION, No. 823 BROADWAY, NEW-YORK, Sept. 25, 1863.  To the Editor of the New-York Times: Dr. J.S. NEWBERRY, our Secretary of the Western Department, telegraphs us that twenty additional agents of the Sanitary Commission have gone to Chattanooga. that stores are going forward in large quantities, and that everything possible is doing to alleviate the sufferings of our wounded. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 27.  Gen. ROSECRANS telegraphs to the War Department that he cannot be dislodged from his present position, and the inference is that he will act strictly on the defensive, at least for some time to come.  Gen. ROSECRANS, in his official dispatches, charges the loss of the late battle to Gen. MCCOOK's disobedience of orders, in failing to occupy an important position that had been assigned to him. Rossville, to which the army of Gen. ROSECRANS retreated after the battles of the 19th and 20th, is a small post village, lying directly on the line separating Tennessee and Georgia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 26.  TEN MILES SOUTH OF CHATTANOOGA, Via RINGGOLD, Sept. 21. To Gen. Cooper: The enemy retreated on Chattanooga last night, leaving his dead and wounded in our hands. His loss is very large in men, artillery, small arms and colors. Ours is heavy, but not fully ascertained. The victory is complete, and our cavalry are pursuing. With the blessing of God, our troops have accomplished great result against largely superior numbers. We have to mourn the loss of many gallant men and officers. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 25.   Mr. CYRUS W. FIELD is among the passengers by the China. Prior to Mr. FIELD's departure from England everything had been put in train to secure the laying of the Atlantic Telegraph Cable between Ireland and Newfoundland during the Summer of 1864. Messrs. GLASS, ELLIOT  ES  Co., as already stated, had contracted to carry out the work, and had commenced the manufacture of the cable. They not only undertake to make the cable, but also to successfully lay it, thus showing implicit confidence in the success of the undertaking.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 24.  By proclamation of the president, Alexandria, Virginia, was opened to trade to-day.  NEW YORK, Sept. 24.  We are now enabled, by telegraphic reports, to obtain a clearer idea of the action fought on Saturday and Sunday last in Northwestern Georgia. The battle was neither a  QN crushing defeat QN  nor a  QN magnificent victory QN  for the army of Gen. ROSECRANS, or for the army of the rebels. After two days of very severe fighting and of various fortune, Gen. ROSECRANS still held his ground, but his prospects, his losses and the necessities of the situation were such, that on Sunday night he ordered his army to fall back to Chattanooga.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 23. Shortly after noon yesterday, a dispatch was received here from an officer in command at Chattanooga, speaking in most encouraging terms of the general result of the actions of Saturday and Sunday last, wherein, according to his representations, the Union army achieved a substantial success instead of being beaten -- the enemy being more damaged in killed, wounded, etc.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 22.  Gallant cavalry action occurred near Madison Court-House, Virginia.  A skirmish has reportedly occurred near Rockville, Maryland.  LOUISVILLE, Monday, Sept. 21 -- 12:45 A.M. Our army under Gen. ROSECRANS has been badly beaten, and compelled to retreat to Chattanooga, by BRAGG, with heavy reinforcements from LEE, BEAUREGARD and JOE JOHNSTON. RUMORS. LOUISVILLE, Sunday, Sept. 20. All kinds of exciting rumors are prevalent here, some of them quite adverse to ROSECRANS' army. The military authorities have the telegraph line, and there is very little prospect of getting anything through to-night. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 21.  Gen. Thomas has reportedly repelled the assault of the rebels on his corps at Rossville.  A great battle at Chickamauga has concluded.  Our forces have fallen back to Chattanooga after a gallant fight by Gen. Thomas' corps.  The battle commenced on the Chickamauga Creek and was waged from that point to Chattanooga.  Gen. Thomas' corps displayed great gallantry, and by its bravery saved the army from great disaster.  The rebels acknowledged very heavy loss in officers and men.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 20.  The great battle at Chickamauga, Georgia, continued to-day.  Union forces attacked at Zollicoffer, Tennessee.  PARIS, Friday, Sept. 4, 1863. A most important change has taken place in European affairs. the Emperor NAPOLEON has turned a summerset, and now lies in the dust at the feet of Prince GORTSCHAKOFF. His position of European dictator is at an end, and hereafter he will have enough to do to take care of himself. For the moment he is practically isolated and powerless to do harm. He is to-day the laughingstock of European diplomacy.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 19.  A great battle commenced to-day at Chickamauga, Georgia.  Our army was attacked in large force by the rebels under Gen. Bragg, who had been reinforced by Gen. Longstreet's corps from Virginia.  Rebels in the Indian Country have been defeated.  LONDON, Sept. 5 Via HALIFAX, Sept. 15. To the Associated Press of New York. At a meeting of the Directors of the Atlantic Telegraph Company, the tender of Messrs. GLASS, ELLIOTT  ES  Co. to manufacture and lay down in the Summer of next year a good submarine telegraph cable between Ireland and Newfoundland was unanimously accepted. (Signed.) CYRUS W. FIELD. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 18.   FUGITIVES RECAPTURED BY THEIR MASTERS. On Sunday last thirty slaves belonging in Anne Arundel and Calvert counties, Maryland, attempted to escape through Prince George county to this city. They encountered the citizen's patrol of Prince George county, who tried to stop them, but they resisted, when the negro catchers fired upon them wounding five. Their owners coming up aided in capturing most of the fugitives. One slave received a load of fine shot in his face, totally destroying his sight.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 17.   Gen. FOSTER telegraphs from Fortress Monroe that the main body of the rebel army is at Richmond, where LEE's headquarters now are, and that there is no force of any consequence in Gen. MEADE's front. Gen. PLEASANTON will probably ascertain the exact position of the rebel army in a day or two. A train of cars ran through to Culpepper from Washington, to-day, with supplies for our troops.   The rebels, yesterday morning, made an attempt to recross the Rapidan, which was prevented by our artillery and cavalry. The rebels advanced in three columns, with artillery, toward the river. and being met by our troops on this side, soon fell back. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 16.  A skirmish occurred to-day at Raccoon Ford on the Rapidan river.  QUEENSTOWN, Sunday, Sept. 6 [BY TELEGRAPH.] LONDON, Sunday. Sept. 6. The Globe's Paris correspondent says that M. CHEVALIER's pamphlet on Mexican affairs heralds most unmistakably a prompt if not immediate recognition of the Southern Confederacy by the Emperor NAPOLEON. The Pays denies the official character of the pamphlet. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 15.  A proclamation has been made by the President, suspending the writ of habeas corpus in certain cases.  Gen. Gillmore has issued an order congratulating his troops on their success in Charleston Harbor.  From the returns brought by telegraph of the State election in Maine, held yesterday, there seems to be no doubt that the Union ticket has been overwhelmingly successful. This insures the election of SAMUEL CORNY for Governor over BRADBURY, the Democratic candidate. The Republican gains in Portland, heretofore a strong Democratic city, are very large.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 14.  Yesterday, Gen. Rosecrans' army has been attacked at Bird's Gap.  Richmond papers of the 5th contain the proceedings of a Convention of some of the leading Secessionists of Mississippi, which called of JEFF DAVIS to summon out and arm for the rebellion one hundred thousand negroes. EXCHANGE OF PRISONERS. The President was interrogated to-day upon the subject of the exchange of prisoners, by the father of a New-York officer of one of the colored regiments, who is a prisoner in Richmond, Mr. LINCOLN said he would do all in his power to effect the release of these officers, and all others now prisoners.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 13.  There has been a brilliant cavalry fight at Culpepper, Virginia.  GALWAY, Tuesday, Sept. 1. The Polish insurrection is still raging. Telegraphic advices report a great victory at Kanow (on which side is not stated.) The Richmond Government had made a pressing appeal to the Spanish Government to obtain recognition of the Confederate States, offering to guarantee to Spain the possession of Cuba and Porto Rico. The Spanish Government declined.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 12.  Rebel Gen. Imboden's troops have attacked a small force of our troops at Moorefield, wounding 15 and capturing about 150.  ST. JOHNS, N.F., Tuesday, Sept. 8. The steamer Adriatic, from Liverpool, via Galway, on the 1st inst., passed Cape Race to-day, and was boarded by the news yacht of the Associated Press, and a Summary of news obtained.  CHATTANOOGA, Sunday, Sept. 6.  The enemy is quite active above and below the town. but there are no further indications of an attack.  Two privates, four regulars and one of ROSECRANS' telegraph operators were captured yesterday near Running Waters bridge.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, September 11.   The first vessel of the Russian fleet has arrived at New York.  Rebel dispatches from Charleston bring us advices to the morning of the 6th inst. It is stated this after a bombardment of 52 hours a part of our forces landed on Cummings' Point and attacked Battery Gregg, but were repulsed. Dispatches from Chattanooga to the 5th inform us that no battle had been fought there up to that date. It appears by a dispatch which we find in the Western papers, that Gen. BLUNT's recent operations in the Indian Territory have been much more important than we were led to suppose from the telegraphic reports which have reached us.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 10.  Little Rock, Arkansas, is now occupied by our forces.  The War with Japan.  The news from Japan fully prepared our readers for the announcement which comes to us this morning by the Pacific telegraph that war has broken out with that country. The quarrel which has led to hostilities is exclusively an English one, yet it seems to have been an American vessel which received the first hostile shot from the Japanese, and an American man-of-war which opened active of offensive operations. and if they were English troops who fought the first land fight, they were American sailors who achieved the first naval victory.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 9.  Gen. Crittenden has reportedly taken possession of Chattanooga, TN.  Cumberland Gap has been taken by our army.  The bombardment of Fort Moultrie is continuing.  A skirmish at Telford, East Tennessee, is underway.  ST. LOUIS, Sunday, Sept. 6. Gen. SCHOFIELD telegraphs to Lieut.-Gov. HALL, from Kansas City, that there will be an invasion of Missouri by the people of Kansas.  FORTRESS MONROE, Wednesday, Sept. 9. The steamship Daniel Webster has arrived here from City Point, Va., and brings rebel reports that Morris Island has been evacuated by the Confederates, and that our forces hold possession of the entire Island.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 8.  Union forces at Bath, Virginia, were to-day attacked by rebels.  An unsuccessful naval assault has occurred on Fort Sumter.  Fort Moultrie was bombarded and one of its magazines exploded.  An attack occurred on rebel fortifications at Sabine Pass, Texas, but was unsuccessful.  JOHNSTON, NEW YORK, Sunday, Sept. 6. The Galway steamer Hibernian, which leaves Tuesday morning next, will call at St. Johns, N.F., landing and receiving mails, and will convey all later news or commercial dispatches that may be telegraphed to that point for Europe. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 7.  Gen. Gilmore took possession of Fort Wagner and Battery Gregg in the morning.  Captured are 36 artillery pieces and a large amount of ammunition.  NEW YORK, September 6.  A BOATMAN CHARGED WITH MURDER -- At a late hour on Friday night, a telegraphic dispatch was received by Inspector LEONARD, at Police Headquarters, from Mr. W.R. STEVENS, a Justice of the Peace residing in Frankfort, Herkimer County, this State, requesting him to cause the arrest of LUMAN WIDE-RICK, a boatman, who is charged with having murdered a colored man named MOSES BLISS.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 6.  The rebels have reportedly evacuated Forts Wagner and Gregg in Charleston Harbor under cover of the night darkness.  TROY, N.Y., Friday, Sept. 4. The draft in this city began at 9 o'clock this morning, and terminated of 3 o'clock this afternoon. The proceedings were orderly, but great interest was felt in the revolutions of the wheel, and the office of Provost-Marshal HUGHES was crowded throughout the day with those who wished to find out whether they had drawn  QN prizes QN  or not. Only a small military force was on hand, although two regiments are in the city.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 5.  There has been furious bombardment of Forts Wagner and Gregg in Charleston harbor.   BRIDGEPORT, Tenn., Friday, Sept. 4. Gen. BURNSIDE telegraphs that he took Kingston on the 2d inst. Part of Gen, MINTRY'S brigade, of this array, went in immediately. Gen. BURNSIDE says he met with little serious opposition. All Eastern Tennessee except the Chattanooga region has been evacuated and is free. Everything is working splendidly both in this army and in BURNSIDE'S. The great obstacles of the region -- the Lookout Mountains -- will be surmounted in a day or two.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 4.  An expedition has reportedly left New-Orleans today for Texas under Gen. Franklin.  RICHMOND, September 4.  To-day a bread riot occurred in Mobile, Alabama.  SAN FRANCISCO, Wednesday, Sept. 2. No trade doing to-day. The stores and shops are generally closed, the citizens all attending the election. The vote of the city up to 4 P.M. is unprecedently large. The majority for the Union State ticket it is estimated will be about 7,000. Telegraphic returns from Sacramento, Nevada, Stockton, San Jose and Marysville counties up to noon, estimate a majority in those precincts for the Union State ticket of nearly two to one.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 3.  From HEADQUARTERS ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, SATURDAY, Aug. 29, 1863. The dull monotony of this Summer camp life has been agreeably broken within the past few days by the occurrence of one or two of those pleasant occasions which are not only agreeable in themselves, but serve to bind anew and with still stronger ties the affections of the soldiers to their leaders. The first occurred on Wednesday at Warrenton, when an elegant horse, sword, and set of equipments were presented to Gen. SEDGWICK, by the officers of his old command, the Second division of the Second Army Corps. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 2.  From CINCINATTI, Saturday, Aug. 29. Late information from Vicksburgh confirms the death of Gen. PEMBERTON. He was shot by Texan soldiers.  A Union meeting was recently held at Pelham, Greenbriar county, Tenn. Resolutions were passed expressive of a desire to return to the Union, repudiating the act of secession passed in 1861. Gen. GRANT was tendered the hospitalities of Memphis on Wednesday last. There was 600 Illinois troops on the steamer Courier when she collided with the Des Arc. Fifty thousand rounds of ammunition and all the guns and knapsacks and baggage of the soldiers were lost.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, September 1.  To-day there was a fierce artillery fight at Port Royal, Virginia.  Knoxville, Tennessee, has been captured by Gen. Foster of Burnside's army.  Fort Smith, Arkansas, is now occupied by our forces.  VICKSBURGH, Miss., Thursday, Aug. 20, 1863. Gen. GRANT and Gen. THOMAS left yesterday for Memphis, and it is the intention of the former to visit Columbus also. and perhaps Cairo.  It would not be at all surprising if the telegraph should get hold of this unimportant fact, and find therein confirmation of the canard that he had been called to the command of the Army of the Potomac.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 31.  Fort Moultrie, Charleston harbor, was attacked to-day.  Rear-Admiral PORTER forwards the report of Lieut. BACHE, relative to the White River expedition. He first stopped at Des Arc, on the White River, and burnt Confederate stores, destroyed the telegraph wires, etc., and then sent the Cricket after the steamers Tom Gregg and Kaskaskia, which he had reason to believe were hid up the river, while he and the Marmora proceeded to Augusta, thirty miles further. There he obtained valuable information of the enemy, namely: that the grand Southern army was concentrating at Brownsville, to make their line of defence on the Bayou Meto.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 30.   The Army of the Cumberland has crossed the Tennessee River.  A dispatch received from Fortress Monroe yesterday, announced the reception of news there that Forts Sumter and Wagner were occupied by our forces on Monday last, the 24th. To show that the news is unreliable, it is only necessary to refer to the fact that the Arago, whose advices we published yesterday, did not leave Charleston bar until the 25th -- the day after its alleged occupation -- at which time the rebels still had possession. We also have this morning an official dispatch from Gen. GILLMORE, dated the 24th, announcing the practical demolition of Sumter.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 29.  From CHARLESTON, Tuesday, Aug. 18. All day yesterday the bombardment was more furious than on any day. The Ironsides, six monitors and six gunboats, with all the enemy's land batteries, opened on battery Wagner at daybreak, throwing twenty shells per minute at our works. This continued until 11 o'clock, when the fleet and land batteries turned their attention to Fort Sumter. The Ironsides and six monitors approached within three-quarters of a mile of Fort Sumter, and battered vigorously against the south face of the fort. Sumter replied vigorously from her barbette guns. The contest lasted about three hours.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 28.  The rebels have driven across Bayou Metairie Bridge, Arkansas, with considerable loss.  MORRIS ISLAND, S.C., Friday, Aug. 21, 1863. The orders issued by Gen. GILLMORE Sunday night, for the artillery commanders to open their batteries on the rebel works at daybreak Monday morning, did not, in consequence of the advanced state of our siege operations, create any undue surprise. News of attack was circulated with remarkable rapidity through the camp, and upon the countenances of the soldiers could be traced evidences of satisfaction, if not actual delight, at the prospect of being relieved of the monotonous life.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 27.  From Richmond.  Rebel John B. Floyd died to-day.  The Sentinel announces that no paper would be issued from its establishment on the following day, in consequence of JEFF. DAVIS' Fast occurring on Friday. Brig.-Gen. ROGER A. PRYOR, commonly known as Bowie-knife PRYOR, has tendered his resignation to the rebel War Department, and it has been accepted. An accident occurred recently near Fort Deposit, on the Alabama and Florida road. A brake got under one of the cars, throwing it off, along with seven other cars, by which three soldiers of a South Carolina regiment were killed and thirty wounded.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 26.  An expedition has left Williamsburgh, Virginia, for Bottom's Bridge, Virginia.  There has been an attack on the rebel rifle pits near Fort Wagner.  JACKSON, MISS., Tuesday, August 18. The Federal cavalry from Yazoo City have reached Durot Station, on the Mississippi Railroad, where they captured a train and cut the telegraph wires. Serious destruction on the railroad northward is apprehended. The Yankees are carrying two engines and trains northward from Vaden. and a heavy raid is coming southward from the Charleston Railroad. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 25.  DESERTIONS FROM LEE'S ARMY.  LEE's army is daily decreasing in strength -- the number of desertions from it outnumbering the conscripts daily joining it. At no previous period of the war has there been so great a disposition manifested to desert from it.   Deserters now number now four or five times as many as ever before, and by far the greater portion of them are natives. They unite in declaring that nine-tenths of those who are now deserting LEE make for their respective homes, instead of coming this way. They also say that the feeling that the rebel cause is lost is universal in the rebel army of Virginia.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 24.  Charleston, South Carolina, was again shelled by Gen. Gillmore to-day.  SARATOGA, New York, Friday, Aug. 14, 1863. Correspondence of the New-York Times. There has been a very large assemblage of Christian patriots here to-day, at a Convention of the Christian Commission, which crowded the Baptist Church in this place morning and evening. President HOPKINS, of Williams College presided. After the reading of the Scriptures and prayer, Rev. GEO. J. MINGINS, a delegate of the Commission, made a most earnest and eloquent address. Some of the incidents which he related drew tears from unaccustomed eyes.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 23.  Fort Fisher, near Wilmington, North Carolina, has been bombarded by the frigate Minnesota.  Gen. SIBLEY telegraphs, under date of the 7th inst., that he has had three engagements with 2,200 Sioux warriors, in all of which the Indians were routed, and finally driven across the Missouri River, with the loss of all their subsistence, etc., and at least one hundred and fifty killed and wounded. The loss among the white troops was but seven killed and wounded. Gen. POPE considers Indian hostilities east of the Missouri as at an end, LITTLE CROW, the principal Chief, having been killed, and his son captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 22.  C.S. Gen. Beauregard has protested against the shelling of the City of Charleston.  ST. LOUIS, Saturday, Aug. 15. Col. CATHERWOOD, commanding Sixth Artillery Missouri State Militia, telegraphed Headquarters, as follows: PINSVILLE, MCDONALD CO., Mo., Saturday, Aug. 15. Col. COFFEE attacked me to-day, He is completely routed, with over 30 killed and wounded. We have a large number of prisoners, all his ammunition wagons, commissary stores, arms, horses, etc. We scattered all his command except 200 with himself. A force is following him closely. My horses are so worn down they cannot move farther until rested.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 21.   Lawrence, Kansas, has been pillaged and burned by the guerrillas.  Gen. Gillmore has demanded the surrender of Morris island and Fort Sumter, and threatened to shell Charleston in case of non-compliance with his demand.  Our batteries opened on Charleston, South Carolina, during the night.  The advance of the Army of the Cumberland has appeared before Chattanooga, Tennessee, and opened fire on the city.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 20.  Fort Sumter continues to be bombarded to-day.  Gen. Rosecrans' forces have reached the Tennessee River.  QUEBEC, Friday, Aug. 14. Parliament assembled yesterday and elected Hon. LEWIS WALBRIDGR Speaker by eight majority. To-day the Governor-General delivered the opening speech. He directed special attention to the Militia law, which, he said, required extensive amendment in order to make it effective.  The establishment of telegraphic and postal communication between Lake Superior and the Pacific coast was recommended as a matter for the consideration of the Parliament. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 19.  The bombardment of Fort Sumter is continuing to-day.  The draft in New York city has recommenced.  SAN FRANCISCO, Thursday, Aug. 13. As was anticipated yesterday, the reports of secession risings in Santa Clara and Saline Counties were untrue. Gen. WRIGHT has just received orders and funds from Washington, to construct new harbor defenses, for San Francisco. Batteries mounted by guns of large calibre are to be erected at Rincon Point, Rincon Hill, Buena Vista Island, and probably on Telegraph Hill.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 18.   Fort Sumter has continued to be bombarded to-day.  SAN FRANCISCO, Tuesday, Aug. 11. The State is full of rumors of a contemplated rising of the Secessionists, consequently there is an uneasy feeling in the public mind. On the 6th an affray occurred at Visalia, a small town in Tillare County, between the Secessionists and the soldiers stationed there. One of the latter was killed. Several of the former were wounded. Thirty-six shots were exchanged. Gen. WRIGHT, the military commander at San Francisco, telegraphed that all the spare arms among the soldiers at Visalia, be distributed among the loyal citizens.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 17.  There has been great destruction of rebel property at Grenada by our troops from Tennessee.  A grand attack on Fort Sumter has commenced by both the iron-clad fleet and land batteries.  The steamer City of Madison exploded to-day on the Mississippi River.  A reconnaissance in force by the rebel army has reportedly begun in Virginia.  The steamer Nita has been captured running out of Mobile, Alabama.  Gen. Dix made an address to the citizens of New York relative to the draft.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 16.  The steamer Alice Vivian has been captured running out of Mobile.  Gen. Rosecrans has commenced his advance across the Cumberland mountains.  Large numbers of contrabands continue to arrive within our lines, embracing men, women and children of all ages, and even colors, some having but very little African blood coursing their veins. Those that arrived yesterday state that there is no force of rebels this side of Little Washington. They also report that thousands of slaves are huddled together, and are now preparing to come within our lines. All of the young, athletic negroes express a great desire to enter the army as soldiers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 15.  The authorities of the City of New York have appropriated  SX 3,000,000 to pay for substitutes.  The following telegram released to-day.  HEADQUARTERS ARMY OF THE POTOMAC, WARRENTON, July 31, 1863.  QN OFFICIAL, QN  CHARLES E. PEASE, A.A.G. HEADQUARTERS CAVALRY CORPS, July 31, 1863. The Major-General Commanding directs that under this order every man shall take the oath of allegiance, or be arrested and sent in. You will have this order published to the officers under your command. By command of (Signed) Maj.-Gen. PLEASANTON. A.J. COHEN, A.A.G.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 14.  Commodore Morris died to-day.  The following telegram released to-day.  UNITED STATES MILITARY TELEGRAPH, BY TELEGRAPH FROM WASHINGTON, July 31, 1863 -- 4 P.M. To Maj.-Gen. Meade: Cant. MEANS reports that about (500) five hundred of the enemy's cavalry have appeared at Point of Rocks. The present time should be availed of to drive out every guerrilla and disloyal man between the Potomac, Rappahannock and Blue Ridge. (Signed,) H.W. HALLECK, General-in-Chief.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 13.  An expedition has left Lagrange, Tennessee, for Central Mississippi.  NEW YORK, August 12.  The Cunard mail steamer China, Capt. ANDERSON, which left Liverpool at 10 o'clock on the morning of the 1st, and Queenstown on the 2d of August, arrived here last evening. A telegraphic summary of her news has already been published, as received from Cape Race. Dispatches from Rio Janeiro, vid Lisbon, report that the American ships Talisman, bound from New-York for Shanghai, and the Comod, bound from Montevideo for New-York, had been captured by the Alabama. Their crews were landed at Rio. No further particulars are given.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 12.  Fort Sumter, Charleston harbor, has been battered by our shot.  The rebels opened on our works near Charleston with grape and canister.  BUFFALO, Monday, Aug. 10. The draft in this city was concluded to-day. It passed off quietly, though every necessary precaution was taken. Six employees of the telegraph office were drafted.   NEW YORK, Aug. 12.  The officers of the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad announced that that great thoroughfare is opened anew for freight and travel, through its entire length, from Baltimore to Wheeling. Over 18,000 ties, hundreds of tons of rail, and 30 miles of telegraph wire were taken away or destroyed by rebels.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 11.  A thousand conscripts a day are now arriving at the Army of the Potomac, and attaching themselves to the old regiments. They go forward in excellent spirits.  Substitutes are offering themselves at very cheap rates, both in Philadelphia and Washington, as well as at other points where drafting is going on. Prices range from one hundred to two hundred dollars, and cases are reported where persons voluntarily and freely offer themselves as substitutes for their drafted friends. A thousand conscripts a day, and the volume constantly increasing! The ranks of the army will soon be filled up at this rate. The shadowy regiments will soon be full-bodied.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 10.  From MORTON, Mississippi, July 25, 1863. GRANT has fallen back toward Vicksburgh. The evacuation is likely permanent, and West Mississippi will be left to the mercy of raiders.  The gathering of a heavy naval force at Pensacola would indicate an early attack on Mobile, but the difficulties in the way of GRANT's participation in it are very great. He will hardly attempt it by land from the river. Want of water, hot weather and sickness will deter him. It is more probable that, content with his exploits in the South for the present, he will merely hold the strategic points he has gained, and operate the balk of his army somewhere North.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 9.  BALTIMORE. Aug. 8 -- Arr. schr. Yorktown. Wyland New-York. Cld. brigs Harkaway, Wilson, Montevideo, Elisha Doane. Jones. Cardenas. Sarah Atlec, (Br..) Pictou, N.S.. schrs. White Cloud. Leavitt New-York via Wicomico River, Md.. June, Small, do. Via do. CHICAGO, Wednesday, Aug. 5, 1863. The National Teacher's Convention convened in this city.  The school-masters are indeed abroad, and the school-mistresses with them, in large and unexpected numbers. It would seem that New-England has heard that she was to be left out in the cold by a certain class of Western politicians, when they reconstruct the Union.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 8.  On the Day of National Thanksgiving, August 6, thousands of clergymen held forth from their pulpits.  In our Armies, stationed on the Potomac, on the Tennessee, on the Upper and Lower Mississippi, and on the headwaters of the Arkansas -- in our Navy, stationed all along the Atlantic and Gulf coasts, and on all the rivers of the South -- our soldiers and our sailors kept holiday, and acknowledged that not alone their own valor and endurance, but a higher Power had led them on to victory. In the City of San Francisco, as we learn by telegraph, there were national salutes and ringing of bells morning, noon and night.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 7.  President Lincoln has sent a reply to New York Gov. Seymour's letter of remonstrance against the draft, in which the president asserted that the draft should proceed.  HAVANA, Saturday, Aug. 1, 1863. The latest news from Mexico comes to us from St. Jago de Cuba, whither it was carried by the French mail steamer Florida. The most important subject is the confirmation of the proclamation of the Empire, and of Prince MAXIMILIAN as Emperor.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 6.   The ship Francis B. Cutting has been captured and bonded by the Florida.  To-day is National Thanksgiving Day.  The draft in four out of seven Wards in this city has been completed. It embraces 2,600 whites and 818 colored men. Amongst the drafted are three clergymen, as many members of the City Councils, and several telegraph operators. also, reporters, printers, lawyers and representatives of all classes of business. A party of drafted men attempted yesterday to escape from the city, but were apprehended as deserters. Judge-Advocate HOLT has given the opinion that Paymasters Clerks are not found in the list of exempted classes.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 5.   Adj.-Gen. THOMAS leaves to-morrow for the West, to organize more negro regiments. He will proceed directly to Memphis, and from that point to New-Orleans, organizing regiments all along the River. He will be gone three or four months, and has the same full powers as before.   NEWBERN, N.C, Saturday, July 25, 1863. A very successful cavalry raid was made a few days since by a detachment comprising twelve companies of the Third New-York cavalry, three companies of Mix's new cavalry, Companies A, B and C of the Twelfth New-York cavalry, with one company North Carolina Union Volunteers, Brig.-Gen. POTTER in command.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 4.  An engagement occurred to-day near Brandy Station, Virginia.  The steamer Ruth, with  SX 2,500,000 in government funds, burned to-day on the Mississippi River.  A reconnaissance of Fort Darling on the James River is completed.  MEMPHIS, August 1.  Gen. GRANT has perfected a complete system of mounted patrols between Vicksburgh and New-Orleans, which, with the gunboats, affords ample protection to vessels.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 3.  New York Gov. Seymour has indicted a letter to the President, remonstrating against the enforcement of the draft in New York because of unfair enrollment etc.  The telegraph brings from Memphis the statement  QN removal of the slaves from Mississippi into Alabama and Georgia has been carried to such an extent that the Governors of those States have issued proclamations forbidding their further introduction, and Gen. JOHNSTON's pickets have turned a large number back. QN  Most of these slaves have learned by this time that the war which is raging around them, and driving them from one place to another, has something to do with their freedom.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 2.  From PHILADELPHIA, Thursday, July 30. Three wards underwent the process of the draft to-day, the First, the Sixth and the Eleventh. As usual, everything passed off quietly. Among those who were so  QN fortunate QN  as to be honored with the draft to-day were three more telegraphers, making fifteen in all from the American Company, including JAMES MERRIHEW, Assistant Manager. JAMES J. REVILLE, of the Continental office, and WILLIAM CARLEY, clerk. It is proposed by these  QN lucky QN  telegraphers to apply for a separate organization, as a company for telegraphic duty.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, August 1.  A battle occurred to-day between the cavalry of the two armies near Culpepper, Virginia.  Jefferson Davis has appealed to the deserters from the rebel army to return, offering them pardon and amnesty.  NEW HAVEN, August 1.  There are about 200 drafted men and substitutes at Grapevine Point, the conscript camp near New-Haven. Saturday night, fifteen substitutes who had received their pay, attempted to run the guard and escape, but were fired upon. Most of them were driven back to the camp, but four or five escaped. One fellow, calling himself JOHN MCCARTEN, of Toronto, was hit and his arm shattered so that amputation was necessary.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 31.  There has been heavy bombarding of our works on Morris Island, Charleston harbor, from Fort Wagner.  To-day there was a successful attack on the rebels at Lancaster, Kentucky.  A reconnaissance mission has reportedly been made to Sperryville, Virginia.  PHILADELPHIA, Wednesday, July 29. The draft in the Fifth Ward of this city was completed to-day. Among those who have been so  QN lucky QN  as to he drawn are Mr. MORRIS HARDING, of the Philadelphia Inquirer, and five telegraph operators attached to the American and National lines.  BUFFALO, Wednesday, July 29. The draft at Lockport was completed yesterday.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 30.  President Lincoln has issued a proclamation to-day in regard to rebel treatment of colored troops.  The Cummings Point rebel battery at Charleston harbor has been bombarded.  Rebels were defeated to-day at Winchester, Kentucky.  A special correspondent telegraphs from the Army of the Potomac, under date of yesterday, that the army now occupies practically the same line that it did two months ago, and that the recent active movements will necessarily be followed by a period of comparative inaction. During the next month the cavalry is expected to do most of the fighting.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 29.  Rebels have been repulsed to-day at Paris, Kentucky.  PHILADELPHIA, July 28.  Jacob Forney, an engineer on the Pennsylvania Central Railroad, was killed on July 6 while in the discharge of his duties. When the train under his charge was near Coatesville, Chester County, deceased was in the act of looking back at his train from the window, when his head struck a telegraph pole, with such force as to crush it in a shocking manner.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 28.  Confederate States Senator and orator, William L. Yancey of Alabama, has died to-day.  The rebels have been defeated at Lexington, Tennessee.  FORTRESS MONROE, Tuesday, July 28. Flag-of-truce steamer New-York arrived from City Point last evening, in charge of Capt. MULFORD. She brings no prisoners. She brings Richmond papers to the 27th. The propeller United States arrived here this afternoon with 154 rebel prisoners, which were sent to Fort Norfolk. The steamer New-York left here at 2 o'clock P.M., for Annapolis.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 27.  Dispatches indicate that Gen. LEE's army is out of the Shenandoah Valley, and is again back on the upper waters of the Rappahannock, from which two months ago it set forth to capture Washington. The two corps of HILL and LONGSTREET reached Culpepper Court- house on Friday last, and the third corps, that of EWELL, has undoubtedly followed in their wake.  One report is that they passed through Chester Gap of the Blue Ridge, six miles west of Manassas Gap. but our own dispatch says their march was through Thornton's Gap, twenty miles south of Chester Gap, and from thence to Sperryville, and so on down to Culpepper Court-house.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 26.  The Hon. John J. Crittenden died to-day.  Rebel Morgan and the remainder of his band were captured to-day near New-Lisbon, Ohio.   WASHINGTON, July 22, 1863. To D. Bookstaver, Mayor, Syracuse, New York: Volunteers will be received on your quota up to time of draft, and all who have been mustered into the United States service up to that time must be credited on your quota by your Board of Enrollment I cannot tell when the draft will take place in your city. JAMES B. FRY, Provost-Marshal-General. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 25.  The steamer Merrimac has been captured running the blockade at Wilmington, North Carolina.   NEW-ORLEANS, La., Saturday, July 18, 1863. This city is suddenly galvanized into new life by the presence of a large body of officers who, for weeks past, plunged up to their necks in warlike duties before Port Hudson. The new military order issued by Gen. EMORY, compelling all officers to carry their side arms in the streets, gives the place a very martial appearance, and the clanking of spurs and sabers, which greets one at every turn, produces quite an impressive music.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 24.  Col. Toland has attacked the enemy at Wytheville, on the East Tennessee and Virginia Railroad, capturing two pieces of artillery, 700 muskets and 125 prisoners.  The following dispatches give the rebel version of affair in the vicinity of Jackson: JACKSON, Tuesday, July 7. Vicksburgh has fallen. It was surrendered on the morning of the 4th. the men being in a starving condition, completely worn out by excessive fatigue. By the terms of capitulation, the officers are allowed to retain their side-arms horses, and all their private property. They and the men are to be paroled immediately, and allowed to march out with all their colors.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 23.  To-day there was a sharp fight near Front Royal, Virginia.  REWARD FOR DESERTERS. WAR DEPARTMENT ADJUTANT-GENERAL's OFFICE WASHINGTON July 16,1863. GENERAL ORDERS No. 222. -- The reward of  SX 5, with transportation and reasonable expenses, for the arrest and delivery at the nearest military post or depot of any officer or private soldier fit for duty who may be found absent from his command without just cause, is hereby increased to  SX 10.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 22.  A railroad bridge that was 350 feet long, over the Tar River at Rocky Mount, North Carolina, has been destroyed by a cavalry expedition from Newbern.  They also destroyed a large amount of property.  Brashear City, Louisiana, has been recaptured by our troops.  A boy employed in carrying telegraphic messages was arrested, to-day, for opening them and conveying valuable information thus obtained to his brother, on LEE's Staff.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 21.  The only signs of the rebels in our immediate front is a party of forty of MOSEBY's guerrillas, who are pursuing their usual avocation of horse stealing in the vicinity of Occoquan Creek. Last night a band of guerillas came within two miles of Fort Ethan Allen, near the Chain Bridge, and stole twenty horses.  Eleven hundred rebel prisoners, captured at Williamsport, arrived here last night, and were consigned to the Old Capitol Prison. The recent battles at Gettysburgh have furnished evidence of the necessity of some such organization of an  QN Ambulance Corps, QN  as was sought to be attained in the bill defeated by Congress at the last session.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 20.  Gov. Seymour of New York has ordered the return of the state arms used against the rioters in New York city.  There has been a cavalry reconnaissance to Front Royal, Virginia.  A sharp fight has occurred with the rebel guerrilla Morgan, and large portions of his force have been captured at George's Creek.  An expedition of Union troops have destroyed railroad and other property at Rocky Mount, North Carolina. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 19.   The rebel Morgan made an unsuccessful attempt to cross the Ohio River.  More of his men were captured.  Two companies of rebels and an ammunition train have been captured at Jackson, Tennessee.  Major-Gen. HURLBUT telegraphs from Memphis, July 17, to the War Department, as follows:  QN The enemy's cavalry was sharply punished at Jackson, Tenn., by Col. HATCH, on the 13th. Then loss was two hundred in killed, wounded and prisoners, four hundred conscripts released, and about two hundred and fifty horses taken, with more than that number of arms. QN  
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 18.  Fort Wagner in Charleston harbor has been stormed.  Gen. Foster has arrived at Fort Monroe.  Gen. Lee's rear guard has departed Martinsburgh, Virginia.  Morgan's force has dispersed and a large number of his men have been captured.  There has been a fight with Morgan's men at Buffington, Ohio.  Admiral Porter has reported the complete success of the Red River expedition.  Fort Wagner in Charleston harbor has been bombed, the fort stormed, and our troops repulsed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 17.  The Seventh Regiment has arrived in New York.  Quiet is restored in this city. the draft riot is suppressed.  Gen. Brown is succeeded by Gen. Canby in command of the troops in New York. Archbishop Hughes has made a speech to the mob.  WASHINGTON, July 17.  A battle occurred to-day with the rebel Gen. Morgan at Berlin, Ohio.  Two expeditions, one up the Red River and one to Natches--have made large captures of arms, ammunition, and cattle.  NASHVILLE, Tenn., Friday, July 10. The guerrillas have again interrupted communication by rail between here and Louisville. Since Friday evening no train has reached us from the latter city.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 16.  Jefferson Davis has issued a proclamation immediately conscripting every able-bodied man between the ages of 18 and 45.  Gen. Blunt has crossed the Arkansas River.  Gen. Joe Johnston has evacuated Jackson, Mississippi, in the night.  The rebels have been routed in Indian Country.  There was a brisk engagement to-day on James Island, South Carolina.  Gen. Blunt is victorious over 5,000 rebels at Elk Creek.  Jackson, Mississippi, has been taken by our army.  NEW YORK, July 16.  The draft riot in New York is continuing.  Archbishop Hughes has invited the mob to visit him at his residence on the morrow. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 15.  The draft riot in this city is continuing.  The military is routed, more negroes are hung, and there is terrible excitement in New York and the neighborhoods.  Mayor Opdyke has made a proclamation.  A mob in Troy has destroyed the Times office and other property.  Gen. Dix has been ordered to New York and Gen. J. G. Foster to Fort Monroe.  WASHINGTON, July 15.  A proclamation of the President was issued to-day, appointing August 6 for a National Thanksgiving for our great victories.  C. L. Vallandigham has appeared at Niagara Falls, Canada, from his journey through the Southern states.  Jackson, Mississippi has been shelled by our forces. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 14.   The draft riot is continuing to-day in this city.  Business is suspended, negroes have been hung, Col. O'Brien has been killed, there is conflict between the mob and soldiers.  Gov. Seymour has made a proclamation and a speech to his friends.  Postmaster Wakeman's house is destroyed.   WASHINGTON, July 14.  A riot occurred to-day in Boston.  Gen. Meade's army is advancing.  Our cavalry is occupying Falling Waters, on the Potomac, and have captured a brigade of rebels.  Williamsport, Maryland, is occupied by our forces.  Admiral Lee has captured Fort Powhattan, on the James River.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, July 13.  A great draft riot has commenced in this city.  The drafting office in Third Avenue is destroyed, a negro hung, and public and private property is destroyed.  WASHINGTON, July 13.  Gen. Lee's army has escaped across the Potomac River in the night.  Gen. Meade has reconnoitered the rebel position and is reportedly making preparations for an attack.  There has been an engagement at Jackson. Yazoo City has been captured by our troops.  FREDERICK, Md., Tuesday, July 7.   The latest intelligence from the front places LEE'S headquarters at Hagerstown to-day. The prospect of another conflict ere crossing the river is not promising.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 12.  Our forces have entered Hagerstown, Maryland.  The rebels evacuated the town during the night.  Our forces have passed through South Mountain and have come up with the rebel army of Gen. R. E. Lee securely posted on the heights of March's Run.  WASHINGTON, Wednesday, July 8. A dispatch from Gen. GRANT to Gen. HALLECK, dated at Vicksburgh, at half-past 10 o'clock on the morning of the 4th of July, states that the rebels surrendered this morning, and that their troops were paroled as prisoners of war.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 11.  There has been a brilliant engagement on Morris Island in Charleston harbor.  All of the batteries have been evacuated by the rebels who are defending themselves in Fort Wagner.  A draft has commenced in New York City.  PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, July 7 -- 2 P.M. The State House bell is ringing a joyful pea over the capture of Vicksburgh. All the fire-bells in the city are also now ringing, by direction of the Mayor, sent through the police telegraph. PHILADELPHIA, Tuesday, July 7.  The newspaper offices are illuminated this evening. The Ledger building has stars placed along the entire front. The North American has the word  QN Victory. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 10.  Gen. Gillmore has commenced operations against the rebel batteries on Morris Island, Charleston harbor.  Gen. Strong has taken possession of several of the rebel works.  Martial law has been declared in Louisville, Kentucky.  An engagement has begun at Jackson, Mississippi and at Sharpsburgh, Maryland.  A skirmish has occurred near Funkstown, Maryland.   WASHINGTON, Tuesday, July 7. Officers arrived this evening from the flag of truce boat last sent to City Point, bring back rebel news, and files of Richmond papers to July 4. Profound ignorance was existing as to the whereabouts of LEE'S forces, and the progress of the great battle.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 9.  Port Hudson has been taken possession by the Union army.  Our cavalry have scored a victory under Gens. Buford and Kilpatrick at Boonsboro.  HARRISBURGH, Sunday, July 5. Surgeon-Gen. Hammond, Washington: Our people over the State are exceedingly anxious to render aid and assistance to the wounded at Gettysburgh. Will you say how many volunteer Surgeons I may send. You may be assured that our people will take the wounded to their houses, and render every assistance that the most careful nursing may demand, and that our public buildings can be used as hospitals to any extent.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 8.  To-day, Port Hudson surrendered with 7,000 prisoners and a large number of cannon and small arms, to Gen. Banks.  The rebel Gen. Morgan has crossed into Indiana and captured the town of Corydon.   Gen. Gillmore issued orders for an attack on Morris Island in Charleston harbor.  GETTYSBURGH, July 4. GENERAL ORDERS NO. 68. -- The Commanding General, in behalf the country, thanks the Army of the Potomac for the glorious result of the recent operations. Our enemy, superior in numbers, and flushed with the pride of a successful invasion, attempted to overcome or destroy this army but has now withdrawn from the contest.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 7.  A battle commenced to-day at Williamsport, Maryland.  The rebel Gen. Morgan's force currently appears to be at Bardstown, Kentucky.  Rebel Gen. Bragg's army is now retreating across the Tennessee River.  Gen. Meade is in pursuit of Gen. R. E. Lee.  TULLAHOMA, Saturday, July 4. The telegraph wires have been extended to this place.  TULLAHOMA, Monday, July 6 -- 3 A.M. Maj. Gen. THOMAS has succeeded in crossing the Elk River, with his corps and a division of cavalry, under Gen. STANLEY, and is in close pursuit of BRAGG's army, with every prospect of capturing their wagon train and rear guard.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 6.  Rebel Gen. Johnston has been defeated on the Big Black River.  His rear guard has been captured at Bolton.  The rebel army from Gettysburgh has arrived at Hagerstown, Maryland.  Rebel Gen. Stuart has been defeated by Gen. Buford at Hanover.  THURSDAY, July 2, 1863, 12 Meridian. The engagement yesterday was very sharp, and one of the bloodiest, for its duration, yet encountered by the Army of the Potomac. It was entirely between our Advance Guard, the First corps, supported subsequently by the Eleventh, and the combined forces of the rebel Generals HILL and EWELL.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 5.  At Gettysburgh, the day is occupied by Gen. Meade in succoring the wounded and burying the dead left on the field.  PHILADELPHIA, July 4.  A dispatch has been received here from Washington announcing that Vicksburgh had been captured. During the evening, however, it was ascertained that the story was false. The Government yesterday received dispatches from Gen. GRANT to the 27th, stating that the siege was progressing finely. Another attack was expected from JOHNSTON during this week, but in the meantime Vicksburgh was expected to surrender.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 4.  Vicksburgh, Mississippi, surrendered to-day to Gen. U. S. Grant.  Surrendered are 31,000 troops, 220 guns, and 70,000 small arms.  A Union victory also occurred to-day at Helena, Arkansas.  The retreat of the rebels from the battlefield at Gettysburg has commenced.  President Lincoln has issued a proclamation announcing a victory at Gettysburgh.  Gen. Meade has issued a congratulatory address to his army on the victory of Gettysburgh.  It is reported that Alexander Stevens, Vice President of the Confederate States, applied for permission to visit Washington as bearer of a letter from Jefferson Davis to President Lincoln.  His application was refused.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 3.  The battle at Gettysburg is continuing to-day.  There are heavy losses on both sides.  A great victory appears to be gained by the Union army and the rebels are compelled to retreat.  The rebel pontoon bridge over the Potomac near Williamsport, Maryland, has been destroyed.  A cavalry expedition from Newbern, North Carolina, has departed for the interior.  GETTYSBURGH, Thursday 4:30 P.M. Via BALTIMORE, Friday A.M. The day has been quiet up to the present moment. The enemy are now massing a heavy force on our left, and have just began the attack with artillery. The probability is that a severe battle will be fought before dark.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 2.  The battle at Gettysburgh is continuing to-day.  The rebels have attacked our forces in large numbers, but have been repulsed.  Gens. Weed and Zook were killed to-day and Gen. Sickles has been wounded.  The rebel Gen. Barksdale, of Mississippi, is killed.  Chambersburgh and Shippensburgh, Pennsylvania, have been evacuated by the rebels.  A skirmish occurred to-day near Bottom's Bridge, Virginia.  Tullahoma, Tennessee, is now occupied by our forces.   BALTIMORE, Thursday, July 2. The American learns from parties who left Gettysburgh at noon to-day that everything was progressing favorably for the ultimate success of our arms.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 01:00:00 -0500</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, July 1.  A battle has commenced to-day at Gettysburgh, Pennsylvania.  The First and Eleventh Corps have been significantly engaged.  Gen. Reynolds has been killed.  There are large losses on both sides.  A brilliant fight occurred at Carlisle between the rebel cavalry and artillery of Gen. Fitzhugh Lee, and our forces under the command of Gen. W. F. Smith.  PHILADELPHIA, Sunday, June 28. The report from Harrisburgh, at midnight of Saturday, that the rebels had arrived opposite Duncannon, at the junction of the Juniata and Susquehanna Rivers, is probably an error, as the telegraph line remains in order to Pittsburgh this (Sunday) morning. 
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
