<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 30.  The Battle of Charles City Cross Roads, or White Oak Swamp, near Richmond occurred to-day.  The rebels are still held at bay.  Losses are very heavy on both sides.  As of nightfall, McClellan's forces are around Malvern Hill.   Since a very early hour on Saturday morning Gen. MCCLELLAN has been deprived of his telegraphic communication with Washington. He abandoned its use several hours before the wires were cut, doubtless being fearful that the enemy might, by placing a magnet on the wires, read his orders. Direct communication is now being opened with him, however, by gunboats up the mouth of the Chickahominy.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 29.  Battle fought one and one-half miles from Savage's Station, near Richmond.  At dark, the rebels were repulsed, and forced to abandon their position.   Confederate forces are closely following and attacking McClellan's retreating columns.  The Union rear guard was constantly in action and withstood the repeated assaults. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 28.  The battles before Richmond are continuing, though quieter to-day.  Long lines of wagons moving towards the James River mark McClellan's retreat.  McClellan has reportedly sent a telegram to the President saying the battle is lost because his force is too small.  The evacuation of White House Landing is completed. MEMPHIS, June 28.  Near Vicksburg, Commodore Farragut's fleet moved upriver at 2 a.m. in an attempt to pass the defenses.  At 4 a.m., the air betwen the city and the river was full of flying shells and mortar bombs as the boats raced north.  All but three of the ships made the passage.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 27.  The Battle of Gaines Mills commenced to-day, near Richmond.  Stonewall Jackson and Ewell attempted to turn our right flank and were repulsed.  The entire right wing of our army crossed the Chickahominy in the night in perfect order.  Gen. Fremont has been relieved of the command of the Mountain Department.  MEMPHIS, June 27.  Shelling of Vicksburg commenced to-day.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 26.  Terrific fighting occurred before Richmond to-day.  The rebels attacked the Union right wing when they were engaged in changing base from the Pamunkey to the James Rivers.  Gen. Pope has been assigned to command the Army of Virginia.  MEMPHIS,  June 26.  The rebels destroyed their gunboats Van Dorn, Polk, and Livingston on the Yazoo River near Vicksburg.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 25.  To-day there was severe and successful fighting before Richmond.  A reconnoitering expedition left Newbern, N.C.  NEW ORLEANS, June 25.  Gen. Butler ordered the seizure of the property of the traitor Twiggs.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 24.  President Lincoln is at West Point, New York, to-day.  White House Landing was evacuated by Gen. McClellan's forces.  Gen. Hooker's division was attacked by the rebels who were repulsed at the point of the bayonet.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>LOUISVILLE, Monday, June 23. The Southwestern Telegraph line is now in operation from here to Memphis. CLEVELAND, Monday, June 23. The Pacific Telegraph line has been broken in several places, but the principal trouble is the high water in Green River, where the line has been carried away, and there are no present means of crossing to repair it. 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sunday, June 22.  It appears that the telegraphic communication between the White House and Gen. MCCLELLAN was not broken until near one o'clock on Saturday, and then the wire was cut at Dispatch Station, eleven miles out. Tunstall's Station, four miles out, was in our possession until four o'clock in the afternoon, at which hour the operator at White House heard a strange signal coming over the wire. On going to the instrument he was heralded with what the Federal soldiers call the rebel National salute --  QN I say, O you Yankee -- of --. QN  This was the signal given for the final evacuation, when a portion of the infantry forces immediately embarked.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 21.  Col. Ellet, of the Mississippi ram fleet, died to-day.  BUFFALO, Monday, June 23. FLOUR market quiet and steady. WHEAT dull. sales at 82c. for Milwaukee Club. CORN quiet. sales at 37 1E2c. for old. OATS quiet at 35 1E2c. WHISKY quiet and no sales, FREIGHTS steady. Imports -- 24,000 bbls. Flour, 117,000 bushels Wheat, 30,000 bushels Corn, 11,000 bushels Oats. Exports -- 4,000 bbls. Flour, 96,000 bushels Wheat, 84,000 bushels Corn, 19,000 bushels Oats.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, June 20.  Commodore Porter arrived off Vicksburgh with ten mortar-boats.  WASHINGTON, June 20.  The Free Territory act was signed by the President.  Holly Springs is now occupied by our forces.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, June 19.  The citizens of Richmond, we are glad to see, are awakening to a proper estimate of the shameful extortion practiced upon them in the various articles of food furnished the market, while, not thirty miles around the country, the very same articles for which they pay down a small fortune here daily, are selling at the most moderate of prices, and in abundance at that. It is plain that unless the authorities move in the matter of getting these supplies into the city there will be want in our midst before Midsummer. Railroad communication is cut on the east and north by the enemy, and monopolized on the south and west by the Confederate Government.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 18.  The Cumberland Gap is now occupied by Union Gen. George Morgan's force.   PHILADELPHIA, June 18 -- Arr. bark White Wing. Porto Cabello June 5. Left brig James C. Coale, from New-York for Cienfuegos to sail 6th. June 17, lat. 35 50, lon. 74 40, spoke brig Porto Plata, from Porto Plata for New-York. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>ST. LOUIS, June 17.  To-day there was a battle between our gunboats and rebel batteries at St. Charles, Arkansas, on the White River.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 16.  The Battle of James Island, S.C., occurred today.  Union forces were reportedly repulsed.  From the Richmond Whig, June 14. The brilliant operations of Gen. JACKSON in the Valley of the Shenandoah, crippling and dispersing the forces of MILROY and SCHENCK at McDowell, -- of BANKS at Front Royal and Winchester, -- of FREMONT at Cross Keys, and SHIELDS at Fort Republic, have had a wide-reaching and important bearing on the war. These several corps were to have been consolidated and brought across the Blue Ridge en route for Richmond. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 15.  Gen. Wool visited Harper's Ferry to-day.  Gen. J.E.B. Stuart reportedly arrived back in Richmond to-day.  The British Admiralty have granted to the Atlantic Telegraph Company the services of the ships and crews necessary for revising and extending the former surveys of the route along which the cable is in tended to be submerged. The route westward from the Irish coast, for a distance of some five hundred miles, will be sounded at distances of about a mile apart, the previous soundings having been some thirty miles asunder. A good map of the bottom may, in this manner, be obtained, and thus facilitate the operation of laying the cable. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 14.  CAPE RACE, Saturday, June 14. The steamship Bavaria from Southampton 4th, and the China from Liverpool and Queenstown 8th inst., passed this Point at 11 o'clock this morning, and were both boarded by the news yacht of the Associated Press. The steamship Jura, arrived on the 3d, and the Edinburg on the 4th inst. The general news contains no striking characteristics. The division of the French army left at Rome consists of three brigades, under Gen. MONTEBELLO. The Prussian Ambassador has arrived at Paris. The silk crop in France is represented as most satisfactory. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 13.  Union pickets were driven in from Old Church before Richmond.  The railroad behind McClellan's army, four miles from the White House, were cut by the rebel cavalry.  STAUNTON, June 13. -- FREMONT has certainly retreated below New-Market. His army is almost entirely Dutch. It persists of MITCHER's, BLENKER's, and other divisions. Others of the enemy admit a loss of 400 killed and 600 wounded in Sunday's fight. They also say that Gen. MCDOWELL has been arrested for disloyalty and went to Fort Lafayette! FREMONT's officers claim to have 2,000 men and 105 cannon.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW YORK, June 12.  The British Government, at the request of the Atlantic Telegraph Company, had ordered two steamers to be got ready for the purpose of making a further survey on both sides of the Atlantic. The United States Consul at Paris had issued a notice that no further application can be received from foreign officers for commissions in the Federal army. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>HALIFAX, Wednesday, June 11. The steamship Africa, from Liverpool, on the 31st ult., via Queenstown, on the 1st inst., arrived off the harbor at 4 o'clock this morning, and was towed up to port, in consequence of having damaged her rudder in the ice off Cape Race. The damage will be repaired, and she will sail for Boston at 1 o'clock this afternoon. The Africa reached her dock at 6 A.M. Her dates are two days later than those already received. She has sixty-four passengers.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 10.  To-day there was a skirmish near James Island.  UNITED STATES MILITARY TELEGRAPH, HEADQUARTERS DEPARTMENT POTOMAC, GAINES' HILL, SEVEN MILES FROM RICHMOND, June 2. From the time the army of the Potomac first left Washington the United States Military Telegraph has never for an hour been allowed to remain in the rear. Before reaching his new headquarters Gen. MCCLELLAN almost invariably learns that the wire is on the advance. that an office has already opened at the point designated before he left his old camp, and that communication to the War Department at Washington is open.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 9.  To-day there was a battle at Port Republic, Virginia, between Gen. Shield's and rebel Gen. Jackson's forces.  Gen. Jackson's  QN foot cavalry QN  has marched 400 miles in the last 38 days.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 8.  Gen. Fremont's army was engaged with the rebels at Cross Keys, Virginia, to-day.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 7.  Battle occurred to-day at Union Church near Harrisonburgh, Virginia.  The rebels were routed.  Federal forces shelled Chattanooga, Tennessee, waking the rebels to the realization that they had better fortify that important rail junction or lose it.  NEW ORLEANS, June 7.  Wm. B. Mumford was executed for tearing down the American flag from the mint at New Orleans.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>MEMPHIS, June 6.  This city is now occupied by the Union army.  A great gunboat battle commenced opposite of Memphis.  Seven of the rebel gunboats and rams were destroyed.  The Union fleet under command of Commodore Charles Davis sailed down the Mississippi and engaged the Confederate ships below the bluffs of the city.  Citizens of Memphis lined the bluffs to watch the Union be defeated.  The fight became a free-for-all with gunboats and rams going in every direction either running or attacking.  After an initial assualt by the rams, the gunboats took over the action and blasted the Confederate ships.  Few escaped.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 5.  Artillery battle occurred to-day near New Bridge, near Richmond.  Gen. Fremont attacked the rebel rear guard near Harrisonburgh, Va.  HARPER's FERRY, Tuesday, June 3, 1862. The contest is over for the present at Harper's Ferry, as the rebels have left en masse. Telegrams have given very, very meagre accounts of the state of things existing meantime. The military supervision has been very restrictive.  At the telegraph office the operators said all dispatches must go to Washington.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 4.  A skirmish occurred to-day on James Island, S.C.  MEMPHIS, June 4.  Gen. Pope is reportedly 30 miles south of Corinth, pushing the enemy.  The rebels have burned their works near Fort Pillow.  The evacuation of Fort Pillow was completed after a 52 day seige and the road is open to Memphis.  No dispatches have been received to-day at the War Department from the headquarters of the army of the Potomac. The military telegraph line between Fortress Monroe and headquarters has been broken down by the storm, but is expected to be repaired by to-morrow. No intelligence of public interest has been received from the Valley of the Shenandoah. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 3.   Union troops have landed on James Island, S.C.  WASHINGTON, Tuesday, June 3. The telegraph line to Fort Monroe is working well, but the Associated Press and private dispatches are subject to some delay, owing to the immense amount of important official business passing over the wire. The same is true with regard to the military line from Fort Monroe to headquarters. Important Government messages have precedence over all others, and next the Associated Press reports are forwarded, to give the public the earliest possible information. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, Sunday, June 1. During the whole of the battle of this morning, Prof. LOWE'S balloon was overlooking the terrific scene from an altitude of about two thousand feet. Telegraphic communication from the balloon to Gen. MCCLELLAN, and indirect connection with the military wires, was successfully maintained. Every movement of the enemy was obvious, and instantly reported. This is believed to be the first time in which a balloon reconnaissance has been successfully made during a battle, and certainly the first time in which a telegraph station has been established in the air to report the movements of the enemy, and the progress of a battle. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, June 1.  The battle of Fair Oaks contineud to-day.  This day's fight was very severe, and we regained our position of the day before.  The Union loss in two days' battles was 5,739 in killed, wounded, and missing.  The rebels have been driven out of Strasburgh, Virginia, and the town is occupied by Gen. Fremont's army.  ON GAINES' FARM, NEAR NEW BRIDGE, HENRICO Co., Va., Sunday, June 1, 1862. We retired to rest last evening, anticipating a quiet day on the coming Sabbath. but, alas! for human expectations.  QN Man proposes, but God disposes. QN  It was thought by many that Gen. MCCLELLAN would be loath to commence battle on Sunday.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 31 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 31.  A battle started to-day at Fair Oaks  (Seven Pines), before Richmond.  The result of the fighting was unfavorable for the Union.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 30 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 30.  Front Royal is occupied by our troops.  Rebel Gen. Jackson's forces are beginning to fall back from Harper's Ferry.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 29 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, May 29.  Corinth was evacuated during the night by the rebels.  WASHINGTON, May 29.  A bridge 500 feet long across South Anna Creek, Virginia, was burned by our cavalry, who also captured Ashland, Virginia.  Some light skirmishing has occurred near Seven Pines on the Chickahominy.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 28 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, May 28.  The rebels have reportedly begun retreating from Corinth.  An expedition under Col. Elliott, sent from camp near Corinth to the Sashville and Ohio Railroad, was successful.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 27 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 27.  President Lincoln delivered a message to Congress to-day relative to Secretary Cameron's transactions.  The Steamer Patras has been captured.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 26 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 26.  This capitol is supposed to be in danger.  Gen. Morgan has ordered the Seventh Regiment to Washington.  Other regiments are expected to follow.  Hanover Couthouse, Virginia was captured by Gen. McClellan.  The rebels have been completely routed.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 25 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 25.  Gen. Banks retreated from Winchester to Martinsburgh, Virginia, fighting as he went.  Our troops were attachked early in the morning, and fought during most of the day.  Our baggage trains reached the Potomac.  Another great haul of supplies and munitions was garnered for the Confederacy.  President Lincoln is reportedly getting anxious about the defense of Washington.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 24 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 24.  Gen. Banks' column retreated from Strasburgh to Winchester, Virginia, fighting the rebels gallantly.  A large quantity of provisions and equipment have been abandoned.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 23 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 23.  Terrific fighting has occurred between Gen. Banks' advance under Col. Kenley and the rebels at Front Royal, Virginia.  The battle created a stir in this city, as residents could see rebel Gen. Jackson's legions looming in the distance.  A portion of Gen. McClellan's army has crossed the Chickahominy river.  McClellan's army engaged in three skirmishes, the rebels driven from Mechanicsville.  The rebels were defeated at Lewisburgh, Virginia, in the Mountain Department.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 22.   The CHESAPEAKE TELEGRAPH's longitudinal wires are hooped by a still heavier wire, wound spirally around them, which binds them together, so that they form a strong but flexible tube of iron that effectually protects the conductor and the insulating coat. This is deemed a great improvement over the English system of spiral wire armor which was used in the Atlantic cables, and tended so strongly and incorrigibly to twist and kink. At the time of laying the first temporary cable, there was no heavy cable in this country, or machinery for its expeditions manufacture.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 21 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 21.  THE CHESAPEAKE TELEGRAPH CABLE LAID. The telegraph cable was successfully laid yesterday, across Chesapeake Bay, from Cherrystone to Back River, in Virginia, and the War Department is now in telegraphic communication with Fortress Monroe and Gen. MCCLELLAN's headquarters. The cable, twenty-five miles in length, is heavily armored with sixteen stout iron wires, arranged longitudinally, like the staves of a barrel, around the insulating coat and conductor, and protecting them from all strain by any force short of what would be required to break the covering wires, aggregate strength equals that of a ship's chain.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 20 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>RICHMOND, May 20.  Confederate President Davis, in response to a resolution of the Confederate Congress, announced that Richmond would be defended.  Gen. McClellan's advance reached near New Bridge, eight miles from Richmond.  WASHINGTON, May 20.  Col. STAGER deserves and will receive the thanks of the public for the science, ingenuity, ready resource and untiring energy displayed by him in the construction and management, under circumstances of peculiar difficulty, of the United States Military Telegraph, a machine whose vastness and the important part which it plays in the conduct of the war, few can realize.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 19 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 19.  On the James River, under a flag of truce, the rebels attacked, killed, and took prisoners a party of our men.  The President, by proclamation, repudiated the order of Gen. Hunter liberating the slaves in his department.   THE RELEASED PRISONERS. The recent arrival of National prisoners released from Richmond, on parole, and quartered here at the  QN Soldiers' Rest, QN  are still in total darkness as to what our Government intends to do with them -- whether to pay them off and send them home, or keep them till exchanged and take them into service again. or when anything will be done. Such suspense is little better than their former imprisonment. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 18 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, May 18.  Word received from Corinth that the picket lines are within hearing distance and exchange some fire.  WASHINGTON, May 18.  SICK AND WOUNDED. Information was received here to-night, that the Daniel Webster left Yorktown to-night, under direction of the Sanitary Commission, for Boston, with 200 sick soldiers, fully equipped with surgeons, nurses and hospital supplies. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 17 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 17.  The rebels have been driven across the Chickahominy river at Bottom's Bridge.  The rebels burned the bridge, and obstructed the march of our troops.  CHICAGO. Saturday, May 17. FLOUR dull. WHEAT 1c. TO 2c. lower. sales at 77c. TO 78c. for No. 1, and 67c. TO 70c. for No. 2. CORN dull at 28c. TO 29c. for Mixed, in store. Receipts -- 5,600 bbls. Flour, 26,000 bushels Wheat, 60,000 bushels Corn. FREIGHTS 1E2c. TO 3E4c. lower. 6 1E2c. for Corn to Buffalo. Exchange on Gold unchanged. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 16 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 16.  The United States transport Oriental has wrecked near Cape Hatteras.  OSWEGO, Monday, May 19. FLOUR unchanged. sales,, at  SX 4 75 for Fancy from Spring Wheat. WHEAT dull. sales, 3,000 bushels No. 1 Chicago Spring, at 90c., and 6,300 do., at 88c. CORN quiet. Old Indiana held at 42c. Other grains nominal. CANAL FREIGHTS unchanged. Flour, 25c.. Wheat, 9c. to New-York. Imports -- 2,555 bbls. Flour, 340,000 bushels Wheat, 63,000 bushels Corn, 7,600 bushels Rye. Exports -- 8,186 bbls. Flour, 88,000 bushels Wheat, 24,000 bushels Corn, 6,900 bushels Rye. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 15.  Mounted guerillas attacked our railroad guard near Front Royal, Virginia.  NEW ORLEANS, May 15.  Maj. Gen. Butler has created a sensation with Order Number 28 reading  QN As the officers and soldiers of the United States have been subject to repeated insults form the women calling themselves ladies of New Orleans in return for the most scrupulous non-interference and courtesy on our part, it is ordered that hereafter when any female shall by word, gesture, or movement insult or show contempt for any officer or soldier of the United States she shall be regarded and held liable to be treated as a woman of the town plying her avocation. QN </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 14 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 14.   Light skirmishing has reportedly occurred around Corinth, Mississippi.  BUFFALO, May 14. FLOUR market steady. WHEAT dull. sales 14,000 bush. Chicago Spring and Milwaukee Club, on private terms. CORN dull. sales 30,000 bush. at 36 1E2c. TO 37c. for new, and 38 1E2c. TO 39c. for old. Other grains quiet. WHISKY quiet and steady. CANAL FREIGHTS steady. Imports -- 16,000 bbls. Flour, 262,000 bush. Wheat, 281,000 bush. Corn, 22,000 bush. Rye. Canal Exports -- 2,200 bbls. Flour, 33,600 bush. Wheat, 35,000 bush. Corn.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 13 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 13.  Gen. McClellan's advance guard is reportedly at White House, Virginia.  Gen. McClellan's headquarters are now at Cumberland, near which was skirmishing with the enemy.  ALBANY, May 13. The shipments by tows are numerous. Ten tows have left this city for New-York since Friday. The tows to-day take down at least 500,000 bushels of Wheat. No sales of WHEAT here. RYE 78c.. sales 15,000 bushels. CORN -- Sales at 49c. TO 50c. for old and 47c. TO 48c. and in the afternoon no buyers over 45c. OATS dull, at 40c. BARLEY more active. sales 5,000 bushels Canada West at 80c.  WHISKY -- Sales 200 bbls., at 22 1E4c. TO 23c. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 12 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 12.   It is reported that those in Richmond who can afford it are leaving the city.   Great destruction of tobacco has occurred on the Elizabeth River.  The Rebel steamer Gov. Morton has been captured.    NEW ORLEANS, May 12.  Natchez, Miss. Has surrendered to Flag Ship Officer Farragut's fleet to-day.  Farragut is pushing his way up river toward Foote's river fleet.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 11 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 11.  The rebels set fire to the Merrimac. she blew up at 5 a.m.  The Monitor and other gunboats proceeded toward Norfolk.  PARKERSBURGH, Saturday, May 10, via BALTIMORE, Sunday, May 11. The report of the capture of Arnoldsburgh by the rebels is contradicted. The rebels merely burned some stores at Running Creek. Their subsequent defeat is authoritatively reported by Gen. KELLEY. The telegraph from here to Gen. SCHENCK's position has been cut, and useless all day. News has arrived, however, that our forces are at Franklin, safe. The army of FREMONT and SCHENCK has saved MILROY. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 10 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 10.  Rebel forces set fire to Norfolk Navy Yard before evacuating it and moved west towards Richmond.  Union troops under Maj. Gen. Wool crossed Hampton Roads and occupied the city.  Norfolk is surrendered.  Gosport Navy-yard is burned by the rebels.  Craney Island is abandoned by the rebels.  NEW ORLEANS, May 10.  There is victory on the Mississippi River, near Fort Pillow, in a gunboat engagemtn between eight rebel iron-clads and six Union boats.  Two of the rebel gunboats were blown up and one was sunk.  Gen. Butler seized  SX 80,000 in the office of the Consul of the Netherlands, New Orleans.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 09 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 9.  Gen. McClellan effected a junction with Franklin's Corps at West Point.  The Monitor fired on batteries at Sewell's Point.  Gen. Hunter issued his order declaring free the slaves in Georgia, Florida, and South Carolina.  The evacuation of Pensacola by the rebels is completed.  An engagement has occurred at Slater's Mills, Virginia.  A gunboat fight occurred at Fort Darling, on the James River.  NEW ORLEANS, May 9.  The Battle at Farmington, near Corinth, Mississippi, occurred to-day.  The rebels attacked our position and though our forces were at first compelled to fall back, the fight resulted in a victory for our arms.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 08 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 8.  The iron clad Galena and gunboats Aroostook and Port Royal started up the James River.  The Monitor, Naugatuck and several gunboats left for Sewell's Point which place they attacked.  The Merrimac appeared, but refused to fight.  The Battle of McDowell took place in western Virginia to-day, as rebel Gen. Jackson's men were attacked by forces under Gen. Schenck.  The Federal forces retreated towards Franklin and Jackson pursued, his foot cavalry making their mark.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 07 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 7.  The battle of West Point, Virginia, occurred to-day.  Gen. Franklin's division was engaged ina terrible conflict with the rebels under Gen. Lee, but succeeded in driving them back in the Chickahominy.  The President visited Fort Monroe and the gunboats Galena, Monitor, and Minnesota.  The Merrimac appeared off Craney Island and returned to Norfolk.  Gen. Milroy, in the Mountain Department, fell back after some skirmishing.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 06 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 6.  Williamsburg is occupied by Federal troops.  The Merrimac is moving and the Monitor and other vessels are preparing for action.  The rebels burned their gunboats on the York River.  OSWEGO, Monday, May 5. FLOUR steady for fancy. WHEAT firm. sales 2,500 bush. White Michigan, at  SX 1 25. CORN dull. sales 7,000 bush. New Indiana at 42c. Other grains quiet. CANAL FREIGHTS steady and unchanged. Wheat, 11c.. Corn, 9 1E2c. to New-York, Lake Imports -- 32,100 bush. Wheat, 12,000 bush. Corn. Canal Exports -- 1,000 bbls. Flour, 128,000 bush. Wheat, 36,000 bush. Corn. 15,200 bush. Barley 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 05 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 5.  The battle of Williamsburgh, Virginia, occurred to-day.  After a hard-fought battle in which Union forces came near being defeated, they were victorious and the rebels abandoned their position in the night, leaving sick and wounded to be cared for.  Mr. Lincoln has gone to Fort Monroe aboard the steamer Miami, accompanied by Secretaries Stanton and Chase.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 04 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 4.  Yorktown has been evacuated by the rebels early in the morning and our troops occupied the works.  Brisk fighting has occurred between our cavalry and artillery and the rebels from Yorktown to Williamsburgh.  Gen. McClellan reported the capture of 71 heavy guns and large amounts of ammunition, tents, etc.  Gloucester has been taken.  Rebel Gen. Jackson's men have boarded trains and headed for Staunton where they arrived about 5 p.m.  Morgan's rebel cavalary have reportedly attacked at Lebanon, Tennessee.  The English steamer Circassian has been captured near Havana.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 03 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 3.  Confederate forces are withdrawing from around Yorktown, Virginia.  NEW ORLEANS, May 3.  Rebels have attacked near Farmington, Mississippi.  Two bridges have been destroyed.  CHICAGO, Friday, May 2. FLOUR active and [???] higher. WHEAT 1c. TO 1 1E2c. higher: sales at 83 1E2c. for No. 1, and 77c. TO 77 1E2c. for No. 2. CORN steady at 28 1E2c., on board. OATS firm. Receipts: 7,200 bbls. Flour, 21,000 bush. Wheat, 44,000 bush. Corn. Shipments: 5,600 bbls. Flour, 16,000 bush. Wheat, 7,200 bush. Corn. Exchange unchanged. Gold 2 1E2 premium, FREIGHTS 7c. on Corn and 8c. on Wheat to Buffalo. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 02 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 2.  Rebel Gen. Morgan captured some of our troops at Pulaski, Tennessee.  NEW ORLEANS, May 2.  Gen. Butler has taken possession of the True Delta in New-Orleans.  CHICAGO, Wednesday, April 30.  Wheat steady and unchanged. sales at 81c. TO 82c. for No. 1, and 74c. TO 76c. for No. 2. CORN steady at 27 1E2c. TO 28c. for store. Receipts -- 7,300 bbls. Flour, 12,000 bush. Wheat, 58,000 bush. Corn. Shipments -- 1,900 bbls. Flour, 34,000 bush. Wheat, 56,000 bush. Corn. Exchange and gold unchanged. Freights nominal, 6 1E2c. on Corn and 7c. on Wheat to Buffalo. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 01 May 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, May 1.  Huntsville, Alabama, is now reportedly in possession of Gen. Mitchel.  A rebel battery at White Point, North Edisto Island, has been captured.  The schooner Magnolia is captured.  NEW ORLEANS, May 1.  To-day there was a great rise in the Mississippi. Gen. Benjamin Butler and his troops have assumed control of New Orleans.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 30.  Cannonading has occurred at Yorktown.  The rebels have cut the telegraph wire near Huntsville, Alabama and attacked one of our brigades.  CHICAGO, Wednesday, April 30. The Memphis papers of the 26th April say that at a Convention of Cotton Planters held at Selina, Ala., it was unanimously resolved to restrict the production of cotton to 500 pounds for each hand employed, and advising the cultivation of breadstuffs instead. It was recommended to levy a tax of  SX 25 per bale on all grown over that amount. Martial law is declared in Eastern Tennessee. The Columbus, Ga., works are throwing out six cannon per day. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 29.  Gen. Mitchel has reportedly routed the rebels at Bridgeport, Ala.  A successful skirmish has occurred near Corinth.  NEW ORLEANS, April 29.  The rebel battery near Port Royal is now captured.  MILWAUKEE, Wednesday, April . FLOUR firm. WHEAT lc. higher. sales at 83c.  TO 86c. Receipts -- 2,900 bbls. Flour, 42,000 bush. Wheat. Shipments --1,400 bbls. Flour, 15,200 bush. Wheat. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 28.  The captured steamer Ella Warley arrived at Port Royal, South Carolina.  A skirmish has reportedly occurred at Monterey, Tennessee.  NEW ORLEANS, April 28.  Forts Jackson and St. Philip have surrendered.  The Mississippi River is now open for navigation as far as New Orleans.  Flag Officer Farragut has threatened to bombard the city if the Rebels didn't show some respect for the Union flag.  Rebel gunboats on the Warwick River shelled our encampments.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, April 27.  The American flag has been raised over the mint in New-Orleans.  FORTRESS MONROE, Sunday, April 27. Hon, E.M. Stanton, Secretary of War: A fugitive black, just arrived from Portsmouth, brings the Petersburgh Express of yesterday, which contains the following dispatch: NORFOLK, Friday, April 25. The enemy passed Fort Jackson at 4 o'clock yesterday morning. When the news reached New-Orleans, the excitement was boundless. Martial law was put in full force, and business was completely suspended. All the cotton and steamboats, excepting such as were necessary to transport coin, ammunition, etc., were destroyed. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 26.  A rebel outwork has been captured at Yorktown.  Fort Macon is now occupied by our forces.  NEW ORLEANS, April 26.  Commodore Farragut has demanded the surrender of New-Orleans.  The Mayor replied that the city was at the mercy of our gunboats.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 25.  Fort Macon, North Carolina, has surrendered after a bombardment of ten and a half hours by our fleet and batteries.  Gen. C.F. Smith died to-day.  NEW ORLEANS, April 15.  Our squadron arrived off New Orleans to-day.  The local perople had set the waterfront afire and Flag Officer Farragut anchored his fleet in the river away from the flames.  A rude, nearly violent, and noisy throng met Farragut's officers when they landed to meet the mayor of New Orleans.  The mayor has claimed no authority to surrender the city, not that it matters--the city is taken.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 24.  The destruction of the Dismal Swamp Canal in North Carolina is reportedly completed.  NEW ORLEANS, April 24.  Our fleet passed Forts Jackson and St. Philip below New-Orleans.  The United States Steamer Varuna has been sunk after a most gallant action.  There is great destruction of property in New-Orleans, in anticipation of the approach of our forces.  Rebels near Corinth have been attacked and driven back.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 23.  The gunboat Santiago de Cuba was reportedly chased unsuccessfully by the Nashville.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 22.  Gen. Banks' advance reached Harrisonburgh, Virginia.  The bombardment of Fort Jackson is continuing.  Report received from Richmond that the rebel Congress ws suddenly dispersed.  CINCINNATI, Monday, April 21. FLOUR dull, and prices nominal  SX 4 TO  SX 4 10. WHISKY steady, at 18c. MESS PORK -- There is no demand, and prices are nominal. BULK MEATS are steady, with moderate demand. LARD dull, at 7c. TO 7 7E8c. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 21.  The ship R.C. Files is reportedly captured at Mobile, Ala.  NEW ORLEANS, April 21.  Flag Officer Farragut is reportedly delayed in his approach to New Orleans.  The chains barring the river has been a problem but it is now divided and gives space enough to go through.  CHICAGO, Monday, April 21. FLOUR without change. WHEAT lc. higher: No. 1 quoted at 77c. TO 77 3E4c.. No. 2, 72c. TO 73c. CORN firm and inactive. BEEF CATTLE  SX 2 80 TO  SX 3 for fair to good. Receipts -- 3,000 bbls. Flour, 200 bushels Wheat, 12,000 bushels Corn. Shipments -- 5,000 bbls. Flour, 281,000 bushels Wheat, 123,000 bushels. Corn. Gold unchanged.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, April 20.  Fort Jackson and Fort St. Phillip on the Mississippi River are proving bigger impediments than expected to Federal progress toward New Orleans. To-day, the problem was not the forts themselves, but obstructions to navigation which the forts protected. Flag Officer Farragut sent parties ashore from USS Itasca to sneak in and blow the obstructions up. The bomb failed, but the landing parties did enough damage that a gap was created.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 19.  To-day a battle occurred at Camden (South Mills), North Carolina.  Gen. Banks advance now occupies Sparta, Virginia.  NEW ORLEANS, April 19.  Gen. Mitchell is now in Iuka, Mississippi.  The bombardment of Fort Wright is continuing.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>NEW ORLEANS, April 18.  The bombardment of Forts Jackson and St. Philip, below New Orleans, commenced to-day.  Gen. Reno's expedition landed above Elizabeth City.  WASHINGTON, April 18.  Rebels at Yorktown were repulsed in a night attack on our troops.  Falmouth, opposite Fredericksburg, Virginia, is now occupied by our troops.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 17.  Mount Jackson and Newmarket, Virginia, are occupied by Gen. Bank's troops.  A part of Gen. McDowells' force marched from Warrenton on Fredricksburg.  An expedition, under Gen. Reno, left Newbern, N.C. to attack a body of rebels newar Elizabeth City.  NEW YORK. -- At 4 1E2 o'clock yesterday afternoon Mayor OPDYKE received a telegraphic dispatch from Washington, asking that two of the most powerful hand engines of this City be immediately forwarded to Fortress Monroe. The Assistant to Chief Engineer, Mr. BAULCH, was instructed to select the engines to be sent on. Engines Nos. 16 and 31 were accordingly prepared.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 16.  President Lincoln to-day signed the bill abolishing slavery in the District of Columbia.  An engagement occurred with the rebels at Lee's Mills, near Yorktown.  RICHMON, April 16.  French Minister M. Mercier arrived to-day.  RICHMOND, April 16.  President Davis signed the bill authorizing conscription of every white male between eighteen and thirty five years of age.  This bill provides for substitution of draftees.  NEW ORLEANS, April 16.  Flag Officer Farragut has moved his fleet upriver to just below Forts Jackson and St. Philip.  Troops left Ship Island for New-Orleans.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 15.  Our gunboats shelled the neighborhood of Gloucester, Virginia, near Yorktown.  Ex-Secretary Cameron has been arrested on charge of falsely impersonating Pierce Butler.  Rebels have reportedly opened the levee on the Arkansas side of the Mississippi river near Fort Wright.  Immense destruction of property has occurred from the flooding.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 14.  The bombardment of Fort Pillow has commenced.  A gunboat expedition from the Potomac flotilla up the Rappahannock has begun.  The batteries at Lowry's Point are shelled out. HEADQUARTERS DEPARTMENT OF THE SOUTH, PORT ROYAL, S.C., SUNDAY, April 6, 1862. The sanitary condition of this Department, according to Dr. COOPER, Medical Director, is excellent. There are very few cases in the Hospitals, and the Surgeons are out of business. He pronounces the health of this army superior. What has become of the 33 1E3 per cent. of sick soldiers that we used to hear about at Port Royal? </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 13.  Two bridges on the Mobile and Ohio Railroad are destroyed by an expedition from Pittsburgh Landing.   Saturday, April 12. The Chicago Tribune reporter, who has returned from Pittsburgh Landing, furnishes the following:  QN TAYLOR's and WATERHOUSE's batteries, supported by the Twenty-third Illinois, Seventy-seventh and Fifty-third Ohio regiments, were the first in the fight. Both the Ohio regiments ran, the Seventy-seventh without firing a gun, leaving WATERHOUSE without any support. He fought half an hour, retiring with three of his guns. He was wounded in the thigh by a Minie ball, but not fatally. His battery is badly cut up. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 12.  Gen. Hunter, at Fort Pulaski, declared free all slaves in the Fort and on the Cockspur Island.  There has reportedly been an engagement at Monterey, Virginia.  RICHMOND, April 12.  An expedition from Huntsville, Alabama, has reportedly seized the juncion of the Memphis and Charleston Railroad.  Another expedition from Huntsville arrived at Decatur in time to save the railroad bridge which was found to be in flames.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 11.  The bombardment of Fort Pulaski continued today and the fort surrendered.  The gunboat Merrimac has made her second appearance in Hampton Roads.  She captured three small vessels and then returned.  The District of Columbia emancipation bill passed the House of Representatives.  PITTSBURG LANDING, Tennessee.  Gen. Halleck arrived at Pittsburg Landing to-day.  Huntsville, Alabama, is reportedly occupied by Gen. Mitchel's forces.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 10.   The bombardment of Fort Pulaski has commenced.  Congress has passed a joint resolution calling for the gradual emancipation of the slaves in all the states.  President Lincoln approved the measure and signed it.  PITTSBURG LANDING, Tennessee.  The cleanup continues following the fighting.  Most of the dead soldiers are buried now and the wounded who can be moved are transported down the Tennessee river to hospitals.  </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 9.  There is great rejoicing over the Union victories.  Congratulatory orders are issued by Secretaries Stanton and Welles.  Gen. Halleck left St. Louis to assume command of his department in the field.  RICHMOND, April 9.  The Confederate Congress has reportedly passed a conscription bill to get the necessary manpower for the army.  Many are objecting to this draft law, claiming it infringes upon the liberties of the individual.  It seems people who left the Union for  QN liberty infringement QN  are having no better luck with their new government.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WAR DEPARTMENT, WASHINGTON, D.C., April 8, 1862. D.C. McCALLUM, having been appointed Colonel in the volunteer service, is assigned to special duty in the War Department, as Military Superintendent of Railroads. ANSON STAGER, having been appointed Colonel in the volunteer service, he is assigned to special duty in the War Department, as Military Superintendent of all the telegraph lines in the United States. EDWARDS S. SANFORD, having been appointed Colonel in the volunteer service, he is assigned to special service in the War Department, as Military Supervisor of telegraphic dispatches and army intelligence throughout the United States. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 7.  Island No. 10 reportedly surrendered to-day.  Gen. Pope crossed his army to the Tennesee shore below the Island.  The Battle of Pittsburg Landing is continuing.  Our troops, reinforced, retook the camp and batteries captured by the rebels on the 6th, and caputred a large number of prisoners.  The enemy was put to a full retreat and rebel Gen. A.S. Johnston was killed.  The rebels are commanded by Gens. Polk and Beauregard.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 6.  The battle of Shiloh, or Pittsburg Landing, commenced to-day.  The rebels outnumbered our forces and on this day succeeded in driving our troops back to the protection of the gunboats.  Gunboat Pittsburg rand the batteries at Island No. 10 under a terrific fire from the rebel batteries.  The Carondelet engaged with rebel batteries all day.  Gen. Mitchell reached Shelbyville, Tennessee.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 5.  The Army of the Potomac arrived in front of the enemy's works at Yorktown.  The rebels fired the first shot, after which the cannonading continued with but slight intermission until dark.  The gunboat Carondelet arrived at New Madrid, Missouri, having run the rebel batteries in a terrible thunder storm.  WASHINGTON, Saturday, April 5. EVENTS OF THE COMING WEEK. The coming week will furnish an interesting page in the history of the rebellion and the country. The War and Navy Departments to-day furnish no news that can be published. </description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 4.  The departments of the Shenandoah and of the Rappahannock have been created.  Shelling of the rhe rebel floating battery at Island No. 10 is continuing.  Rebels have attacked forces at Pittsburg Landing.  The following rebel telegram is received by way of Fortress Monroe: MOBILE, Friday, April 4. On Wednesday a Yankee force, two thousand strong, landed at Biloxi, from three vessels, and cut the telegraph line between Mobile and New-Orleans. 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 3.  To-day, the bill for the abolition of slavery in the District of Columbia passed the Senate by a vote of 29 to 14.  Word is received that Apalacicola, Florida, has surrendered to our seamen.  GREAT SALT LAKE CITY, Saturday, March 15. 1862. The new theatre is in full blast two nights per week. This building is at present the most imposing of any in the city.  The telegraph has been set aside for more than a week, and the  QN Pony QN  put into requisition for about forty miles from this city to the east.  Some mountains twenty miles east, and over which the telegraph passes, cannot be crossed by season of storms, intense cold, and depth of snow.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 2.  Gen. McClellan and his staff have reportedly arrived at Ft. Monroe aboard the steamer Commodore.   Gunboats have begun a bombardment of Yorktown.   The prospects of getting a submarine inter-continental telegraph cable in operation before very long are encouraging. Mr. CYRUS FIELD, whose name is traditionally associated with this great project, went to England bearing a dispatch from Mr. SEWARD to Mr. ADAMS, to the effect that the United States Government is prepared to ask Congress to guarantee two per cent. upon a capital of three or three and a half million dollars for twenty or twenty-five years, if England will do the same.</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubdate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 01:00:00 PST</pubdate>
<description>WASHINGTON, April 1, 1862.  Gen. Banks' forces have reportedly moved from Strasburgh to Woodstock, Virginia, and are engaged with the enemy at Woodstock.  Thoroughfare Gap, Virginia, is occupied by Gen. Geary's army.  Col. Roberts men spiked the guns of the upper rebel battery at Island No. 10.  The pioneer steamer passed through the nely constructed coanal from above Island No. 10 to New-Madrid.  President Lincoln's Emancipation and Compensation resolutions passed the Senate. </description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
